<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>law &#8211; rLOVEutioners</title>
	<atom:link href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tag/law/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/</link>
	<description>revoution for evolution</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 14:49:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Bhagat Singh</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/bhagat-singh/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 07:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=427</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[“Leave sentimentalism aside. Be prepared to face the facts. Revolution is a very difficult task. It is beyond the power of any man to make a revolution. Neither can it be brought about on any appointed date. It is brought about by special environments, social and economic. The function of an organized party is to &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/bhagat-singh/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Bhagat Singh</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre id="tw-target-text" class="tw-data-text tw-ta tw-text-small" dir="ltr" data-placeholder="Translation" data-fulltext=""><span lang="hi">
“Leave sentimentalism aside. Be prepared to face the facts. Revolution is a very difficult task. It is beyond the power of any man to make a revolution. Neither can it be brought about on any appointed date. It is brought about by special environments, social and economic. The function of an organized party is to utilize such an opportunity offered by these circumstances. [To] prepare the masses and organize the forces for the revolution is a very difficult task. And that requires a very great sacrifice on the part of the revolutionary workers.”

<strong>Bhagat Singh</strong> in a letter “To the young political workers”, 2 February 1931

</span></pre>
<pre id="tw-target-text" class="tw-data-text tw-ta tw-text-small" dir="ltr" data-placeholder="Translation" data-fulltext=""><span lang="hi">
भावुक होना छोड़ दें।
और सच का सामना करने के लिए तैयार हो जाऍ।
क्रांति करना एक असाधारण कार्य है।
और क्रांति का उद्घोष करना किसी एक व्यक्ति विशेष की शक्ति से परे है।
और न ही इसे किसी एक सुनिश्चित समय पर लाया जा सकता है।
क्रांति विशेषतः, अनुकूल सामाजिक और आर्थिक परिस्थितियों द्वारा लाई जाती है।
एक सुव्यवस्थित संगठन का कर्तव्य इन परिस्थितियों द्वारा उत्पन्न किए जाने वाले अवसरोॅ का सदुपयोग करना है।
[जनता को] क्रांति के लिये तैयार करना और क्रांतिकारी ताकतोॅ को सॅगठित करना एक बहुत ही मुश्किल काम है।
और इसके लिए क्रांतिकारीयोॅ को एक महान त्याग करने की आवश्यकता है।

<strong>भगत सिॅह</strong> का २ फरवरी १९३१ को "युवा राजनैतिक कार्यकर्ताओॅ " के लिये लिखा पत्र 

</span></pre>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biggest Political Mistake in Indian History</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 12:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=38</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It all happened just before the Indian Independence Day and it happened so fast that no body could even think the aftermaths of the event would be so disastrous that the whole world would laugh at a nation which was divided into 2 by some lazy people who never thought that things could be worked &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Biggest Political Mistake in Indian History</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It all happened just before the Indian Independence Day and it happened so fast that no body could even think the aftermaths of the event would be so disastrous that the whole world would laugh at a nation which was divided into 2 by some lazy people who never thought that things could be worked out. Yes I am talking about the Partition of India and Pakistan.</p>
<p><span id="more-1299"></span>Today is the Independence Day and I want to give you a reason to think. I have a question for you guys.</p>
<blockquote><p>Do you think Jawahar Lal Nehru did the right thing by agreeing to Muhammad Ali Jinnah ?</p></blockquote>
<p>Before you come to any conclusions, I just want to let you know that I am just asking for your opinion. I have put across my thoughts, now I need to know what you think. Pt. Jawahar Lal Nehru when agreed to Muhammad Ali Jinnah would have thought that now India would live happily ever after. But I guess they were wrong, I mean they have been wrong all throughout. Pakistan has gone so far sometimes after the division that its unbearable, but still we Indians believe in Peace. We still believe in talks with our neighbor countries. We still believe that <strong>“Kutte ki poonch Seedhi ho jayegi”.</strong> We still think that now we will live without any fear since our Prime Minister is a bit aggressive now. What the hell ?</p>
<p>My only point is that its our politicians who have been giving us pain all through out . Had Jawahar Lal Nehru not agreed to Muhammad, we would have had a single country spanning a long Kashmir having the most amazing tourist place ever. Imagine Afridi and Sehwag opening for India. No power would have stopped that India to win against any country. What a scene would that be. Imagine the biggest tourist place in the world for its beautiful mountains, a place known to be heaven on earth. We could have been so advanced today that the whole world would have envied us.</p>
<p>But let’s face the reality. Since both the countries are not in good terms and are always fighting, we spend over billions on getting the most latest and deadliest weapons from Israel and Russia. Just imagine 3-4% of GDP of India and Pakistan going into preparing for battle against each other. Imagine this money spent for good cause, for betterment of both countries. None of the countries people have proper food to eat, but we want to fight. The whole world looks at us as a country of poor, which some time ago used to be the “<strong>Golden Bird</strong>.” Had we spent those billions for improving our infrastructure then what a country India would have been. People would have lead a life which they deserve rather than leading their lives in fear of getting blasted in some suicide bombing.</p>
<p>I really feel that our life was fcuked on that day when India and Pakistan parted their ways. Just wait for some time, its quite possible that India will get partitioned further because we have the same Congress in center which made all this possible. Rumors are that China is thinking of creating a mess in India and trying to divide India into several parts.</p>
<p>What do you say ?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I see a Policeman on motorbike without a Helmet, I stop him and hand him over a ticket</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 13:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=43</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[How cool will that be ? I mean I was just wondering for quite some time now that how nice it would be if we could really take control of our law enforcement. Imagine while roaming on the road you see someone breaking the law and you take out your camera, take a picture while &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">I see a Policeman on motorbike without a Helmet, I stop him and hand him over a ticket</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How cool will that be ? I mean I was just wondering for quite some time now that how nice it would be if we could really take control of our law enforcement. Imagine while roaming on the road you see someone breaking the law and you take out your camera, take a picture while he is breaking the traffic rules. Catch hold of him. Show him the picture and hand over the ticket to him. I mean imagine the force we would have on roads and people will think twice before doing anything wrong.</p>
<p>People may use the power for wrong doing but I think we can start with some intelligent and responsible people like Bus Conductor, Shopkeepers who are sitting on a road watching it all the time. A Pan wallah on the Traffic Signal.</p>
<p>I am thinking of creating another website where I urge people to submit such pictures where people are captured while breaking the law. And our law enforcement team has to just identify the person and fine him/her.</p>
<p>Think about it. Bye !</p>
<p>Let me know your thoughts by posting your comments.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indian Government asking Social Networks and Google to censor political parties and politicians. But why?</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/indian-government-ranks-3rd-in-terms-of-reteriving-data-from-google/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/indian-government-ranks-3rd-in-terms-of-reteriving-data-from-google/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 18:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=75</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Recently read a news about US government asking Google to provide lots and lots of data related which is related to the services Google provides. I am sure they must be utilizing this data for get to the corrupts. And then automatically me being a typical Indian wanted to check our country’s  rank in that &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/indian-government-ranks-3rd-in-terms-of-reteriving-data-from-google/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Indian Government asking Social Networks and Google to censor political parties and politicians. But why?</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently read a news about US government asking Google to provide lots and lots of data related which is related to the services Google provides. I am sure they must be utilizing this data for get to the corrupts. And then automatically me being a typical Indian wanted to check our country’s  rank in that list. To my surprise we rank 3rd in that list after US and Brazil. Wow.. It feels great to be in a such a list. Well that’s one side of the story I was thinking. But after reading the data requests that Google received I started thinking about what would our government departments have actually asked for. Checkout for analysis after the break.</p>
<p><span id="more-2453"></span><br />
<img loading="lazy" class="alignnone" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932im_/http://img201.imageshack.us/img201/1192/indiangovernmentgoogled.png" alt="" width="600" height="321" /><br />
<strong>About Google Transparency</strong> : Its an interactive map of Government Requests that shows the number of government inquiries for information about users and requests for Google to take down or censor content. The interactive Traffic graphs provide information about traffic to Google services around the world. Each graph shows historic traffic patterns for a given country/region and service. By illustrating outages, this tool visualizes disruptions in the free flow of information, whether it’s a government blocking information or a cable being cut.</p>
<p>Below is the graph that shows the requests from Indian Government agencies to Google in the past 1 year.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932im_/http://img52.imageshack.us/img52/6910/searchpatterngoogletran.png" alt="" width="600" height="177" /></p>
<p>I’ll leave you guys with that thought because I need to go to bed now. OK, still let me give you some perspective. Have you ever looked at <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932/http://www.revolutioners.com/where-the-hell-are-indian-web-developers/">our government websites</a>. I have talked about it earlier as well. But I think the more we are so called developing the more our government is showcase that they are technically sound. I mean I am not talking about the politicians. We bloody pay some great amount of money in taxes can’t we hire some sound technical guys to handle these stuffs. Alright I think I am deviating from the topic.</p>
<p>OK, I was suppose to give you some perspective. Alright, I was just looking at my blog and saw an advertisement on my blog via adsense that I have setup. I did not click on the ad but copied the link to the URL. You believe me it was <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932/http://www.delhitrafficpolice.nic.in/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Delhi Traffic Police</a> Delhi Traffic Police is advertising via Google Adwords. Anyways, then in curiosity I went to check out the website. Our government needs to accept the fact that their developers su*k.  So there were some nice presentations regarding common wealth games. I could not believe my eyes by looking at the presentation. I mean such a big country and not even one single fucking person in India who can make a good looking presentation. You don’t believe me check <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932/http://www.delhitrafficpolice.nic.in/cwg1.ppt" target="_blank" rel="noopener">this out</a>. And yeah I was in an impression since it being a website where the whole world would be browsing to look for updated information but then I saw a link to download flash player which still links to Macromedia site. Thanks to Adobe that they have redirected it to the right place.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/indian-government-ranks-3rd-in-terms-of-reteriving-data-from-google/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smoking Ban Act, India – Must Read</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/smoking-and-tobacco-facts-and-figures-india-smoking-ban-india/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/smoking-and-tobacco-facts-and-figures-india-smoking-ban-india/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 18:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=80</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Let’s see the scene of tobacco and smoking in India first. OK, some facts and figures about Smoking and Tobacco in India. In India, tobacco use causes nearly 40 percent of all health problems and 50 percent of all cancers, according to Health Minister, Anbumani Ramadoss. In India The tobacco contributes to 56.4% and 44.9% &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/smoking-and-tobacco-facts-and-figures-india-smoking-ban-india/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Smoking Ban Act, India – Must Read</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Let’s see the scene of tobacco and smoking in India first. OK, some facts and figures about Smoking and Tobacco in India.</p>
<ul>
<li>In India, tobacco use causes nearly 40 percent of all health problems and 50 percent of all cancers, according to Health Minister, Anbumani Ramadoss.</li>
<li>In India The tobacco contributes to 56.4% and 44.9% of cancers in men and women, respectively.</li>
<li><strong>India ranks 2nd in smoking cigarette in top 10 countries.</strong></li>
<li>Nearly 17 percent of students in India, aged 15 and under, use some form of tobacco, mainly cigarettes, according to a survey conducted by the World Health Organization.</li>
<li>India has the largest number of oral cancer cases in the world which is due to tobacco.</li>
<li>In India, an estimated 120 million people smoke. But the problem is that smoking in India is on rising side unlike Western countries.</li>
<li>Cigarettes compromise just 19 percent of tobacco consumption in India however Bidis account for 53 percent, according to the Bidi Smoking and Public Health report by the Union Ministry of Health and Family.</li>
<li><strong>Around 1 billion Bidis are sold in India every year.</strong> Bidis contain more tar, nicotine and other toxic substances but less tobacco than traditional cigarettes.</li>
<li>Tobacco smoking accounts for 82% of Chronic obstructive lung disease in India.</li>
</ul>
<p>It’s been around 1 year now that Indian Government imposed ban on smoking in public places including government and private offices. You might not know but this act was in existence for 2 years before our government thought of implementing it seriously. Seriously, imagine. We create acts, put them in files, make a pile out of it, put them in a room somewhere and then don’t look at them for 3-4 years. Then suddenly you wake up and try to enforce everything. And I’ll tell you some facts about this so called smoking ban in public places today. Well, I think I don’t really have to tell you anything as most of you already know it to some extent.</p>
<p>Alright let’s first discuss what the ban exactly is. As per the government, no one is allowed to smoke in public places including public transportation and public offices etc. As per the rules, smoking is banned in shopping malls, cinema halls, public/private work place, hotels, banquet halls, discotheques, canteen, coffee house, pubs, bars, airport lounge, railway stations. Public places cover all government, private and public sector offices as well. I work with an MNC and believe me there people adhere to the regulation. People go out of the offices for smoke. Earlier employees could smoke in the office premises but ever since the smoking ban everyone is prohibited to smoke inside the office premises. Also, any employer found to be letting its employees smoke inside the office premises are supposed to be penalized. Moreover I think people working with big MNCs in India are mature enough to understand what it means for our country. We tell clients coming from abroad that there are restrictions on smoking inside the premises, so we don’t want them to see us smoking in there.</p>
<p><span id="more-2359"></span>Alright, that’s the rule now lets see how is our government who imposed the ban is doing about it. You remember me <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104834/http://www.revolutioners.com/visit-to-mtnl-sanchaar-haat-a-must-read/">visiting MTNL office</a>, I saw employees smoking inside the building. Well, that was not it. I shave seen many more government offices with people smoking inside the offices. But today was the height of everything, I went to a government office today (would not want to quote) and saw employee smoking in the building that too on his seat as well. And the head of the office was also smoking in the office.</p>
<p>I just want to understand why has it always been like this? <strong>Why do we citizens only have to follow all the rules?</strong> Why the people who create the rules, don’t have to adhere to them.</p>
<p>And believe me its not the only thing which is wrong these days Things like these keep happening in our country. It has been in existence in one or another form with each and every government department of India. <strong>For example, Delhi Police does not need any helmet while driving on the road but they want each and every rider in Delhi to wear helmet and don’t miss a chance of not giving ticket to the rider if he/she is not wearing the helmet.</strong>Similarly they want everyone to wear seat-belts while driving even if the traffic is not even moving. <em>Every government department you go in, you’d find yourself on the verge of having an argument all the time</em>. People don’t really seem to take their jobs seriously.</p>
<p>I am not able to understand the mentality of our government employees as in why do these people behave like this. I mean its good that you are sitting there in a government office but aren’t you suppose to work. Yeah, let me not just start that. I’d need an entire book on that just one post won’t be enough I guess.</p>
<p>Don’t know when would we be free, free as in FREE…! The ultimate question is should we try and ban these things from selling or should we ban smoking of cigarettes. ?</p>
<p>Some interesting reading about tobacco and smoking.</p>
<ul>
<li>Avoiding tobacco adds 20 years to the life of a teenager.</li>
<li><strong>In India, 900,000 people die due to tobacco related diseases per year.</strong></li>
<li>Tobacco smoking accounts for 82% of Chronic obstructive lung disease in India.</li>
<li><strong>Tobacco indirectly causes lung tuberculosis.</strong> Prevalence of TB is about 3 times as great among the ever-smokers as among the never-smokers. The heavier the smoking, either cigarettes or bidis, the greater the prevalence of TB among smokers. Mortality from TB is 3 to 4 times as great in ever-smokers as in never-smokers.</li>
<li><strong>About half of the teenagers who use tobacco will eventually be killed by it (about a quarter in middle age and a quarter in old age).</strong></li>
<li>It is estimated that India as compared to any other country will have the fastest rise in tobacco related deaths each year.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/smoking-and-tobacco-facts-and-figures-india-smoking-ban-india/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
