<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Personal &#8211; rLOVEutioners</title>
	<atom:link href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/category/personal/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/</link>
	<description>revoution for evolution</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 13:59:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>मैॅ तो बस बोलता हूॅ</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/main-to-bas-bolta-hoon/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/main-to-bas-bolta-hoon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 05:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/?p=526</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[लिखने का शौक तो नहीॅपर शब्दोॅ मेॅ रस घोलता हूॅजाने अनजाने ही सहीपर कडवा सच बोलता हूॅजीवन के अनसुलझे रहस्योॅ कोपरत दर परत खोलता हूॅ इसलिए &#8230;मैॅ तो बस बोलता हूॅ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>लिखने का शौक तो नहीॅ<br>पर शब्दोॅ मेॅ रस घोलता हूॅ<br>जाने अनजाने ही सही<br>पर कडवा सच बोलता हूॅ<br>जीवन के अनसुलझे रहस्योॅ को<br>परत दर परत खोलता हूॅ<br><br>इसलिए &#8230;<br>मैॅ तो बस बोलता हूॅ<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/main-to-bas-bolta-hoon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meet, US</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/meet-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 08:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=408</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="683" src="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/IMG_0858-1024x683.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-579" srcset="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/IMG_0858-1024x683.jpg 1024w, http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/IMG_0858-300x200.jpg 300w, http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/IMG_0858-768x512.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How about telemarketers get charged 1000 rs for calling you</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 19:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=95</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Every now and then my mind keeps flooding with some insane ideas. But after some time when I think about it, it all starts making some sense. I was on my way to office 2-3 days ago and I get a call from someone trying to sell me some Life Insurance. This guy has been &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">How about telemarketers get charged 1000 rs for calling you</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every now and then my mind keeps flooding with some insane ideas. But after some time when I think about it, it all starts making some sense. I was on my way to office 2-3 days ago and I get a call from someone trying to sell me some Life Insurance. This guy has been calling me for i don’t know may be for the last 4-5 days continuously. I know like me you are also frustrated with all those telemarketers calling you day and night and selling stuff in which you are not even remotely interested. But I have an idea to deal with this situation. I don’t know the feasibility to implement it. May or may not be possible.</p>
<p><span id="more-2318"></span>How about a service which lets you convert your normal mobile phone number to a premium call rate number. I mean I get to choose how much a person pays for a call whenever someone calls me. For example anyone calling me on my mobile would end up paying 100 Rs per minute. This way I would not be able to stop them calling me but I can ask them to call me up again and again and get them to spend money. I take revenge. And the amazing part is that you get paid a handsome amount of money at the end of the month. Because this is how premium call rate numbers work. The organization that owns these premium call rate numbers gets the share from the total revenue generated.</p>
<p><strong>Now let’s talk about the downsides of this idea</strong>. Suppose I setup this service on my mobile and one of my old friends gets hold of my number and calls me up. He would end up paying 100 bucks for the call. Well I have a solution for that. I ask my operator to warn the users who are calling me about the premium call rate. That way anyone calling me would think twice before calling me.</p>
<p><strong>But what about my friends, family and colleagues?</strong> Would they ever be able to call me on my cell phone?  Hmm.. I thought about that also actually. I got this idea from the recently held Apple Special Event, where Steve announced Ping. In Ping you get to choose who follow you. So basically, you get to choose a white list of numbers who would not be charged premium rates.</p>
<blockquote><p>How about your own premium number to fight spam?</p></blockquote>
<p>I know there are solutions like Block List which I used to use. But that is not universal to all phones. I think only on Nokia phones this functionality is available. And moreover the hassle of adding them in the list and keeping them updated. It’s not just worth it. And don’t forget about the limitation of number of phone numbers that you can add.</p>
<p>I need to think about some idea on Mobile Spam, the text messages because they seem to be bugging more than the phone calls.</p>
<p>Oh, one more thing. Did I tell you that well before even any mobile operator implemented this caller tune thing I had this idea in mind. I thought why not have something different than rather just that old boring Tring Tring. And to my surprise Indian Operators introduced Caller Tune to us.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top must do after you write a New Blog Post</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/after-what-to-do-after-writing-a-new-blog-post/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/after-what-to-do-after-writing-a-new-blog-post/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 10:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=172</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Do you also feel the same way as I do. I mean do you not feel a bit relaxed after writing that post. I get a sense of accomplishment every time and I am sure you do too. But remember that when you’re done writing a new blog post, you still have some work to &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/after-what-to-do-after-writing-a-new-blog-post/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Top must do after you write a New Blog Post</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you also feel the same way as I do. I mean do you not feel a bit relaxed after writing that post. I get a sense of accomplishment every time and I am sure you do too. But remember that when you’re done writing a new blog post, you still have some work to do. There are many things you should be doing after writing a new post and I will try and explain a few of the most important things you should do after every blog post you write.</p>
<p><strong>#1 Edit Your Post</strong></p>
<p>Well, I do it all the time and still end up with some minor typos. Why I am saying you should always edit your post is because I don’t know about other people but I like to write my posts in one go. I am not that blogger who sits back and writes one post in 1 month. So most of the time I write my posts in 10 to 15 minutes max. Don’t publish your post until it has been completely edited and checked for spelling/grammar errors. Read over it carefully and make sure everything flows and that everything is written correctly. Like I said, It doesn’t have to be perfect but you don’t want it to be full of errors either. You also want to make sure all your spelling and punctuation is correct. One good way to do this is to paste it into MS Word and run a spell check. Like I am doing it right now <img class="wp-smiley" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308094704im_/http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_razz.gif" alt=":P" /></p>
<p><strong>#Share the Post on Social Networks</strong></p>
<p>In the recent past a lot of Social boom has happened so everyone is jumping in the wagon. Therefore the next thing you want to do after you write a blog post is to share your post with as many people as you can. There are a lot of social bookmarking websites on the internet that you can use to do this. Some of the best and most popular are Stumbleupon, Digg, Delicious, Mixx, and Reddit. Make sure you bookmark your post to at least a few of them.</p>
<p><strong>#3 Tweet It</strong></p>
<p>Twitter has really picked up the speed in social networking in the last year or so. Its like the small version of big posts. Sometimes people want to elaborate on their thinking and sometimes they just post a shorter version of that. Any which ways twitter is hot nowadays. So after you write a new blog post you should always “tweet” it. Twitter is really popular right now and it only takes a few seconds to tweet your followers about your post. This can give you extra traffic and maybe even a few people will retweet it or link to your post, which will help even more. So make sure you take a little time to tweet about your post whenever you publish a new one.</p>
<p>Alright, that should be enough to get you started. Just remember that after you finish writing a blog post you aren’t done with the work. If you do the things listed above then you will have a much better shot at building a successful blog.</p>
<p><strong>#4 Comment on other Blogs with post link</strong></p>
<p>This in my views is one of the most effective way ot getting traffic to your blog or site. As soon as you write a post, start going to your favorite blogs and comment with url of the new post that you written. Give the Name accordingly. Some Blog admins don’t mind accepting your name as your blog name if the comment adds something to the conversation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/after-what-to-do-after-writing-a-new-blog-post/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to use Hiren Boot CD programs with switches</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/notron-ghost-switches-hiren-bootcd-application-switches-command-prompt/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/notron-ghost-switches-hiren-bootcd-application-switches-command-prompt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 10:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=176</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Last night it look me over 3 hours to understand the problem why Norton Ghost was acting weird. I was not able to clone my laptop hard drive with an existing image. The image was correct and consistent however Norton Ghost while restoring kept giving me some inconsistency errors. Image was created with a 160 &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/notron-ghost-switches-hiren-bootcd-application-switches-command-prompt/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">How to use Hiren Boot CD programs with switches</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Last night it look me over 3 hours to understand the problem why Norton Ghost was acting weird. I was not able to clone my laptop hard drive with an existing image. The image was correct and consistent however Norton Ghost while restoring kept giving me some inconsistency errors. Image was created with a 160 GB partition and I was restoring it on 320 GB drive. I tried both ways to restore. Image to Drive and Image to Disk. But every time it gave me inconsistency errors.<br />
<span id="more-2028"></span></p>
<p>Finally after some research I found out the solution for the problem. There are various switches that you can use on command line Ghost. I had to use <strong>-ntc-</strong> switch. This switch basically Disables NTFS contiguous run allocation which makes the image to be restored on any hard drive with any size of drive. But unfortunately when you use Hiren Bootcd you can not run Ghost with any switch.</p>
<p>But suddenly all my problems were solved. Actually what happens is whenever you run any program from the menu it first gets extracted and then gets saved in the RAM drive created by the CD. That’s it. That was the solution.</p>
<p>To run Ghost or any other program from Hiren Bootcd with switches follow the steps below:</p>
<ol>
<li>Boot with Hiren BootCD.</li>
<li>Run a program of your choice. I was using Ghost so I will continue with Ghost with the example.</li>
<li>Once Ghost is up and running <strong>Exi</strong>t it without doing anything.</li>
<li>It will take you back to the Command Prompt.</li>
<li>Now use <strong>Ghost.exe -ntc-</strong></li>
<li>That’s it. Similarily you can use any program with their compatible switches. All you need to do is run it first and then exit it.</li>
</ol>
<p>Pretty Simple huh !!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/notron-ghost-switches-hiren-bootcd-application-switches-command-prompt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What if there was nothing immoral</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/lets-for-once-assume-that-there-is-nothing-bad-or-wrong-in-this-world/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/lets-for-once-assume-that-there-is-nothing-bad-or-wrong-in-this-world/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 13:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Well lets just once assume in this world. I mean let the person kill someone if he wants to. Let a person rob someone if he wishes to. Let anyone become a suicide bomber or a terrorist if he/she wants to do it under someone’s influence. What a world would that be. It would be &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/lets-for-once-assume-that-there-is-nothing-bad-or-wrong-in-this-world/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">What if there was nothing immoral</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Well lets just once assume in this world. I mean let the person kill someone if he wants to. Let a person rob someone if he wishes to. Let anyone become a suicide bomber or a terrorist if he/she wants to do it under someone’s influence. What a world would that be. It would be horrific, right. No, It would not be horrible, It would be great because the way I look at it is that if we use the technology to an extent where all these bad activities would not even be remotely possible. I would want to live in a world like that.<br />
<span id="more-1670"></span></p>
<p>I wish technology advances so much that it does not leave any chance of error for humans. For example</p>
<ul>
<li>People could freely shop online and never be afraid of their bank details being leaked and hacked.</li>
<li>I want the examination system to be like that it does not let anyone cheat.</li>
<li>A world where if a crime is committed the culprit can never escape and gets the punishment instantly.</li>
<li>A world where piracy will not be illegal. It will be legal because it would be upto the publishers to protect their creations/products/music/movies etc. And because the technology would be so strong that it does not even leave a chance for anyone to pirate.</li>
<li>Where Microsoft does not have to be afraid over WGA cracks anymore because they know that their activation process is so amazing that no one can make copies.</li>
</ul>
<p>What do you think about it ? Do you wanna live into that kind of world. Where you have all the freedom to do anything in this world and no one would complain about that.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/lets-for-once-assume-that-there-is-nothing-bad-or-wrong-in-this-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Learn to Drive rash on Indian Roads</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2009 19:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What is this all about ? What the crap ? What the hell is wrong with Kuldeep ? Why is he writing on such a pathetic topic? While your mind is flooded with all these kinds of questions, there goes one more. Ever wondered how any people die just because of rash driving. I know &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Learn to Drive rash on Indian Roads</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What is this all about ? What the crap ? What the hell is wrong with Kuldeep ? Why is he writing on such a pathetic topic? While your mind is flooded with all these kinds of questions, there goes one more. Ever wondered how any people die just because of rash driving. I know what you are thinking now. Alright let me tell you.l I did some digging on this. We are number 1 yey ! According to World Road Statistic data 2007 around 1 million people died in road accident. Now what do you think how many of those 1 million people would have died because of their own mistakes. I would say not more than 50%. So how did the rest of the half a million people die in road accidents. The answer is they all died because some jackass was driving rash.</p>
<p>I also drive rash, But I drive with safety and that too when its required and most of all with intelligence. Yeah, I know what you are thinking. But believe me I don’t act like a school kid who has been just handed over the keys of the car or bike. I have been driving car and riding bikes for the last 8-9 years now. And you know what I am from the most crowded part of India. I am from Delhi. I think anyone who has driven safely on Delhi roads can drive anywhere in the world.  Let me get to the point now because I guess I would have to dedicate a whole new blog to just write about Indian Traffic Rules and Regulations. Its really pathetic how Indian people don’t even think about the traffic rules. And the funny part is the same people who jump traffic signals and break traffic rules, if they go in a different country follow every damn traffic rules. Ever thought why is that the case? Well let me tell you. Its because of our government servants.When we go in a different country we know if we break any traffic rules, the penalty will be so Hugh that they would have to rip their asses off to pay the ticket money. On the other hand in India its mere 100 bucks and that too if you don’t have any policemen in distant relation. But don’t worry if you don’t have any policemen in relation you can just bribe these guys. Just slip a 50 Rs note and you are free.</p>
<p>Alright lets get to the point now. Here are some tips to drive rash on Indian Roads. Believe me they are tried and tested and learnt after 8-9 years of experience.</p>
<h3><strong>Always Drive on left side of the road</strong></h3>
<p>Whenever I have to drive fast, I always drive on the left side of the road. Specially at a crossing. I have met with 2-3 accidents on my bike while I was on the right hand side of the road. The problem is when you are driving on the right hand side you can’t see what is coming from the front because your view is blocked by the railing. <em>And we being Indians we don’t stop/slow down on intersections</em>. Trust me most of the accidents on the road happen because of this reason only. You can’t see what is coming from the right hand side but by the time you realize it, its too late.  But at the same time if you are driving on the left side of the road you have a really good time and view to see if someone is coming from front or right hand side of the road. I have tested it and it really works. I have escaped/saved a lot of accidents this way. So the solution is start driving on the left side while crossing an intersection. I think those railings should be removed from the divider at an intersection for at least around 100 meters so that someone coming on the road can look at both sides of the road if someone is coming or not.</p>
<h3><span class="removed_link" title="http://www.revolutioners.com/commonwealth-games-2010-things-you-can-do-to-contribute-for-a-successful-event/"><strong>Always follow Traffic rules</strong></span></h3>
<p>Indians have just re-engineered the whole traffic signal system. <strong>For us Red means if there is place don’t stop and go on. Yellow is, speed up its going to turn red. Green is, it will turn red hurry up, honk honk and honk.</strong> Damn this is funny. OK. Now this is one of the smartest tips if you ask me. Now you would be thinking how can it be a tip for driving rash. Well the thing is you can drive rash without breaking the rules as well. I mean drive fast, but don’t jump red lights, don’t change lane too often, don’t jump in front of someone like an idiot, don’t keep honking. You know I only drive fast and so called rash when its really required. There is no such pleasure then driving/riding slow. So drive fast/rash until and unless there is a need to it.</p>
<h3><strong>Always look through</strong></h3>
<p>How many times it happened that you were driving really nice and suddenly the person in front of you just stood on the break and your car went creening on the road and you managed to stop the car just an inch away from the car in front of you. It has happened right. So the thing is, if you are driving make sure you are not just watching the car in front of you. Look through the car in front of you. If you see that driver driving madly and stopping suddenly because of xyz reason you have a good amount of time.</p>
<p>I usually not look at the car just in front of me. I watch right into the rear and front mirror and look at the car next to the car in front of me. This way, I keep an eye on the car in front and concentrate on the car that is running in front of the car I am driving behind.</p>
<h3><strong>Don’t play it loud</strong></h3>
<p>Well I am sure people who drive rash they have a nice music system in their cars. When you drive rash and the music is loud you can’t hear anyone honking from the back and then you suddenly try to change the lane. This gets dangerous when that vehicle is two wheeler. So stay put, don’t drive out loud.</p>
<h3><strong>Don’t drink and drive</strong></h3>
<p>Here is the thing. You are drunk and you’ve got friends who are also drunk. Get a drunkard’s cab. Yeah they are in business now. Now what, you show off. You show them how well you can drive. In that madness you drive here and there and that’s it. That is the beginning of the end of your life. Don’t drink and drive. I am speaking from my personal experience.</p>
<p><strong>Share it if you would like to save someone’s life.</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Birth of Revolutioners.com</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/birth-of-revolutioners/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 07:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=184</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[outpowerhosting: ok.. ok.. gimme your domain name once again.. make sure it's spelt correctly Kuldeep: accha u suggest a good one outpowerhosting: 2 mins gone :D Kuldeep: I'll give u the background koi nahin bahut time hai tere paas outpowerhosting: k letshelpgovt.com? Kuldeep: I will be running a forum where people talk about their problems &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/birth-of-revolutioners/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Birth of Revolutioners.com</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>outpowerhosting: ok.. ok.. gimme your domain name once again.. make  sure it's spelt correctly
 
Kuldeep: accha u suggest a good one
 
outpowerhosting: 2 mins gone :D
 
Kuldeep: I'll give u the background
 koi nahin
 bahut time hai tere paas
 outpowerhosting: k
 letshelpgovt.com?
 
Kuldeep: I will be running a forum where people talk about their problems that they face in their day to day life
 and then people will suggest the soultion
 
outpowerhosting: helpme.com
 not available
 
Kuldeep: and may be ... may be . we can get some politicians or govt officials to look at those ideas and imprelemt them
 
outpowerhosting: hmmmm.. good thought
 
Kuldeep: accha everythng apart
 idea kaisa hai
 
outpowerhosting: helpmeindia.com
 
Kuldeep: ab to tujhe paise bhi mil gaye hai
 jhoot mat boolna
 outpowerhosting: lol..never lied
 
Kuldeep: accha cloremint khate ho
 
outpowerhosting: sometimes
 
Kuldeep: tabhi...
 accha think about domain name
 i gave u the idea
 it will not be limited to india
 
outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: for ur informaiton
 thats why i opted ,com domain
 outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: agar chali to i am thinking of a very large community
 outpowerhosting: but the domain you suggested had no relevance to the idea.. I first though it was about complaints to the govt and help them in some way

 Kuldeep: thats why i was asking you for more bandwidth
 haan
 outpowerhosting: we'll see.. as the site grows.. I'll help out with the needs
 
Kuldeep: first let govt know what is wrong
 and then people from community will give idea that what should govt do
 they'll discuss about that
 
outpowerhosting: don't' you think it's better to anchor it to one region..
 because it's too vast a subject to be a worldwide one
 
Kuldeep: well i am assuming not much people other than Asian continent will turn up in the forum
 so its kinda anchored in this region
 and moreover US UK govt doesn't need help
 
outpowerhosting: if i were to use the forum.. I should feel like.. ok.. I'm going to post my problem in some forum in which India is just one of the countries...

 Kuldeep: why
 
outpowerhosting: I should feel confident that someone is going to listen and that there are people who understand the situation

 Kuldeep: can u not talk about a problem in US
 
outpowerhosting: not that I'm just going to post and hope just hope that an Indian sees it
 
Kuldeep: well i can
 why
 yaar share your information

 outpowerhosting: kuldeep.. the idea is there.. but everyone doesn't think like you and me..
 
Kuldeep: lets see what others have to say
 
outpowerhosting: we have generalize it to suit the millions
 
Kuldeep: i mean a problem is in India
 right
 people from India to dekhenge hi
 
outpowerhosting: yeah.. i know..
 but like i said..
 
Kuldeep: par bahar wale aa kar suggestions denge tabhi to kucch accha sochnege
to govt ke badle kucch aur hona chahiye tu bol raha hai
 
outpowerhosting: like i said.. i shouldn't feel like I'm just one in the world.. it would feel much better if I'm one in India... besides.. who's stopping people from outside posting something in a forum related to India
 what i meant is
 it should be region specific
 or what you do is
 have the main domain
 and then create sub domain
 like india.helpthegovt.com
 and then on your main page
 list the countries
 which will lead to a forum
 
Kuldeep: Faizal see my motto is to get information ...inside information that you don't know from Bangladesh
 China
 Pakistan
 right
 India
 I can't be there all the time
 but people are there
 and if they post something only then I'll know about it na
 and then only i can suggest something
 
outpowerhosting: yes... the reason the information is inside and not public is because only people from that region know it.. and they wouldn't bother telling it to someone else.. if you give them the comfort that they are telling it to people of their same region.. they will feel much more confident to open up..
 do you understand what I'm saying?
 so.. let it be global.. but create sub domains that are region specific
 
Kuldeep: So u are saying people from Pakistan won't talk about their govt with Indian people
 creating sub domains will be hell lot of a work
 
outpowerhosting: not everyone will if they think their enemy is going to read it
 i know.. no pain.. no gain
 
Kuldeep: i mean moderating and managing

outpowerhosting: well.. if there are lot of people then.. obviously you can part that job with others..
 but till then I don't think it should be an issue

Kuldeep: but as of now i don't have anyone that's why i was thinking of having it in one
 
outpowerhosting: are.. people will come only when you open the forum
 ok..
 
Kuldeep: I am the only person

 outpowerhosting: then do one thing
 open and Indian sub domain as of now
 and a world region
 as more an more dome
 split it up
 
Kuldeep: and the domain
 what should it be

outpowerhosting: hmmm....
 helpmeworld.com
 lol
 
Kuldeep: don't think about India only
 u there
 i am on Gtalk now
 outpowerhosting: helpmeworld.com
 
Kuldeep: naah
 outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: who is me here
 
outpowerhosting: you want govt in it?
 
Kuldeep: check letshelptheworld
 outpowerhosting: the one who wants help
 letshelptheworld.com is there

 Kuldeep: what do u think about it
 
outpowerhosting: a bit lengthy

 Kuldeep: han yehi main soch raha tha
 
outpowerhosting: remove lets
 
Kuldeep: willhelp
 check this
 
outpowerhosting: what willhelp.com?
 doesn't make sense yaar
 
Kuldeep: india.willhelp.com

 outpowerhosting: doesn't make sense.. but if you want.. I'll check
 
Kuldeep: india.helptheworld.com
 
outpowerhosting: hmmm..
 so helptheworld.com?
 
Kuldeep: what do you say
 now just because i am wasting your time don't say yes

 outpowerhosting: it's not available

 Kuldeep: is it parked
 
outpowerhosting: i guess so
 
Kuldeep: how do we go about that
 
outpowerhosting: you'll have to pay a heavy sum if you need it
 depends on what the owner asks you for
 
Kuldeep: how much
 K
 leave leave
 think of something else
 i've given u the idea
 if we can eliminate help or govt
 or whatever
 
outpowerhosting: you don't want 'me' in it?
 
Kuldeep: yar i don't want to help me only. i want to help others as well
 
outpowerhosting: k

Kuldeep: so its not about me its about US
 
outpowerhosting: would it be appropriate to think in the lines of solution center?
 something like world solution center wsc.com or something?

Kuldeep: hmm
 sounds good

 outpowerhosting: so? then?

Kuldeep: but do u think wsc would make a good impact

 outpowerhosting: nope
 
Kuldeep: got the answer
 
outpowerhosting: but if you advertise it without the domain name.. then it will help..

 Kuldeep: lets make a difference
 
outpowerhosting: like if you advertise it as world solution center insteand of wsc.com.. it will help
 how would you suggest a domain name for that?
 
Kuldeep: that will be a bit long
 www.makeadifference.com

outpowerhosting: already there
 
Kuldeep: helpworld is not there as well

outpowerhosting: k now?
 
Kuldeep: i am asking ? is it?
 
outpowerhosting: nope.. not available

Kuldeep: u create account for hosting
 i'll tell u the domain name later

outpowerhosting: better to do with domain..
 
Kuldeep: why
 
outpowerhosting: name server issue.. coz if i create the account now.. and then register the domain.. the name server change sometimes might affect the account.. and in rare cases, edit or recreate the account.. but it should work most of the time
 
Kuldeep: world's problem solution
 
outpowerhosting: naaa
 
Kuldeep: center
 center theek nahin hai
 something else

outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: some historic word
 saveworld
 
outpowerhosting: naa.. you're not saving anyone.. only helping
 
Kuldeep: worldhelp
 check that
 worldforhelp
 
outpowerhosting: nope.. smarter guys already got it
 
Kuldeep: igottahelp
 ineedhelp
 
outpowerhosting: so.. now it's become all about I ? hahahhaha
 
Kuldeep: weneedhelp
 just giving example
 i am not buying it
 ha ha ha
 
outpowerhosting: k.. just kidding
 we need help already taken
 
Kuldeep: accha
 helpus
 
outpowerhosting: nope
 taken
 
Kuldeep: F1world
 yar going in other direction warna idea accha tha
 
outpowerhosting: F1?
 
Kuldeep: F1=help
 
outpowerhosting: why change?
 hahahahhaha
 do you think everyone's gonna click with that?
 
Kuldeep: letschangeworlf
 
outpowerhosting: it didn't click for an IT admin.. then how come it will click for normal guys?
 
Kuldeep: hmm
 Edit world
 how is this
 
outpowerhosting: now you wannna become wolf? hahahhaha
 
Kuldeep: edit bole to change
 if change is not available
 
outpowerhosting: letschangeworld.com available
 
Kuldeep: the missing
 
outpowerhosting: yeah
 
Kuldeep: but then very lengthy
 
outpowerhosting: add d
 
Kuldeep: nope
 wonb't suit
 am i wasting your time
 
outpowerhosting: naa
 tell me
 
Kuldeep: you are with me na
 
outpowerhosting: yeah

 Kuldeep: synonyms of change
 
outpowerhosting: google :p
 addition , adjustment , advance , break , compression , contraction , conversion , correction , development , difference , distortion , diversification , diversity , enlargement , innovation , metamorphosis , modification , modulation , mutation , novelty , permutation , reconstruction , refinement , remodeling , reversal , revision , revolution , shift , surrogate , switch , tempering , transformation , transition , transmutation , turn , turnover , variance , variation , variety , vicissitude, enlargement
 hahahhahahahha
 
Kuldeep: revolutioners
 check this
 
outpowerhosting: revolutioners.com
 available
 
Kuldeep: agar hai to kar de
 haan kar de
 spelling check kar leoutpowerhosting: are you sure?
 
Kuldeep: are you ?
 
outpowerhosting: seems ok. but not sure if there is a thing in mind that we're going to change when we mean revolution
 coz we revolt against something in existence..
 
Kuldeep: hmmm
 ya so there is something that we want to change and revolt from that
 
outpowerhosting: k..
 
Kuldeep: or evolve
 i had thought of rangdebasanti
 par mila nahin
 for india only
 
outpowerhosting: rangdebasanti?
 what has that got to do with anything?

Kuldeep: are movie nahin dekhi tune
 
outpowerhosting: nope.
 
Kuldeep: kya
 rangdebasanti nahin dekhi
 
outpowerhosting: never got time :p
 
Kuldeep: accha
 phir kya kara
 english dekhi
 koi
 
outpowerhosting: didn't see any recent movies
 
Kuldeep: i saw cloverfield and jumper
 good quality cam rip

outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: http://india.revolutioners.com/
 kaisa lag raha hai
 
outpowerhosting: seems good
 
Kuldeep: ya http://india.letschangetheworld.com/
 
outpowerhosting: which one?
 
Kuldeep: are yar u seem to be in rush
 i am asking u
 
outpowerhosting: no
 letschangetheworld.com and http://india.letschangetheworld.com/ is not available
 
Kuldeep: maine bola hai k agar time nahin hai to main kal kara lunga yar
 not a problem
 
outpowerhosting: no.. I'm right here
 going no where
 
Kuldeep: are u home
 
outpowerhosting: s bolo that na.. leave pe hoon to ghar me hoon

Kuldeep: dekha mujhe pata hi tha k itna accha idea kaun chod dega
 
outpowerhosting: lol
 
Kuldeep: yeh bhi parked hai yar

outpowerhosting: i guess

Kuldeep: haan chal phir 1 hi option bacha revolutioners.com ya yeh theek nahin hai
 
outpowerhosting: are you sure? lock karun?
 
Kuldeep: world laga le uske pehle worldrevolution.com
 
outpowerhosting: lemme check
 
Kuldeep: hai shayad
 
outpowerhosting: nope taken
 
Kuldeep: it says available
 
outpowerhosting: where?
 
Kuldeep: domainsearch.com
 
outpowerhosting: no yaar
 I'll check again.. check your spelling
 
Kuldeep: let me check somewhere else
 
outpowerhosting: nope

Kuldeep: haan
 nahin hai
 govt ko beech main lana is not good waise
 people will think k kucch nahin ho sakta
 ha na
 
outpowerhosting: yeah
 
Kuldeep: accha chal revolutioners.com
 register kar de
 agar kuccch aur idea aayega to aur kara lenge
 theek hai
 
outpowerhosting: okie
 
Kuldeep: now i am going out for sutta and shave
 
outpowerhosting: k.. so <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/">revolutioners.com</a>?
 
Kuldeep: i'll come back in 30 mins or so
 
outpowerhosting: check spelling
 
Kuldeep: haan bhai theek hai
 
outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: tujhe mujhse jyada hi pata hoga
 
outpowerhosting: lol
 
Kuldeep: registrar ko kya information dega
 
Kuldeep: fake ki real
 
outpowerhosting: jo tumne mujhe diya that.. .but three is privacy protection.. your whois info will be hidden
 
Kuldeep: good
 accha how is this
 letseditworld

 outpowerhosting: edit?
 
Kuldeep: haan bole to change
 ;)
 
outpowerhosting: na.. it sounds geeky.. not for average person
 
Kuldeep: chal see ya then
 be online
 
outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: stick with revolutioners

 outpowerhosting: k

Kuldeep: .com
 ok
 
outpowerhosting: yeah.. doing now
 
Kuldeep: be online
 
outpowerhosting: will be
 
Kuldeep: i'll be back in 30 mins
 bye
 
outpowerhosting: k
 bye

 Kuldeep: if u r going offline then mail the details to me
 ok
 outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: bye
 any contact no u have
 
outpowerhosting: only personal no. as of now.. will get another one within a week. ... will give then
 
Kuldeep: i thought by now you'd give me ur personal no as well.
 anyways
 thanks
 bye
 
<a href="http://outpowerhosting.com/">outpowerhosting</a>: bye</pre>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
