<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>history &#8211; rLOVEutioners</title>
	<atom:link href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tag/history/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/</link>
	<description>revoution for evolution</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 13:34:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How India lost its freedom after Independence</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/do-we-need-bhagat-singh-and-rajguru-like-patriots-to-free-our-country-again-from-our-old-conservative-politicians/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/do-we-need-bhagat-singh-and-rajguru-like-patriots-to-free-our-country-again-from-our-old-conservative-politicians/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 12:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=40</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What do you think. I know I am talking the hard way here. But the situation is like that it will not get resolved with Mahatma Gandhi. We need people like Bhagat Singh and Rajguru to take initiatives and save us from our old conservative politicians. The situation is getting worse day by day. The &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/do-we-need-bhagat-singh-and-rajguru-like-patriots-to-free-our-country-again-from-our-old-conservative-politicians/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">How India lost its freedom after Independence</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What do you think. I know I am talking the hard way here. But the situation is like that it will not get resolved with Mahatma Gandhi. We need people like Bhagat Singh and Rajguru to take initiatives and save us from our old conservative politicians.</p>
<p>The situation is getting worse day by day. The crime is taking its toll. No political party seems to care about the citizens of India. Everybody is playing the blame game.</p>
<p>I believe India would have gone miles ahead if we had saved the leaders like Rajiv Gandhi. We need young blood to lead India, not 70 year old man who can barely walk on his feet. We need to come out of our 500 years old mentality that only old men are experienced. We are living in 21st century where what we are learning today, none of our politicians would have even dreamt of doing. Forget about learning, 80% of our politicians would not be graduate even.</p>
<p>We need educated young people who understands the dynamics of today. We don’t need people who are 70 years old and does not even know where to invest and services to provide to their citizens.</p>
<p>I don’t want to elaborate on this. I think you have understood what I am trying to say.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/do-we-need-bhagat-singh-and-rajguru-like-patriots-to-free-our-country-again-from-our-old-conservative-politicians/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biggest Political Mistake in Indian History</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 12:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=38</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It all happened just before the Indian Independence Day and it happened so fast that no body could even think the aftermaths of the event would be so disastrous that the whole world would laugh at a nation which was divided into 2 by some lazy people who never thought that things could be worked &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Biggest Political Mistake in Indian History</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It all happened just before the Indian Independence Day and it happened so fast that no body could even think the aftermaths of the event would be so disastrous that the whole world would laugh at a nation which was divided into 2 by some lazy people who never thought that things could be worked out. Yes I am talking about the Partition of India and Pakistan.</p>
<p><span id="more-1299"></span>Today is the Independence Day and I want to give you a reason to think. I have a question for you guys.</p>
<blockquote><p>Do you think Jawahar Lal Nehru did the right thing by agreeing to Muhammad Ali Jinnah ?</p></blockquote>
<p>Before you come to any conclusions, I just want to let you know that I am just asking for your opinion. I have put across my thoughts, now I need to know what you think. Pt. Jawahar Lal Nehru when agreed to Muhammad Ali Jinnah would have thought that now India would live happily ever after. But I guess they were wrong, I mean they have been wrong all throughout. Pakistan has gone so far sometimes after the division that its unbearable, but still we Indians believe in Peace. We still believe in talks with our neighbor countries. We still believe that <strong>“Kutte ki poonch Seedhi ho jayegi”.</strong> We still think that now we will live without any fear since our Prime Minister is a bit aggressive now. What the hell ?</p>
<p>My only point is that its our politicians who have been giving us pain all through out . Had Jawahar Lal Nehru not agreed to Muhammad, we would have had a single country spanning a long Kashmir having the most amazing tourist place ever. Imagine Afridi and Sehwag opening for India. No power would have stopped that India to win against any country. What a scene would that be. Imagine the biggest tourist place in the world for its beautiful mountains, a place known to be heaven on earth. We could have been so advanced today that the whole world would have envied us.</p>
<p>But let’s face the reality. Since both the countries are not in good terms and are always fighting, we spend over billions on getting the most latest and deadliest weapons from Israel and Russia. Just imagine 3-4% of GDP of India and Pakistan going into preparing for battle against each other. Imagine this money spent for good cause, for betterment of both countries. None of the countries people have proper food to eat, but we want to fight. The whole world looks at us as a country of poor, which some time ago used to be the “<strong>Golden Bird</strong>.” Had we spent those billions for improving our infrastructure then what a country India would have been. People would have lead a life which they deserve rather than leading their lives in fear of getting blasted in some suicide bombing.</p>
<p>I really feel that our life was fcuked on that day when India and Pakistan parted their ways. Just wait for some time, its quite possible that India will get partitioned further because we have the same Congress in center which made all this possible. Rumors are that China is thinking of creating a mess in India and trying to divide India into several parts.</p>
<p>What do you say ?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
