<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Social &#8211; rLOVEutioners</title>
	<atom:link href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/category/social/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/</link>
	<description>revoution for evolution</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 14:49:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Bhagat Singh</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/bhagat-singh/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 07:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=427</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[“Leave sentimentalism aside. Be prepared to face the facts. Revolution is a very difficult task. It is beyond the power of any man to make a revolution. Neither can it be brought about on any appointed date. It is brought about by special environments, social and economic. The function of an organized party is to &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/bhagat-singh/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Bhagat Singh</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre id="tw-target-text" class="tw-data-text tw-ta tw-text-small" dir="ltr" data-placeholder="Translation" data-fulltext=""><span lang="hi">
“Leave sentimentalism aside. Be prepared to face the facts. Revolution is a very difficult task. It is beyond the power of any man to make a revolution. Neither can it be brought about on any appointed date. It is brought about by special environments, social and economic. The function of an organized party is to utilize such an opportunity offered by these circumstances. [To] prepare the masses and organize the forces for the revolution is a very difficult task. And that requires a very great sacrifice on the part of the revolutionary workers.”

<strong>Bhagat Singh</strong> in a letter “To the young political workers”, 2 February 1931

</span></pre>
<pre id="tw-target-text" class="tw-data-text tw-ta tw-text-small" dir="ltr" data-placeholder="Translation" data-fulltext=""><span lang="hi">
भावुक होना छोड़ दें।
और सच का सामना करने के लिए तैयार हो जाऍ।
क्रांति करना एक असाधारण कार्य है।
और क्रांति का उद्घोष करना किसी एक व्यक्ति विशेष की शक्ति से परे है।
और न ही इसे किसी एक सुनिश्चित समय पर लाया जा सकता है।
क्रांति विशेषतः, अनुकूल सामाजिक और आर्थिक परिस्थितियों द्वारा लाई जाती है।
एक सुव्यवस्थित संगठन का कर्तव्य इन परिस्थितियों द्वारा उत्पन्न किए जाने वाले अवसरोॅ का सदुपयोग करना है।
[जनता को] क्रांति के लिये तैयार करना और क्रांतिकारी ताकतोॅ को सॅगठित करना एक बहुत ही मुश्किल काम है।
और इसके लिए क्रांतिकारीयोॅ को एक महान त्याग करने की आवश्यकता है।

<strong>भगत सिॅह</strong> का २ फरवरी १९३१ को "युवा राजनैतिक कार्यकर्ताओॅ " के लिये लिखा पत्र 

</span></pre>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Issues India needs to sort out in next 10 years to really be a SuperPower</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 12:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=23&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=23</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are many things that Indian Government needs to fix but these are some of them which I feel will make or break our country’s future in the coming years. Inflation: With the most of India’s vast population living close to or below the poverty line, inflation acts as a ‘Poor Man’s Tax’. This effect &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Issues India needs to sort out in next 10 years to really be a SuperPower</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are many things that Indian Government needs to fix but these are some of them which I feel will make or break our country’s future in the coming years.</p>
<p><strong>Inflation</strong>: With the most of India’s vast population living close to or below the poverty line, inflation acts as a ‘Poor Man’s Tax’. This effect is amplified when food prices rise, since food represents more than half of the expenditure of this group.</p>
<p><strong>Terrorism</strong> &#8211; I know it should have been on the top of the list however I chose it to be on the 2nd place because people are any which ways dying due to not being able to feed themselves because of the rise in price of the consumable commodities.We spend a huge amount of money on defense but where is the defense. We have been preparing for WW III for I don’t know how long. And in that process we have forgotten to spend money in the right direction.</p>
<p><strong>Unemployment</strong> – Not a big deal in the rural areas but a huge concern for the people living in the urban areas. It seems to have deteriorated in the past 1 year but we need to go miles from here. We are no where near what a developed country should be. Unemployment rate as of now is around 10%</p>
<p><strong>Infrastructure</strong> – We need around 100 CWG games organized in our country for the infrastructure to improve. After writing the last sentence, I pondered over it for a couple of seconds and this funny thought occurred to me that we would have 100 more corrupt events and millions of rupees will go into our politicians’ pockets again.</p>
<p><strong>Indo-Pak Relation</strong>: To be absolutely frank, we have to take a stand if we really want to solve this problem. It may not be a problem for the neighboring country but it is affecting us as a country, a lot. We have enough army to defeat a country like Pakistan. At the least give the opponent something to think about before they try or think about doing something which brings disgrace to our country. We keep sitting idle and wait for their response all the time after someone takes responsibility to attack India.</p>
<p><strong>Indian Constitution</strong>: I feel the root of all the problems is our constitution. Written over 60 years ago. Things are bound to change. We are still living in the same 60 year old world. We were a developing country then and are still a developing country. There hasn&#8217;t been any change, moreover our politicians and constitution has brought nothing but misery to our country.</p>
<p><strong>Uneducated Politicians</strong>: We are living in a country where an uneducated/illiterate (politically) person can enter the world of politics. We are living in a state of spiritual disbelief of which our politicians are taking undue advantage. We need to get out of this situation, and pretty fast. But the concern is who will bell the cat. These people are strong and powerful because of their unlawful deeds and its hard to reverse the effects for good.</p>
<p><strong>Division of States</strong>: If we can divide the states then it’s imminent that we would have around 30 countries within India in the next 10 years. Dividing states further was the first weakness shown by a weak leader of our country. People will demand unethical things, it does not mean you mess up with the idea of peace and forget what you are supposed to do.</p>
<p><strong>Communal Riots</strong>: We are the world’s second largest standing army in the world. It definitely means something. But a bunch of people take over a state. Terrorize it. I am not convinced with the fact that a million armed forces can’t take down these Naxalites or any other Maoist groups. We declared them as terrorist groups but we can’t fight them. Over 30% of Indian states are affected by these groups in one way or the other.</p>
<p><strong>Education</strong>: 40% of world’s illiterate population is from India. Nothing much to say about this one.</p>
<p>These are my thoughts. There are so many good things to point out. And the web is flooded with information like that but till the time we don’t highlight the bad it won’t turn into good. That’s my theory. We can’t make something right till the time we don’t believe that there is something wrong.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Diwali &#8211; Plan Baksheesh</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/plan-baksheesh/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/plan-baksheesh/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 09:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=166</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Around Diwali, the usual constant stream of “visitors” will show up. The crew of building watchmen (half a dozen of whom you’ve never seen before), the janitor, the postman, the maid, and probably some random strangers chancing their luck – they will all knock on your door looking for Diwali “Baksheesh.” Baksheesh is a term &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/plan-baksheesh/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">This Diwali &#8211; Plan Baksheesh</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Around Diwali, the usual constant stream of “visitors” will show up. The crew of building watchmen (half a dozen of whom you’ve never seen before), the janitor, the postman, the maid, and probably some random strangers chancing their luck – they will all knock on your door looking for Diwali “Baksheesh.” <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Baksheesh">Baksheesh</a> is a term that loosely refers to either a tip or, interestingly, a bribe.</p>
<p>For people, the popularity of tipping has always been something of a mystery. Take restaurant tipping as a typical example. Since the tip is usually given at the end of the meal, what good purpose does it serve? Since the service has already been provided, it can’t by definition affect the quality of the service you received? It would make sense maybe for a repeat customer on the basis that a kind tip would lead to the probability of better service next time.</p>
<p>But <a href="http://www.ft.com/intl/cms/s/0/be390fbe-a893-11d9-87a9-00000e2511c8.html#axzz1bhFznael">researchers</a> have something else to say. As per the researchers, tipping is equally likely to yield same service whether a customer plans to return or not. The consensus seems to be that tipping is best understood as a social norm, a form of charitable giving tied to the provision of a service.</p>
<p><span id="more-3341"></span>But back to the folks knocking on your door.  Should you be giving them? Why do they expect a tip at Diwali, when you tend to tip them anyway throughout the year, such as when the watchman helps bring up a heavy parcel, or maid comes thrice a day on your request?</p>
<p>During Diwali, Its believed and wise to make necessary pay-outs to avoid sudden disruption of services. So try the formula desribed below and let me know what difference did it make:</p>
<ol>
<li> Begin with a firm budget. Make sure you have in mind about how much to spend on Baksheesh during the festive season well in advance.</li>
<li>Prepare a list of service-providers in descending order of importance. Like Milkman, Sweeper, Maid, Newspaper Wallah, Watchman etc.</li>
<li>Divide the service providers into 2 different lists. First, those who need to be motivated and second, those who need recognition.</li>
<li>Now divide each list further into 3 parts, depending the importance of work they do for you and your family. The persons in the <strong>first list</strong> are the most important service providers like the maid, watchman and liftman. If anyone of them is disappointed, it results in immediate fall-out action. The maid will come late, much after your wife or mom has completed half the housework. The watchman will permit hawkers to knock at our door in the afternoons and spoil your siesta. And the liftman will declare that the lift is under repair and ensure that you climb six floors. They, therefore, should be given top most priority.</li>
<li>In the <strong>second list</strong> houses service providers that are not so important but are required alm0st everyday like, the milkman, the washerwoman and the sweeper. Since the milkman and washerwoman are paid on a daily basis, they recognise that we may have some cash-flow problems. They seem satisfied with smaller amounts. The sweeper, however, needs to be handled with care. He has the power to skip a few days’ garbage collection and cause serious nasal disorder.</li>
<li>The<strong> third list</strong> consists of the people that are not so important like, telephone, post and telegraph community. This list does not evoke too much concern. The importance of the telephone lineman has taken a huge dip. A faulty line does not bother people any more in these days of the mobile phone except you are the broadband subscriber. The post and telegraph group too does not attract too much money. The e-mail has made letter-writing redundant. Therefore you may want to keep service providers alike in this list.</li>
</ol>
<p>A little off topic, there’s a certain irony in being expected to offer a Diwali Baksheesh to someone like the postman who is a government employee and is supposed to do his job without expecting or receiving a tip. Perhaps the double meaning of Baksheesh is fitting here since people have become used to paying bribes for services that they’re entitled to.</p>
<p>I have always remained a keen observer of these Diwali pay-outs over the last so many years and am fascinated by the methods employed by the beneficiaries to gain more handsome pay-outs. Each one carries a list of neighbourhood donors. We know our neighbours well enough to realise that the figures are grossly exaggerated. This is an old technique called <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peer_pressure">Peer Pressure</a>.</p>
<p>I am also intrigued by the fact that the beneficiaries never come in a bunch. They stagger their time of arrival through careful networking, without doubt. All said, the Diwali baksheesh — both the handing and receiving of it — is an interesting exercise in human management.</p>
<p>Thanks for reading. Happy Diwali to you and your familiy in advance.</p>
<p>If you like the post then take 2 minutes and share it with your friends and family. Also do let me know via comments if it helped you or not?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/plan-baksheesh/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over 365 Cool, Innovative and Best Profile Picture Ideas – Male Only</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/best-facebook-linkedin-orkut-myspace-profile-pics-photos-images-ideas/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/best-facebook-linkedin-orkut-myspace-profile-pics-photos-images-ideas/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 13:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=47</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While I was hunting for suitable theme for Revolutioners, I stumbled upon a theme website. The theme was not that good but the content on that site made me post this article. It had lot of images of a single person. I thought it would be a good idea to have it as a single &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/best-facebook-linkedin-orkut-myspace-profile-pics-photos-images-ideas/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Over 365 Cool, Innovative and Best Profile Picture Ideas – Male Only</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While I was hunting for suitable theme for Revolutioners, I stumbled upon a theme website. The theme was not that good but the content on that site made me post this article. It had lot of images of a single person. I thought it would be a good idea to have it as a single point to refer in case anyone is looking for ideas for his/her next Facebook or any other Social Media profile picture. I saved the whole site as Image and posting it here on my blog. I really liked the ideas of the pictures shown on the blog. If you need inspiration for clicking your own picture for your social website’s profile then look nowhere else. The image is really long and huge in size. So be careful.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323131000im_/http://img24.imageshack.us/img24/5550/facebookprofilepicturei.jpg" alt="Social Networking Profile Picture Idea" width="600"></p>
<p><a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323131000/http://img24.imageshack.us/img24/5550/facebookprofilepicturei.jpg">Link to full size image</a></p>


<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/best-facebook-linkedin-orkut-myspace-profile-pics-photos-images-ideas/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why India need fat pipes?</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-india-need-fat-pipes/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-india-need-fat-pipes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2011 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=45</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you follow tech news you might have heard of Netflix and it’s recent success after adopting the streaming model. Their website says “For only $7.99 a month, you get unlimited movies &#38; TV episodes instantly over the Internet to your TV or computer. There are no commercials, and you can pause, rewind, fast forward &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-india-need-fat-pipes/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Why India need fat pipes?</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you follow tech news you might have heard of <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323133002/http://netflix.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Netflix</a> and it’s recent success after adopting the streaming model. Their website says “For only <strong>$7.99 a month</strong>, you get unlimited movies &amp; TV episodes instantly over the Internet to your TV or computer. There are no commercials, and you can pause, rewind, fast forward or re-watch as often as you like. It’s really that easy!”</p>
<p>Isn’t this great, for just <strong>Rs.400 a month</strong>, Netflix gives Video on demand on a lot of devices (PC,macs, mobile devices, gaming consoles etc.) with recommendations, resuming playback of movies/T.V shows where you left them off and a lot more. So if you’re watching a movie late in the night and you get too sleepy, you can shut off your movie and resume it the next day on your way to work on your phone.  We end up paying more for Tata sky which doesn’t even provide video on demand or multiple device viewing.</p>
<p>This model has helped Netflix become a major success in the US and Canada with Apple choosing to bundle a Netflix app on their Apple TV as well. This gets us wondering, why isn’t there a service similar to Netflix in India?</p>
<p>Although there have been a few companies which have tried to imitate the earlier Netflix model, i.e DVD rentals none of them have become hugely popular nor have they offered attractive policies like no late fees, no due dates etc. There was a <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323133002/http://gigaom.com/2006/09/22/seventymm-indias-netflix/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">post</a> on gigaOM way back in 2006 pegging seventymm as India’s Netflix, obviously the service hasn’t caught on.<br />
The posts points out a major hurdle for video rental services like these, piracy. With every railway station selling CDs of the latest movies on as soon as their release dates for as cheap as <strong>Rs.50 ($1)</strong>, it becomes a bit difficult for the survival of this model, also with increasing penetration of the not-so-fast broadband in India, you see people downloading<strong> 700mb DVD</strong>rips from piratebay even if it takes them 24 hours.</p>
<p>So Indian players haven’t even succeeded in coming on par with the Netflix of the earlier years, let alone the current streaming based Netflix. The rental service not catching up is because these players haven’t been able to come up with an effective strategy, but the non existent streaming based service is majorly because of the pathetic internet service in India.</p>
<p>The Netflix page specifies minimum connection requirements for it to work fine “Watching instantly works with all different levels of broadband, however, we recommend a minimum speed of <strong>500kpbs (0.5MB)</strong>.” In average Indian homes unfortunately this sort of connectivity is absent. Speeds like these if offered by ISPs cost a lot. So right now if an Indian Netflix would startup it would remain restricted to the offices of Indian people where stuff like this isn’t permitted. Also the mobile market isn’t ready yet for on the move media viewing, the 3G tariffs are expensive, carriers aren’t ready yet to carry huge amounts of data on their network and a huge part of Indians still don’t have smart phones.</p>
<p>This coupled with the fact that many Indians don’t want to pay for something digital. For example: They won’t hesitate much to buy pirated CDs and DVDs but they have a problem buying a <strong>$.99</strong> game from the AppStore. Fortunately this mindset is changing with the increasing penetration of Internet banking, online shopping etc. A lot of channels like NDTV, CNN, IBN, etc and events like the IPL are providing live streams online. So one can just hope for a Netflix like service to come up in India in the next five years. If they have enough partnerships for providing content then DTH services are doomed!</p>
<p>It was reported that Netflix’s competitor Google has also  launched a pay-per-view online service, in order to gain more traffic to their new service.</p>
<p><a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323133002/http://www.watblog.com/2011/04/25/why-isnt-an-online-streaming-solution-not-possible-in-india-yet/">Source</a>: I feel that we desperately need faster broadband connection for sure. It will solve a lot of problems. I feel piracy can somehow be reduced by providing faster broadband in homes and mobile phones. I would definitely want to subscribe for a 24×7 movie available for 400 Rs/per month. And save money on my broadband and electricity bill.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-india-need-fat-pipes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How India lost its freedom after Independence</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/do-we-need-bhagat-singh-and-rajguru-like-patriots-to-free-our-country-again-from-our-old-conservative-politicians/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/do-we-need-bhagat-singh-and-rajguru-like-patriots-to-free-our-country-again-from-our-old-conservative-politicians/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 12:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=40</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What do you think. I know I am talking the hard way here. But the situation is like that it will not get resolved with Mahatma Gandhi. We need people like Bhagat Singh and Rajguru to take initiatives and save us from our old conservative politicians. The situation is getting worse day by day. The &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/do-we-need-bhagat-singh-and-rajguru-like-patriots-to-free-our-country-again-from-our-old-conservative-politicians/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">How India lost its freedom after Independence</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What do you think. I know I am talking the hard way here. But the situation is like that it will not get resolved with Mahatma Gandhi. We need people like Bhagat Singh and Rajguru to take initiatives and save us from our old conservative politicians.</p>
<p>The situation is getting worse day by day. The crime is taking its toll. No political party seems to care about the citizens of India. Everybody is playing the blame game.</p>
<p>I believe India would have gone miles ahead if we had saved the leaders like Rajiv Gandhi. We need young blood to lead India, not 70 year old man who can barely walk on his feet. We need to come out of our 500 years old mentality that only old men are experienced. We are living in 21st century where what we are learning today, none of our politicians would have even dreamt of doing. Forget about learning, 80% of our politicians would not be graduate even.</p>
<p>We need educated young people who understands the dynamics of today. We don’t need people who are 70 years old and does not even know where to invest and services to provide to their citizens.</p>
<p>I don’t want to elaborate on this. I think you have understood what I am trying to say.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/do-we-need-bhagat-singh-and-rajguru-like-patriots-to-free-our-country-again-from-our-old-conservative-politicians/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biggest Political Mistake in Indian History</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 12:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=38</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It all happened just before the Indian Independence Day and it happened so fast that no body could even think the aftermaths of the event would be so disastrous that the whole world would laugh at a nation which was divided into 2 by some lazy people who never thought that things could be worked &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Biggest Political Mistake in Indian History</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It all happened just before the Indian Independence Day and it happened so fast that no body could even think the aftermaths of the event would be so disastrous that the whole world would laugh at a nation which was divided into 2 by some lazy people who never thought that things could be worked out. Yes I am talking about the Partition of India and Pakistan.</p>
<p><span id="more-1299"></span>Today is the Independence Day and I want to give you a reason to think. I have a question for you guys.</p>
<blockquote><p>Do you think Jawahar Lal Nehru did the right thing by agreeing to Muhammad Ali Jinnah ?</p></blockquote>
<p>Before you come to any conclusions, I just want to let you know that I am just asking for your opinion. I have put across my thoughts, now I need to know what you think. Pt. Jawahar Lal Nehru when agreed to Muhammad Ali Jinnah would have thought that now India would live happily ever after. But I guess they were wrong, I mean they have been wrong all throughout. Pakistan has gone so far sometimes after the division that its unbearable, but still we Indians believe in Peace. We still believe in talks with our neighbor countries. We still believe that <strong>“Kutte ki poonch Seedhi ho jayegi”.</strong> We still think that now we will live without any fear since our Prime Minister is a bit aggressive now. What the hell ?</p>
<p>My only point is that its our politicians who have been giving us pain all through out . Had Jawahar Lal Nehru not agreed to Muhammad, we would have had a single country spanning a long Kashmir having the most amazing tourist place ever. Imagine Afridi and Sehwag opening for India. No power would have stopped that India to win against any country. What a scene would that be. Imagine the biggest tourist place in the world for its beautiful mountains, a place known to be heaven on earth. We could have been so advanced today that the whole world would have envied us.</p>
<p>But let’s face the reality. Since both the countries are not in good terms and are always fighting, we spend over billions on getting the most latest and deadliest weapons from Israel and Russia. Just imagine 3-4% of GDP of India and Pakistan going into preparing for battle against each other. Imagine this money spent for good cause, for betterment of both countries. None of the countries people have proper food to eat, but we want to fight. The whole world looks at us as a country of poor, which some time ago used to be the “<strong>Golden Bird</strong>.” Had we spent those billions for improving our infrastructure then what a country India would have been. People would have lead a life which they deserve rather than leading their lives in fear of getting blasted in some suicide bombing.</p>
<p>I really feel that our life was fcuked on that day when India and Pakistan parted their ways. Just wait for some time, its quite possible that India will get partitioned further because we have the same Congress in center which made all this possible. Rumors are that China is thinking of creating a mess in India and trying to divide India into several parts.</p>
<p>What do you say ?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I see a Policeman on motorbike without a Helmet, I stop him and hand him over a ticket</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 13:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=43</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[How cool will that be ? I mean I was just wondering for quite some time now that how nice it would be if we could really take control of our law enforcement. Imagine while roaming on the road you see someone breaking the law and you take out your camera, take a picture while &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">I see a Policeman on motorbike without a Helmet, I stop him and hand him over a ticket</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How cool will that be ? I mean I was just wondering for quite some time now that how nice it would be if we could really take control of our law enforcement. Imagine while roaming on the road you see someone breaking the law and you take out your camera, take a picture while he is breaking the traffic rules. Catch hold of him. Show him the picture and hand over the ticket to him. I mean imagine the force we would have on roads and people will think twice before doing anything wrong.</p>
<p>People may use the power for wrong doing but I think we can start with some intelligent and responsible people like Bus Conductor, Shopkeepers who are sitting on a road watching it all the time. A Pan wallah on the Traffic Signal.</p>
<p>I am thinking of creating another website where I urge people to submit such pictures where people are captured while breaking the law. And our law enforcement team has to just identify the person and fine him/her.</p>
<p>Think about it. Bye !</p>
<p>Let me know your thoughts by posting your comments.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Does Wikipedia really need money?</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-does-wikipedia-need-money/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-does-wikipedia-need-money/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 18:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=70</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I guess I am not the only one who feels the same way. I was just going through the Wikipedia Financial today on their page. What I saw there made me look into this matter in much greater detail. Wikimedia spent almost $3500, 000 in recruiting and wages in the financial year 2009-2010. And it &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-does-wikipedia-need-money/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Does Wikipedia really need money?</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I guess I am not the only one who feels the same way. I was just going through the Wikipedia Financial today on <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323132239/http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/foundation/d/dd/2010-11_Wikimedia_Foundation_Annual_Plan_FINAL_FOR_WEBSITE.pdf">their page</a>. What I saw there made me look into this matter in much greater detail. Wikimedia spent almost $3500, 000 in recruiting and wages in the financial year 2009-2010. And it grew to almost $6000, 000 in the financial year 2010-2011. I was just wondering isn’t that too much for <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323132239/http://strategy.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Foundation_employees.png">50 employees of Wikimedia</a>. I am now confused as in what is actually a non-profit organization. I mean apart from running your websites do you also need money to run the show? Posting a conversation excerpt that I found in a forum.</p>
<p><img src="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323132239im_/http://img220.imageshack.us/img220/6794/wikipediax.jpg" alt="" width="600" /></p>
<blockquote><p>This is why I have lost faith in humanity, because too many people believe what is told to them and would rather believe in the “make me feel safe, secure, and okay” state of mind rather than face reality. It is a reality that non-profit and profit organizations use fraud to gain extra bucks. This is not conspiracy theories as it is even reported in mainstream media. You would have to be either very naive or not informed of what is going on in the world not to realize this.</p>
<p>Look at the last decade during the many world disasters, the mainstream news media always reported on scams/misuse of funds/missing funds for donations drives for:</p>
<ul>
<li>9/11 Victim families</li>
<li>Tsunami relief 2004</li>
<li>Haiti earthquake relief and many others.</li>
</ul>
<p>Just watch/read the news the next time another major disaster happens and donation drives start up, and you will see it shows up. Now, having said all this, I never said that no one should not donate to Wikipedia. I consider Wikipeidia one of the most important acomplishements of human effort for this decade and maybe even farther back because its primary cause is to spread information, something I believe strongly in.</p>
<p>And that is exactly why I mention that donation drives are not 100% innocent just because they have the “non-profit” tag on them. Those that still refuse to believe this reality attempt to counter with “but they report what they use the money for!” And then further counter by saying you have no evidence in return to go against it.</p>
<p>However evidence does exist in the form of history of scams/fraud in past donation drives for various causes. Also, the excuse of saying they report use is very naive as it *assumes* that those reporting are not involved or prone to fraud or are 100% honest. Even in the face of history proving that people can’t be trusted, which is way laws, courts, and oversight organizations exist (which I will also add are also not immune to being corrupt [as proven by history]).</p>
<p>Beyond failing to observe or forgetting history, I believe most people don’t realize this because they have never been in a “controller” position without oversight, in which human bias and nature is unchecked. This is why in science, double-blind experiments are use to remove bias. However, in the controller position without oversight, this is not removed. If you study literature, this topic (i.e. Lord of the Flies) has been covered many times throughout history as well, even up until now and in films.</p>
<p>Again, I just want to say I support Wikipedia because I so strongly believe in the spreading of information, and by that believe I attempt to spread a little, perhaps unpleasant piece of information as well. Which instead of being pushed under the plate should be swallowed whole, even if it tastes bad and unsettles your bowels. Even still you should make it part of you, move on, and seek out more information.</p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-does-wikipedia-need-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>India China comparison – An eye opener</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/india-china-economic-agricultural-industrial-education-comparison-world-bank/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/india-china-economic-agricultural-industrial-education-comparison-world-bank/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 18:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=83</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Below is a really nice comparison of India and China. Where we stand in terms of population, income, industry and many other. China started their family planning policy in 1970, India in 1952 In 2001 our birth rate was nearly 3 times more than China. 27 births per 1000 as against 8.8 for China! India &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/india-china-economic-agricultural-industrial-education-comparison-world-bank/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">India China comparison – An eye opener</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Below is a really nice comparison of India and China. Where we stand in terms of population, income, industry and many other.</p>
<p><strong>China started their family planning policy in 1970, India in 1952</strong></p>
<p>In 2001 our birth rate was nearly 3 times more than China. 27 births per 1000 as against 8.8 for China! India is adding 18 million people per year, against 9 million per year in China. Total addition to population is a function of total births minus total deaths.</p>
<p><strong>India’s per capita earning is US$440 per year against US$990 per year in China</strong></p>
<p>As per the World Bank, the poverty line definition is US$1 per person per day or US$365/person/year, for underdeveloped countries like India, China etc. As per the official data from both governments, China has 3% population below the poverty line, compared to India’s 26 to 29%! Only better governance can help.</p>
<p><strong>China attracts 87 million tourists per year (this is expected to reach 90 million in 2002) against 2.5 million per year to India.</strong></p>
<p>The international Tourism Industry is [7 times the size of I.T. or software] about, US$3700 billion per year. India, in spite of its old history and 21 cultures and languages, seems to have ‘missed the bus’, in Tourism. Tourism is a very big employment generator. It is estimated that every one tourist generates 2 to 4 jobs. Tourism promotes International trade and understanding.<br />
<strong>How will we provide additional 10 million jobs per year?</strong></p>
<p>The Public Sector and State/Central Government, which is already overstaffed, has a total of 18.7 million employees, therefore offers very little scope for new employment. We have to look outside the government for new employment. The unorganized sector and the SME’s (SSI is not SME) offer the maximum scope for employment, like in all other countries of the world, including China. SME’s account for nearly 75% of employment and 80% of trainees!</p>
<p><strong>The Government can only facilitate jobs; they cannot provide jobs for the 300 million partly or fully unemployed in India!</strong></p>
<p>At 10 million jobs per year it will take us 30 years to remove unemployment, at 5 million jobs for year it will take us 60 years! The present Indian ‘mind set’ will require rethinking and reorganization of the existing perceptions about Public Sector enterprises, and the actual role they are supposed to play! Only efficient organizations can deliver results and growth. Only better governance and efficient administration can deliver results!</p>
<p><strong>In Foreign Direct investment, FDI, China + Hong Kong received US$106 billion last year [US$70billion from NRC&#8217;s] vs US$3.6 billion [US$0.2b from NRI&#8217;s] for India! Only better Governance can attract FDI and Tourists. In exports, China is nearly +700% of India</strong></p>
<p>Taking the exports of Hong Kong + Macau into account, China’s exports would be +1000% of India! China’s GDP is 50% in manufacturing or $ 650 billion per year. India’s GDP is 25% in manufacturing or $110 billion per year. China’s manufacturing base is nearly 6 times of India’s.</p>
<p><span id="more-2946"></span><br />
<strong>In agriculture our yields per acre, are well below the international norms.</strong></p>
<p>India could be a giant exporter of food, only if we could put our ‘house in order’ to near world class standards! China with lesser cultivable land, produces double the food grains, at 415 million tons per year compared with India’s 208 million tons per year. God has been very kind to India with a lot of sunshine, rain, rivers, lakes, coastline and good hard working citizens.<br />
The governance of hamlets, villages, cities, districts, Government and Semi-Government agencies, as facilitators, have not done enough to show the results that India is able or capable of achieving. India would definitely rate as the No.1 country in the world, for Potential vs Performance!<br />
Indians score high marks on performance, outside India! This is because the Governance is better outside. In countries where the Governance &amp; Administration is poor, the performance of its citizens is also low!</p>
<p><strong>In Education, 99.1% of Chinese children attend school for 9 years, this ensures a high level of literacy. In India, literacy is 50 to 60%</strong></p>
<p>While IIT’s, IIM’s are important, the country’s real growth will come because of primary and secondary education and vocational and educational training in all districts of the country. India can rise and shine in exports, agriculture, literacy and other areas with better governance.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/india-china-economic-agricultural-industrial-education-comparison-world-bank/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
