<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>govt &#8211; rLOVEutioners</title>
	<atom:link href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tag/govt/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/</link>
	<description>revoution for evolution</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 13:55:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>मैॅ तो बस बोलता हूॅ</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/main-to-bas-bolta-hoon/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/main-to-bas-bolta-hoon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 05:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/?p=526</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[लिखने का शौक तो नहीॅपर शब्दोॅ मेॅ रस घोलता हूॅजाने अनजाने ही सहीपर कडवा सच बोलता हूॅजीवन के अनसुलझे रहस्योॅ कोपरत दर परत खोलता हूॅ इसलिए &#8230;मैॅ तो बस बोलता हूॅ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>लिखने का शौक तो नहीॅ<br>पर शब्दोॅ मेॅ रस घोलता हूॅ<br>जाने अनजाने ही सही<br>पर कडवा सच बोलता हूॅ<br>जीवन के अनसुलझे रहस्योॅ को<br>परत दर परत खोलता हूॅ<br><br>इसलिए &#8230;<br>मैॅ तो बस बोलता हूॅ<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/main-to-bas-bolta-hoon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Issues India needs to sort out in next 10 years to really be a SuperPower</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 12:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=23&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=23</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are many things that Indian Government needs to fix but these are some of them which I feel will make or break our country’s future in the coming years. Inflation: With the most of India’s vast population living close to or below the poverty line, inflation acts as a ‘Poor Man’s Tax’. This effect &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Issues India needs to sort out in next 10 years to really be a SuperPower</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are many things that Indian Government needs to fix but these are some of them which I feel will make or break our country’s future in the coming years.</p>
<p><strong>Inflation</strong>: With the most of India’s vast population living close to or below the poverty line, inflation acts as a ‘Poor Man’s Tax’. This effect is amplified when food prices rise, since food represents more than half of the expenditure of this group.</p>
<p><strong>Terrorism</strong> &#8211; I know it should have been on the top of the list however I chose it to be on the 2nd place because people are any which ways dying due to not being able to feed themselves because of the rise in price of the consumable commodities.We spend a huge amount of money on defense but where is the defense. We have been preparing for WW III for I don’t know how long. And in that process we have forgotten to spend money in the right direction.</p>
<p><strong>Unemployment</strong> – Not a big deal in the rural areas but a huge concern for the people living in the urban areas. It seems to have deteriorated in the past 1 year but we need to go miles from here. We are no where near what a developed country should be. Unemployment rate as of now is around 10%</p>
<p><strong>Infrastructure</strong> – We need around 100 CWG games organized in our country for the infrastructure to improve. After writing the last sentence, I pondered over it for a couple of seconds and this funny thought occurred to me that we would have 100 more corrupt events and millions of rupees will go into our politicians’ pockets again.</p>
<p><strong>Indo-Pak Relation</strong>: To be absolutely frank, we have to take a stand if we really want to solve this problem. It may not be a problem for the neighboring country but it is affecting us as a country, a lot. We have enough army to defeat a country like Pakistan. At the least give the opponent something to think about before they try or think about doing something which brings disgrace to our country. We keep sitting idle and wait for their response all the time after someone takes responsibility to attack India.</p>
<p><strong>Indian Constitution</strong>: I feel the root of all the problems is our constitution. Written over 60 years ago. Things are bound to change. We are still living in the same 60 year old world. We were a developing country then and are still a developing country. There hasn&#8217;t been any change, moreover our politicians and constitution has brought nothing but misery to our country.</p>
<p><strong>Uneducated Politicians</strong>: We are living in a country where an uneducated/illiterate (politically) person can enter the world of politics. We are living in a state of spiritual disbelief of which our politicians are taking undue advantage. We need to get out of this situation, and pretty fast. But the concern is who will bell the cat. These people are strong and powerful because of their unlawful deeds and its hard to reverse the effects for good.</p>
<p><strong>Division of States</strong>: If we can divide the states then it’s imminent that we would have around 30 countries within India in the next 10 years. Dividing states further was the first weakness shown by a weak leader of our country. People will demand unethical things, it does not mean you mess up with the idea of peace and forget what you are supposed to do.</p>
<p><strong>Communal Riots</strong>: We are the world’s second largest standing army in the world. It definitely means something. But a bunch of people take over a state. Terrorize it. I am not convinced with the fact that a million armed forces can’t take down these Naxalites or any other Maoist groups. We declared them as terrorist groups but we can’t fight them. Over 30% of Indian states are affected by these groups in one way or the other.</p>
<p><strong>Education</strong>: 40% of world’s illiterate population is from India. Nothing much to say about this one.</p>
<p>These are my thoughts. There are so many good things to point out. And the web is flooded with information like that but till the time we don’t highlight the bad it won’t turn into good. That’s my theory. We can’t make something right till the time we don’t believe that there is something wrong.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How India lost its freedom after Independence</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/do-we-need-bhagat-singh-and-rajguru-like-patriots-to-free-our-country-again-from-our-old-conservative-politicians/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/do-we-need-bhagat-singh-and-rajguru-like-patriots-to-free-our-country-again-from-our-old-conservative-politicians/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 12:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=40</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What do you think. I know I am talking the hard way here. But the situation is like that it will not get resolved with Mahatma Gandhi. We need people like Bhagat Singh and Rajguru to take initiatives and save us from our old conservative politicians. The situation is getting worse day by day. The &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/do-we-need-bhagat-singh-and-rajguru-like-patriots-to-free-our-country-again-from-our-old-conservative-politicians/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">How India lost its freedom after Independence</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What do you think. I know I am talking the hard way here. But the situation is like that it will not get resolved with Mahatma Gandhi. We need people like Bhagat Singh and Rajguru to take initiatives and save us from our old conservative politicians.</p>
<p>The situation is getting worse day by day. The crime is taking its toll. No political party seems to care about the citizens of India. Everybody is playing the blame game.</p>
<p>I believe India would have gone miles ahead if we had saved the leaders like Rajiv Gandhi. We need young blood to lead India, not 70 year old man who can barely walk on his feet. We need to come out of our 500 years old mentality that only old men are experienced. We are living in 21st century where what we are learning today, none of our politicians would have even dreamt of doing. Forget about learning, 80% of our politicians would not be graduate even.</p>
<p>We need educated young people who understands the dynamics of today. We don’t need people who are 70 years old and does not even know where to invest and services to provide to their citizens.</p>
<p>I don’t want to elaborate on this. I think you have understood what I am trying to say.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/do-we-need-bhagat-singh-and-rajguru-like-patriots-to-free-our-country-again-from-our-old-conservative-politicians/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biggest Political Mistake in Indian History</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 12:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=38</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It all happened just before the Indian Independence Day and it happened so fast that no body could even think the aftermaths of the event would be so disastrous that the whole world would laugh at a nation which was divided into 2 by some lazy people who never thought that things could be worked &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Biggest Political Mistake in Indian History</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It all happened just before the Indian Independence Day and it happened so fast that no body could even think the aftermaths of the event would be so disastrous that the whole world would laugh at a nation which was divided into 2 by some lazy people who never thought that things could be worked out. Yes I am talking about the Partition of India and Pakistan.</p>
<p><span id="more-1299"></span>Today is the Independence Day and I want to give you a reason to think. I have a question for you guys.</p>
<blockquote><p>Do you think Jawahar Lal Nehru did the right thing by agreeing to Muhammad Ali Jinnah ?</p></blockquote>
<p>Before you come to any conclusions, I just want to let you know that I am just asking for your opinion. I have put across my thoughts, now I need to know what you think. Pt. Jawahar Lal Nehru when agreed to Muhammad Ali Jinnah would have thought that now India would live happily ever after. But I guess they were wrong, I mean they have been wrong all throughout. Pakistan has gone so far sometimes after the division that its unbearable, but still we Indians believe in Peace. We still believe in talks with our neighbor countries. We still believe that <strong>“Kutte ki poonch Seedhi ho jayegi”.</strong> We still think that now we will live without any fear since our Prime Minister is a bit aggressive now. What the hell ?</p>
<p>My only point is that its our politicians who have been giving us pain all through out . Had Jawahar Lal Nehru not agreed to Muhammad, we would have had a single country spanning a long Kashmir having the most amazing tourist place ever. Imagine Afridi and Sehwag opening for India. No power would have stopped that India to win against any country. What a scene would that be. Imagine the biggest tourist place in the world for its beautiful mountains, a place known to be heaven on earth. We could have been so advanced today that the whole world would have envied us.</p>
<p>But let’s face the reality. Since both the countries are not in good terms and are always fighting, we spend over billions on getting the most latest and deadliest weapons from Israel and Russia. Just imagine 3-4% of GDP of India and Pakistan going into preparing for battle against each other. Imagine this money spent for good cause, for betterment of both countries. None of the countries people have proper food to eat, but we want to fight. The whole world looks at us as a country of poor, which some time ago used to be the “<strong>Golden Bird</strong>.” Had we spent those billions for improving our infrastructure then what a country India would have been. People would have lead a life which they deserve rather than leading their lives in fear of getting blasted in some suicide bombing.</p>
<p>I really feel that our life was fcuked on that day when India and Pakistan parted their ways. Just wait for some time, its quite possible that India will get partitioned further because we have the same Congress in center which made all this possible. Rumors are that China is thinking of creating a mess in India and trying to divide India into several parts.</p>
<p>What do you say ?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/biggest-political-mistake-in-indian-history/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I see a Policeman on motorbike without a Helmet, I stop him and hand him over a ticket</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 13:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=43</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[How cool will that be ? I mean I was just wondering for quite some time now that how nice it would be if we could really take control of our law enforcement. Imagine while roaming on the road you see someone breaking the law and you take out your camera, take a picture while &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">I see a Policeman on motorbike without a Helmet, I stop him and hand him over a ticket</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How cool will that be ? I mean I was just wondering for quite some time now that how nice it would be if we could really take control of our law enforcement. Imagine while roaming on the road you see someone breaking the law and you take out your camera, take a picture while he is breaking the traffic rules. Catch hold of him. Show him the picture and hand over the ticket to him. I mean imagine the force we would have on roads and people will think twice before doing anything wrong.</p>
<p>People may use the power for wrong doing but I think we can start with some intelligent and responsible people like Bus Conductor, Shopkeepers who are sitting on a road watching it all the time. A Pan wallah on the Traffic Signal.</p>
<p>I am thinking of creating another website where I urge people to submit such pictures where people are captured while breaking the law. And our law enforcement team has to just identify the person and fine him/her.</p>
<p>Think about it. Bye !</p>
<p>Let me know your thoughts by posting your comments.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>India China comparison – An eye opener</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/india-china-economic-agricultural-industrial-education-comparison-world-bank/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/india-china-economic-agricultural-industrial-education-comparison-world-bank/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 18:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=83</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Below is a really nice comparison of India and China. Where we stand in terms of population, income, industry and many other. China started their family planning policy in 1970, India in 1952 In 2001 our birth rate was nearly 3 times more than China. 27 births per 1000 as against 8.8 for China! India &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/india-china-economic-agricultural-industrial-education-comparison-world-bank/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">India China comparison – An eye opener</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Below is a really nice comparison of India and China. Where we stand in terms of population, income, industry and many other.</p>
<p><strong>China started their family planning policy in 1970, India in 1952</strong></p>
<p>In 2001 our birth rate was nearly 3 times more than China. 27 births per 1000 as against 8.8 for China! India is adding 18 million people per year, against 9 million per year in China. Total addition to population is a function of total births minus total deaths.</p>
<p><strong>India’s per capita earning is US$440 per year against US$990 per year in China</strong></p>
<p>As per the World Bank, the poverty line definition is US$1 per person per day or US$365/person/year, for underdeveloped countries like India, China etc. As per the official data from both governments, China has 3% population below the poverty line, compared to India’s 26 to 29%! Only better governance can help.</p>
<p><strong>China attracts 87 million tourists per year (this is expected to reach 90 million in 2002) against 2.5 million per year to India.</strong></p>
<p>The international Tourism Industry is [7 times the size of I.T. or software] about, US$3700 billion per year. India, in spite of its old history and 21 cultures and languages, seems to have ‘missed the bus’, in Tourism. Tourism is a very big employment generator. It is estimated that every one tourist generates 2 to 4 jobs. Tourism promotes International trade and understanding.<br />
<strong>How will we provide additional 10 million jobs per year?</strong></p>
<p>The Public Sector and State/Central Government, which is already overstaffed, has a total of 18.7 million employees, therefore offers very little scope for new employment. We have to look outside the government for new employment. The unorganized sector and the SME’s (SSI is not SME) offer the maximum scope for employment, like in all other countries of the world, including China. SME’s account for nearly 75% of employment and 80% of trainees!</p>
<p><strong>The Government can only facilitate jobs; they cannot provide jobs for the 300 million partly or fully unemployed in India!</strong></p>
<p>At 10 million jobs per year it will take us 30 years to remove unemployment, at 5 million jobs for year it will take us 60 years! The present Indian ‘mind set’ will require rethinking and reorganization of the existing perceptions about Public Sector enterprises, and the actual role they are supposed to play! Only efficient organizations can deliver results and growth. Only better governance and efficient administration can deliver results!</p>
<p><strong>In Foreign Direct investment, FDI, China + Hong Kong received US$106 billion last year [US$70billion from NRC&#8217;s] vs US$3.6 billion [US$0.2b from NRI&#8217;s] for India! Only better Governance can attract FDI and Tourists. In exports, China is nearly +700% of India</strong></p>
<p>Taking the exports of Hong Kong + Macau into account, China’s exports would be +1000% of India! China’s GDP is 50% in manufacturing or $ 650 billion per year. India’s GDP is 25% in manufacturing or $110 billion per year. China’s manufacturing base is nearly 6 times of India’s.</p>
<p><span id="more-2946"></span><br />
<strong>In agriculture our yields per acre, are well below the international norms.</strong></p>
<p>India could be a giant exporter of food, only if we could put our ‘house in order’ to near world class standards! China with lesser cultivable land, produces double the food grains, at 415 million tons per year compared with India’s 208 million tons per year. God has been very kind to India with a lot of sunshine, rain, rivers, lakes, coastline and good hard working citizens.<br />
The governance of hamlets, villages, cities, districts, Government and Semi-Government agencies, as facilitators, have not done enough to show the results that India is able or capable of achieving. India would definitely rate as the No.1 country in the world, for Potential vs Performance!<br />
Indians score high marks on performance, outside India! This is because the Governance is better outside. In countries where the Governance &amp; Administration is poor, the performance of its citizens is also low!</p>
<p><strong>In Education, 99.1% of Chinese children attend school for 9 years, this ensures a high level of literacy. In India, literacy is 50 to 60%</strong></p>
<p>While IIT’s, IIM’s are important, the country’s real growth will come because of primary and secondary education and vocational and educational training in all districts of the country. India can rise and shine in exports, agriculture, literacy and other areas with better governance.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/india-china-economic-agricultural-industrial-education-comparison-world-bank/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indian Government asking Social Networks and Google to censor political parties and politicians. But why?</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/indian-government-ranks-3rd-in-terms-of-reteriving-data-from-google/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/indian-government-ranks-3rd-in-terms-of-reteriving-data-from-google/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 18:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=75</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Recently read a news about US government asking Google to provide lots and lots of data related which is related to the services Google provides. I am sure they must be utilizing this data for get to the corrupts. And then automatically me being a typical Indian wanted to check our country’s  rank in that &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/indian-government-ranks-3rd-in-terms-of-reteriving-data-from-google/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Indian Government asking Social Networks and Google to censor political parties and politicians. But why?</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently read a news about US government asking Google to provide lots and lots of data related which is related to the services Google provides. I am sure they must be utilizing this data for get to the corrupts. And then automatically me being a typical Indian wanted to check our country’s  rank in that list. To my surprise we rank 3rd in that list after US and Brazil. Wow.. It feels great to be in a such a list. Well that’s one side of the story I was thinking. But after reading the data requests that Google received I started thinking about what would our government departments have actually asked for. Checkout for analysis after the break.</p>
<p><span id="more-2453"></span><br />
<img loading="lazy" class="alignnone" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932im_/http://img201.imageshack.us/img201/1192/indiangovernmentgoogled.png" alt="" width="600" height="321" /><br />
<strong>About Google Transparency</strong> : Its an interactive map of Government Requests that shows the number of government inquiries for information about users and requests for Google to take down or censor content. The interactive Traffic graphs provide information about traffic to Google services around the world. Each graph shows historic traffic patterns for a given country/region and service. By illustrating outages, this tool visualizes disruptions in the free flow of information, whether it’s a government blocking information or a cable being cut.</p>
<p>Below is the graph that shows the requests from Indian Government agencies to Google in the past 1 year.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932im_/http://img52.imageshack.us/img52/6910/searchpatterngoogletran.png" alt="" width="600" height="177" /></p>
<p>I’ll leave you guys with that thought because I need to go to bed now. OK, still let me give you some perspective. Have you ever looked at <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932/http://www.revolutioners.com/where-the-hell-are-indian-web-developers/">our government websites</a>. I have talked about it earlier as well. But I think the more we are so called developing the more our government is showcase that they are technically sound. I mean I am not talking about the politicians. We bloody pay some great amount of money in taxes can’t we hire some sound technical guys to handle these stuffs. Alright I think I am deviating from the topic.</p>
<p>OK, I was suppose to give you some perspective. Alright, I was just looking at my blog and saw an advertisement on my blog via adsense that I have setup. I did not click on the ad but copied the link to the URL. You believe me it was <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932/http://www.delhitrafficpolice.nic.in/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Delhi Traffic Police</a> Delhi Traffic Police is advertising via Google Adwords. Anyways, then in curiosity I went to check out the website. Our government needs to accept the fact that their developers su*k.  So there were some nice presentations regarding common wealth games. I could not believe my eyes by looking at the presentation. I mean such a big country and not even one single fucking person in India who can make a good looking presentation. You don’t believe me check <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932/http://www.delhitrafficpolice.nic.in/cwg1.ppt" target="_blank" rel="noopener">this out</a>. And yeah I was in an impression since it being a website where the whole world would be browsing to look for updated information but then I saw a link to download flash player which still links to Macromedia site. Thanks to Adobe that they have redirected it to the right place.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/indian-government-ranks-3rd-in-terms-of-reteriving-data-from-google/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smoking Ban Act, India – Must Read</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/smoking-and-tobacco-facts-and-figures-india-smoking-ban-india/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/smoking-and-tobacco-facts-and-figures-india-smoking-ban-india/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 18:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=80</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Let’s see the scene of tobacco and smoking in India first. OK, some facts and figures about Smoking and Tobacco in India. In India, tobacco use causes nearly 40 percent of all health problems and 50 percent of all cancers, according to Health Minister, Anbumani Ramadoss. In India The tobacco contributes to 56.4% and 44.9% &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/smoking-and-tobacco-facts-and-figures-india-smoking-ban-india/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Smoking Ban Act, India – Must Read</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Let’s see the scene of tobacco and smoking in India first. OK, some facts and figures about Smoking and Tobacco in India.</p>
<ul>
<li>In India, tobacco use causes nearly 40 percent of all health problems and 50 percent of all cancers, according to Health Minister, Anbumani Ramadoss.</li>
<li>In India The tobacco contributes to 56.4% and 44.9% of cancers in men and women, respectively.</li>
<li><strong>India ranks 2nd in smoking cigarette in top 10 countries.</strong></li>
<li>Nearly 17 percent of students in India, aged 15 and under, use some form of tobacco, mainly cigarettes, according to a survey conducted by the World Health Organization.</li>
<li>India has the largest number of oral cancer cases in the world which is due to tobacco.</li>
<li>In India, an estimated 120 million people smoke. But the problem is that smoking in India is on rising side unlike Western countries.</li>
<li>Cigarettes compromise just 19 percent of tobacco consumption in India however Bidis account for 53 percent, according to the Bidi Smoking and Public Health report by the Union Ministry of Health and Family.</li>
<li><strong>Around 1 billion Bidis are sold in India every year.</strong> Bidis contain more tar, nicotine and other toxic substances but less tobacco than traditional cigarettes.</li>
<li>Tobacco smoking accounts for 82% of Chronic obstructive lung disease in India.</li>
</ul>
<p>It’s been around 1 year now that Indian Government imposed ban on smoking in public places including government and private offices. You might not know but this act was in existence for 2 years before our government thought of implementing it seriously. Seriously, imagine. We create acts, put them in files, make a pile out of it, put them in a room somewhere and then don’t look at them for 3-4 years. Then suddenly you wake up and try to enforce everything. And I’ll tell you some facts about this so called smoking ban in public places today. Well, I think I don’t really have to tell you anything as most of you already know it to some extent.</p>
<p>Alright let’s first discuss what the ban exactly is. As per the government, no one is allowed to smoke in public places including public transportation and public offices etc. As per the rules, smoking is banned in shopping malls, cinema halls, public/private work place, hotels, banquet halls, discotheques, canteen, coffee house, pubs, bars, airport lounge, railway stations. Public places cover all government, private and public sector offices as well. I work with an MNC and believe me there people adhere to the regulation. People go out of the offices for smoke. Earlier employees could smoke in the office premises but ever since the smoking ban everyone is prohibited to smoke inside the office premises. Also, any employer found to be letting its employees smoke inside the office premises are supposed to be penalized. Moreover I think people working with big MNCs in India are mature enough to understand what it means for our country. We tell clients coming from abroad that there are restrictions on smoking inside the premises, so we don’t want them to see us smoking in there.</p>
<p><span id="more-2359"></span>Alright, that’s the rule now lets see how is our government who imposed the ban is doing about it. You remember me <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104834/http://www.revolutioners.com/visit-to-mtnl-sanchaar-haat-a-must-read/">visiting MTNL office</a>, I saw employees smoking inside the building. Well, that was not it. I shave seen many more government offices with people smoking inside the offices. But today was the height of everything, I went to a government office today (would not want to quote) and saw employee smoking in the building that too on his seat as well. And the head of the office was also smoking in the office.</p>
<p>I just want to understand why has it always been like this? <strong>Why do we citizens only have to follow all the rules?</strong> Why the people who create the rules, don’t have to adhere to them.</p>
<p>And believe me its not the only thing which is wrong these days Things like these keep happening in our country. It has been in existence in one or another form with each and every government department of India. <strong>For example, Delhi Police does not need any helmet while driving on the road but they want each and every rider in Delhi to wear helmet and don’t miss a chance of not giving ticket to the rider if he/she is not wearing the helmet.</strong>Similarly they want everyone to wear seat-belts while driving even if the traffic is not even moving. <em>Every government department you go in, you’d find yourself on the verge of having an argument all the time</em>. People don’t really seem to take their jobs seriously.</p>
<p>I am not able to understand the mentality of our government employees as in why do these people behave like this. I mean its good that you are sitting there in a government office but aren’t you suppose to work. Yeah, let me not just start that. I’d need an entire book on that just one post won’t be enough I guess.</p>
<p>Don’t know when would we be free, free as in FREE…! The ultimate question is should we try and ban these things from selling or should we ban smoking of cigarettes. ?</p>
<p>Some interesting reading about tobacco and smoking.</p>
<ul>
<li>Avoiding tobacco adds 20 years to the life of a teenager.</li>
<li><strong>In India, 900,000 people die due to tobacco related diseases per year.</strong></li>
<li>Tobacco smoking accounts for 82% of Chronic obstructive lung disease in India.</li>
<li><strong>Tobacco indirectly causes lung tuberculosis.</strong> Prevalence of TB is about 3 times as great among the ever-smokers as among the never-smokers. The heavier the smoking, either cigarettes or bidis, the greater the prevalence of TB among smokers. Mortality from TB is 3 to 4 times as great in ever-smokers as in never-smokers.</li>
<li><strong>About half of the teenagers who use tobacco will eventually be killed by it (about a quarter in middle age and a quarter in old age).</strong></li>
<li>It is estimated that India as compared to any other country will have the fastest rise in tobacco related deaths each year.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/smoking-and-tobacco-facts-and-figures-india-smoking-ban-india/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to help your Government host a successful event of any kind</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/commonwealth-games-2010-things-you-can-do-to-contribute-for-a-successful-event/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/commonwealth-games-2010-things-you-can-do-to-contribute-for-a-successful-event/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2009 19:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=98</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Alright, I think its the time that I talk about the burning issue of Commonwealth Games supposed to be held in Delhi, India. I think we are trying our best to keep them here but somehow I am getting this feeling that we are not ready. Our government has not even started the construction of &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/commonwealth-games-2010-things-you-can-do-to-contribute-for-a-successful-event/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">How to help your Government host a successful event of any kind</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Alright, I think its the time that I talk about the burning issue of Commonwealth Games supposed to be held in Delhi, India. I think we are trying our best to keep them here but somehow I am getting this feeling that we are not ready. Our government has not even started the construction of some of the stadiums. We I really wish our Indian Government best of luck. May God bless them with some wisdom. Why do these guys not understand that it will be less shameful if we tell the Commonwealth Games community that we are not ready to host the event rather then the athletes coming to India and coming to know that we are not even able to provide the basic facilities to them. Forget about organizing the Commonwealth Games 2010.</p>
<p>Anyways, If I assume it happens and we have all the stadiums ready to organize the games. Though our government has to do a really good job here to crack this nut. What if the people of India are not ready. We are overlooking this part. We have not even considered this factor yet. There will be a huge number of foreigners coming to Delhi and Indian tourism will get a drastic boost during September till December 2010.</p>
<p>I feel there are certain things that we need to take are as Indian citizens. People who are coming from other countries will not be familiar with our countries, so we will have to make sure we help them as much as we can. China was ready for Olympics a year ago from the actual event and we are running late.</p>
<p>Today I am just asking to you remember these 10 things which if done properly would definitely make our country better in terms of hospitality and people coming from other countries will also look at as developing country not under developed.</p>
<p><strong>Give Shelter</strong> : As per Indian Government, Delhi is going to be short of accommodation for at least 6,000 tourists coming to Delhi. I urge every Delhite to make sure if you know someone who is coming to see Commonwealth Games then ask them to stay with you at your house if possible. Otherwise it will really be shameful to not to have space to stay for them.</p>
<p><strong>Have some Generosity</strong> : You might have seen it already when people come from the western side of the world in India they are being overcharged by Indian people. To a certain limit its acceptable. But when people coming at this large scale I don’t think it will be required to do that. So I would urge you all Indians to not to promote such things. If you see some auto rickshaw or taxi driver or any shopkeeper overcharging the foreigners, please go help them.</p>
<p><strong>Keep your city Clean</strong> : Don’t just pee and spit anywhere, I know many of you are reading this would not come under that category, but just think about it. Our government has spent millions in creating places for emergencies like these. I wish we had a rule for penalizing anyone who is found to be spitting on road. And anyone not following it would be charged 500 Rs on the spot. And mainly those Gukta guys, I just can’t explain it. So, guys please mind your tongue for 2 months at least.</p>
<p><strong>Learn to behave</strong> : We by nature are very generous and hospitable, but only for Indians and our brothers. We need to show this hospitality to everyone who is coming to our country. This is the only way we can show our hospitality to the world and people who would come and visit our mother land. Remember<strong> ” Athiti Devo Bhava”</strong> There might be people who are coming to India for the first time and would expect everything to go right.</p>
<p><strong>Help National Security</strong> : We saw terrorist attacks in Mumbai and Delhi this year and last year as well. Mumbai Blasts, Delhi Blasts etc. I am not sure what our government has learnt from it. But I want you to help avoid these kind of mishaps. Help our Security professionals to keep our country safe. I would request you all to report anything you suspect.</p>
<p><strong>Follow traffic rules</strong> : <em>Better late then never</em>, what is this. I don’t understand. Who is <em>late</em>, what is never. I don’t know. All I know is I am getting late and if the traffic signal is not working then I am not going to wait. Please, don’t don’t do this. Don’t show that we don’t have traffic manners. Indians need to understand that traffic rules are not meant to be broken only, then are suppose to be followed as well. Its OK if you wait for 2 minutes and let other pass. If you notice, in hurry you spend 15 minutes standing on the signal because you stuck everybody on the signal. Don’t <a href="http://www.revolutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/">drive rash</a> on roads during the games.</p>
<p><strong>Respect their cultures</strong> : We might see people coming from various countries and cultures. We need to learn to respect their cultures. Their way of living will be different. In western culture display of public affection is not bad but in our culture its not suppose to be a good thing. We need to come out of this conservative ideology and start behaving like a developed country. If we need to be a Developed Country.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/commonwealth-games-2010-things-you-can-do-to-contribute-for-a-successful-event/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ISRO’s Bhuvan will not help the terrorists while Google Earth helped – What a Joke</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/isros-bhuvan-will-not-help-the-terrorists-while-google-earth-helped-what-a-joke/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/isros-bhuvan-will-not-help-the-terrorists-while-google-earth-helped-what-a-joke/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 18:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=89</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ISRO announced today that they will bring Bhuvan the Google Earth competitor in the market. The main feature of ISRO Bhuvan would be that compared to Google Earth, ISRO Bhuvan will be able to zoom till 10 meter anywhere in India. Now tell me last time when terrorists attacked on Parliament and 26/11, our politicians &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/isros-bhuvan-will-not-help-the-terrorists-while-google-earth-helped-what-a-joke/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">ISRO’s Bhuvan will not help the terrorists while Google Earth helped – What a Joke</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ISRO announced today that they will bring Bhuvan the Google Earth competitor in the market. The main feature of <a href="http://www.revolutioners.com/isro-chandrayaan-fails-plans-to-waste-money-again-with-chandrayaan-2/">ISRO</a> Bhuvan would be that compared to Google Earth, ISRO Bhuvan will be able to zoom till 10 meter anywhere in India. Now tell me last time when terrorists attacked on Parliament and 26/11, our politicians said that these guys used Google earth. Will they not have a better tool now. I am not able to understand why <span class="removed_link" title="http://www.revolutioners.com/commonwealth-games-2010-things-you-can-do-to-contribute-for-a-successful-event/">Indian Government</span> is funding such pathetic projects. Another such example of failure is Chandrayaan. I mean I don’t understand why would India send a satellite on moon to find out what ? US have done the research there is nothing that Indian scientists will reveal now. And whatever happened was expected out of it. Chandrayaan was utter failure. All Indian tax payer’s money is going in vain. Nothing is being done for the safety of civilians.</p>
<p>We are still living in the same unprotected world where you don’t know whether you will be alive tomorrow or not. People are so scared to come out of their houses. If there is no terrorist attacks then there are internal terrorists, I mean every day you hear about kidnapping, murders and robberies. Everyday there is a new story about crime. I am sick and tired of listening to these kind of news. I wish I could do something about it. Our law and order needs to be changed. People after being convicted as well roam freely in India. That&#8217;s how our law works. Anyways, I think I deviated from the topic. So what I was saying is that the same way we failed in <a href="http://www.revolutioners.com/isro-chandrayaan-fails-plans-to-waste-money-again-with-chandrayaan-2/">Chandrayaan</a>. ISRO Bhuvan is also going to fail, these guys don’t know what they are up against. Its Google.</p>
<p>Oh my God. We seriously need some developers in Indian Government Department. <a href="http://www.revolutioners.com/where-the-hell-are-indian-web-developers/">Our government websites are damn funny</a>. I can’t even begin to tell you.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/isros-bhuvan-will-not-help-the-terrorists-while-google-earth-helped-what-a-joke/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
