<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>solutions &#8211; rLOVEutioners</title>
	<atom:link href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tag/solutions/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/</link>
	<description>revoution for evolution</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 13:38:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Issues India needs to sort out in next 10 years to really be a SuperPower</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 12:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=23&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=23</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are many things that Indian Government needs to fix but these are some of them which I feel will make or break our country’s future in the coming years. Inflation: With the most of India’s vast population living close to or below the poverty line, inflation acts as a ‘Poor Man’s Tax’. This effect &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Issues India needs to sort out in next 10 years to really be a SuperPower</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are many things that Indian Government needs to fix but these are some of them which I feel will make or break our country’s future in the coming years.</p>
<p><strong>Inflation</strong>: With the most of India’s vast population living close to or below the poverty line, inflation acts as a ‘Poor Man’s Tax’. This effect is amplified when food prices rise, since food represents more than half of the expenditure of this group.</p>
<p><strong>Terrorism</strong> &#8211; I know it should have been on the top of the list however I chose it to be on the 2nd place because people are any which ways dying due to not being able to feed themselves because of the rise in price of the consumable commodities.We spend a huge amount of money on defense but where is the defense. We have been preparing for WW III for I don’t know how long. And in that process we have forgotten to spend money in the right direction.</p>
<p><strong>Unemployment</strong> – Not a big deal in the rural areas but a huge concern for the people living in the urban areas. It seems to have deteriorated in the past 1 year but we need to go miles from here. We are no where near what a developed country should be. Unemployment rate as of now is around 10%</p>
<p><strong>Infrastructure</strong> – We need around 100 CWG games organized in our country for the infrastructure to improve. After writing the last sentence, I pondered over it for a couple of seconds and this funny thought occurred to me that we would have 100 more corrupt events and millions of rupees will go into our politicians’ pockets again.</p>
<p><strong>Indo-Pak Relation</strong>: To be absolutely frank, we have to take a stand if we really want to solve this problem. It may not be a problem for the neighboring country but it is affecting us as a country, a lot. We have enough army to defeat a country like Pakistan. At the least give the opponent something to think about before they try or think about doing something which brings disgrace to our country. We keep sitting idle and wait for their response all the time after someone takes responsibility to attack India.</p>
<p><strong>Indian Constitution</strong>: I feel the root of all the problems is our constitution. Written over 60 years ago. Things are bound to change. We are still living in the same 60 year old world. We were a developing country then and are still a developing country. There hasn&#8217;t been any change, moreover our politicians and constitution has brought nothing but misery to our country.</p>
<p><strong>Uneducated Politicians</strong>: We are living in a country where an uneducated/illiterate (politically) person can enter the world of politics. We are living in a state of spiritual disbelief of which our politicians are taking undue advantage. We need to get out of this situation, and pretty fast. But the concern is who will bell the cat. These people are strong and powerful because of their unlawful deeds and its hard to reverse the effects for good.</p>
<p><strong>Division of States</strong>: If we can divide the states then it’s imminent that we would have around 30 countries within India in the next 10 years. Dividing states further was the first weakness shown by a weak leader of our country. People will demand unethical things, it does not mean you mess up with the idea of peace and forget what you are supposed to do.</p>
<p><strong>Communal Riots</strong>: We are the world’s second largest standing army in the world. It definitely means something. But a bunch of people take over a state. Terrorize it. I am not convinced with the fact that a million armed forces can’t take down these Naxalites or any other Maoist groups. We declared them as terrorist groups but we can’t fight them. Over 30% of Indian states are affected by these groups in one way or the other.</p>
<p><strong>Education</strong>: 40% of world’s illiterate population is from India. Nothing much to say about this one.</p>
<p>These are my thoughts. There are so many good things to point out. And the web is flooded with information like that but till the time we don’t highlight the bad it won’t turn into good. That’s my theory. We can’t make something right till the time we don’t believe that there is something wrong.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I see a Policeman on motorbike without a Helmet, I stop him and hand him over a ticket</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 13:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=43</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[How cool will that be ? I mean I was just wondering for quite some time now that how nice it would be if we could really take control of our law enforcement. Imagine while roaming on the road you see someone breaking the law and you take out your camera, take a picture while &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">I see a Policeman on motorbike without a Helmet, I stop him and hand him over a ticket</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How cool will that be ? I mean I was just wondering for quite some time now that how nice it would be if we could really take control of our law enforcement. Imagine while roaming on the road you see someone breaking the law and you take out your camera, take a picture while he is breaking the traffic rules. Catch hold of him. Show him the picture and hand over the ticket to him. I mean imagine the force we would have on roads and people will think twice before doing anything wrong.</p>
<p>People may use the power for wrong doing but I think we can start with some intelligent and responsible people like Bus Conductor, Shopkeepers who are sitting on a road watching it all the time. A Pan wallah on the Traffic Signal.</p>
<p>I am thinking of creating another website where I urge people to submit such pictures where people are captured while breaking the law. And our law enforcement team has to just identify the person and fine him/her.</p>
<p>Think about it. Bye !</p>
<p>Let me know your thoughts by posting your comments.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Does Wikipedia really need money?</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-does-wikipedia-need-money/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-does-wikipedia-need-money/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 18:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=70</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I guess I am not the only one who feels the same way. I was just going through the Wikipedia Financial today on their page. What I saw there made me look into this matter in much greater detail. Wikimedia spent almost $3500, 000 in recruiting and wages in the financial year 2009-2010. And it &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-does-wikipedia-need-money/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Does Wikipedia really need money?</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I guess I am not the only one who feels the same way. I was just going through the Wikipedia Financial today on <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323132239/http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/foundation/d/dd/2010-11_Wikimedia_Foundation_Annual_Plan_FINAL_FOR_WEBSITE.pdf">their page</a>. What I saw there made me look into this matter in much greater detail. Wikimedia spent almost $3500, 000 in recruiting and wages in the financial year 2009-2010. And it grew to almost $6000, 000 in the financial year 2010-2011. I was just wondering isn’t that too much for <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323132239/http://strategy.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Foundation_employees.png">50 employees of Wikimedia</a>. I am now confused as in what is actually a non-profit organization. I mean apart from running your websites do you also need money to run the show? Posting a conversation excerpt that I found in a forum.</p>
<p><img src="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323132239im_/http://img220.imageshack.us/img220/6794/wikipediax.jpg" alt="" width="600" /></p>
<blockquote><p>This is why I have lost faith in humanity, because too many people believe what is told to them and would rather believe in the “make me feel safe, secure, and okay” state of mind rather than face reality. It is a reality that non-profit and profit organizations use fraud to gain extra bucks. This is not conspiracy theories as it is even reported in mainstream media. You would have to be either very naive or not informed of what is going on in the world not to realize this.</p>
<p>Look at the last decade during the many world disasters, the mainstream news media always reported on scams/misuse of funds/missing funds for donations drives for:</p>
<ul>
<li>9/11 Victim families</li>
<li>Tsunami relief 2004</li>
<li>Haiti earthquake relief and many others.</li>
</ul>
<p>Just watch/read the news the next time another major disaster happens and donation drives start up, and you will see it shows up. Now, having said all this, I never said that no one should not donate to Wikipedia. I consider Wikipeidia one of the most important acomplishements of human effort for this decade and maybe even farther back because its primary cause is to spread information, something I believe strongly in.</p>
<p>And that is exactly why I mention that donation drives are not 100% innocent just because they have the “non-profit” tag on them. Those that still refuse to believe this reality attempt to counter with “but they report what they use the money for!” And then further counter by saying you have no evidence in return to go against it.</p>
<p>However evidence does exist in the form of history of scams/fraud in past donation drives for various causes. Also, the excuse of saying they report use is very naive as it *assumes* that those reporting are not involved or prone to fraud or are 100% honest. Even in the face of history proving that people can’t be trusted, which is way laws, courts, and oversight organizations exist (which I will also add are also not immune to being corrupt [as proven by history]).</p>
<p>Beyond failing to observe or forgetting history, I believe most people don’t realize this because they have never been in a “controller” position without oversight, in which human bias and nature is unchecked. This is why in science, double-blind experiments are use to remove bias. However, in the controller position without oversight, this is not removed. If you study literature, this topic (i.e. Lord of the Flies) has been covered many times throughout history as well, even up until now and in films.</p>
<p>Again, I just want to say I support Wikipedia because I so strongly believe in the spreading of information, and by that believe I attempt to spread a little, perhaps unpleasant piece of information as well. Which instead of being pushed under the plate should be swallowed whole, even if it tastes bad and unsettles your bowels. Even still you should make it part of you, move on, and seek out more information.</p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-does-wikipedia-need-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How about telemarketers get charged 1000 rs for calling you</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 19:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=95</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Every now and then my mind keeps flooding with some insane ideas. But after some time when I think about it, it all starts making some sense. I was on my way to office 2-3 days ago and I get a call from someone trying to sell me some Life Insurance. This guy has been &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">How about telemarketers get charged 1000 rs for calling you</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every now and then my mind keeps flooding with some insane ideas. But after some time when I think about it, it all starts making some sense. I was on my way to office 2-3 days ago and I get a call from someone trying to sell me some Life Insurance. This guy has been calling me for i don’t know may be for the last 4-5 days continuously. I know like me you are also frustrated with all those telemarketers calling you day and night and selling stuff in which you are not even remotely interested. But I have an idea to deal with this situation. I don’t know the feasibility to implement it. May or may not be possible.</p>
<p><span id="more-2318"></span>How about a service which lets you convert your normal mobile phone number to a premium call rate number. I mean I get to choose how much a person pays for a call whenever someone calls me. For example anyone calling me on my mobile would end up paying 100 Rs per minute. This way I would not be able to stop them calling me but I can ask them to call me up again and again and get them to spend money. I take revenge. And the amazing part is that you get paid a handsome amount of money at the end of the month. Because this is how premium call rate numbers work. The organization that owns these premium call rate numbers gets the share from the total revenue generated.</p>
<p><strong>Now let’s talk about the downsides of this idea</strong>. Suppose I setup this service on my mobile and one of my old friends gets hold of my number and calls me up. He would end up paying 100 bucks for the call. Well I have a solution for that. I ask my operator to warn the users who are calling me about the premium call rate. That way anyone calling me would think twice before calling me.</p>
<p><strong>But what about my friends, family and colleagues?</strong> Would they ever be able to call me on my cell phone?  Hmm.. I thought about that also actually. I got this idea from the recently held Apple Special Event, where Steve announced Ping. In Ping you get to choose who follow you. So basically, you get to choose a white list of numbers who would not be charged premium rates.</p>
<blockquote><p>How about your own premium number to fight spam?</p></blockquote>
<p>I know there are solutions like Block List which I used to use. But that is not universal to all phones. I think only on Nokia phones this functionality is available. And moreover the hassle of adding them in the list and keeping them updated. It’s not just worth it. And don’t forget about the limitation of number of phone numbers that you can add.</p>
<p>I need to think about some idea on Mobile Spam, the text messages because they seem to be bugging more than the phone calls.</p>
<p>Oh, one more thing. Did I tell you that well before even any mobile operator implemented this caller tune thing I had this idea in mind. I thought why not have something different than rather just that old boring Tring Tring. And to my surprise Indian Operators introduced Caller Tune to us.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Birth of Revolutioners.com</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/birth-of-revolutioners/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 07:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=184</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[outpowerhosting: ok.. ok.. gimme your domain name once again.. make sure it's spelt correctly Kuldeep: accha u suggest a good one outpowerhosting: 2 mins gone :D Kuldeep: I'll give u the background koi nahin bahut time hai tere paas outpowerhosting: k letshelpgovt.com? Kuldeep: I will be running a forum where people talk about their problems &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/birth-of-revolutioners/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Birth of Revolutioners.com</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>outpowerhosting: ok.. ok.. gimme your domain name once again.. make  sure it's spelt correctly
 
Kuldeep: accha u suggest a good one
 
outpowerhosting: 2 mins gone :D
 
Kuldeep: I'll give u the background
 koi nahin
 bahut time hai tere paas
 outpowerhosting: k
 letshelpgovt.com?
 
Kuldeep: I will be running a forum where people talk about their problems that they face in their day to day life
 and then people will suggest the soultion
 
outpowerhosting: helpme.com
 not available
 
Kuldeep: and may be ... may be . we can get some politicians or govt officials to look at those ideas and imprelemt them
 
outpowerhosting: hmmmm.. good thought
 
Kuldeep: accha everythng apart
 idea kaisa hai
 
outpowerhosting: helpmeindia.com
 
Kuldeep: ab to tujhe paise bhi mil gaye hai
 jhoot mat boolna
 outpowerhosting: lol..never lied
 
Kuldeep: accha cloremint khate ho
 
outpowerhosting: sometimes
 
Kuldeep: tabhi...
 accha think about domain name
 i gave u the idea
 it will not be limited to india
 
outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: for ur informaiton
 thats why i opted ,com domain
 outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: agar chali to i am thinking of a very large community
 outpowerhosting: but the domain you suggested had no relevance to the idea.. I first though it was about complaints to the govt and help them in some way

 Kuldeep: thats why i was asking you for more bandwidth
 haan
 outpowerhosting: we'll see.. as the site grows.. I'll help out with the needs
 
Kuldeep: first let govt know what is wrong
 and then people from community will give idea that what should govt do
 they'll discuss about that
 
outpowerhosting: don't' you think it's better to anchor it to one region..
 because it's too vast a subject to be a worldwide one
 
Kuldeep: well i am assuming not much people other than Asian continent will turn up in the forum
 so its kinda anchored in this region
 and moreover US UK govt doesn't need help
 
outpowerhosting: if i were to use the forum.. I should feel like.. ok.. I'm going to post my problem in some forum in which India is just one of the countries...

 Kuldeep: why
 
outpowerhosting: I should feel confident that someone is going to listen and that there are people who understand the situation

 Kuldeep: can u not talk about a problem in US
 
outpowerhosting: not that I'm just going to post and hope just hope that an Indian sees it
 
Kuldeep: well i can
 why
 yaar share your information

 outpowerhosting: kuldeep.. the idea is there.. but everyone doesn't think like you and me..
 
Kuldeep: lets see what others have to say
 
outpowerhosting: we have generalize it to suit the millions
 
Kuldeep: i mean a problem is in India
 right
 people from India to dekhenge hi
 
outpowerhosting: yeah.. i know..
 but like i said..
 
Kuldeep: par bahar wale aa kar suggestions denge tabhi to kucch accha sochnege
to govt ke badle kucch aur hona chahiye tu bol raha hai
 
outpowerhosting: like i said.. i shouldn't feel like I'm just one in the world.. it would feel much better if I'm one in India... besides.. who's stopping people from outside posting something in a forum related to India
 what i meant is
 it should be region specific
 or what you do is
 have the main domain
 and then create sub domain
 like india.helpthegovt.com
 and then on your main page
 list the countries
 which will lead to a forum
 
Kuldeep: Faizal see my motto is to get information ...inside information that you don't know from Bangladesh
 China
 Pakistan
 right
 India
 I can't be there all the time
 but people are there
 and if they post something only then I'll know about it na
 and then only i can suggest something
 
outpowerhosting: yes... the reason the information is inside and not public is because only people from that region know it.. and they wouldn't bother telling it to someone else.. if you give them the comfort that they are telling it to people of their same region.. they will feel much more confident to open up..
 do you understand what I'm saying?
 so.. let it be global.. but create sub domains that are region specific
 
Kuldeep: So u are saying people from Pakistan won't talk about their govt with Indian people
 creating sub domains will be hell lot of a work
 
outpowerhosting: not everyone will if they think their enemy is going to read it
 i know.. no pain.. no gain
 
Kuldeep: i mean moderating and managing

outpowerhosting: well.. if there are lot of people then.. obviously you can part that job with others..
 but till then I don't think it should be an issue

Kuldeep: but as of now i don't have anyone that's why i was thinking of having it in one
 
outpowerhosting: are.. people will come only when you open the forum
 ok..
 
Kuldeep: I am the only person

 outpowerhosting: then do one thing
 open and Indian sub domain as of now
 and a world region
 as more an more dome
 split it up
 
Kuldeep: and the domain
 what should it be

outpowerhosting: hmmm....
 helpmeworld.com
 lol
 
Kuldeep: don't think about India only
 u there
 i am on Gtalk now
 outpowerhosting: helpmeworld.com
 
Kuldeep: naah
 outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: who is me here
 
outpowerhosting: you want govt in it?
 
Kuldeep: check letshelptheworld
 outpowerhosting: the one who wants help
 letshelptheworld.com is there

 Kuldeep: what do u think about it
 
outpowerhosting: a bit lengthy

 Kuldeep: han yehi main soch raha tha
 
outpowerhosting: remove lets
 
Kuldeep: willhelp
 check this
 
outpowerhosting: what willhelp.com?
 doesn't make sense yaar
 
Kuldeep: india.willhelp.com

 outpowerhosting: doesn't make sense.. but if you want.. I'll check
 
Kuldeep: india.helptheworld.com
 
outpowerhosting: hmmm..
 so helptheworld.com?
 
Kuldeep: what do you say
 now just because i am wasting your time don't say yes

 outpowerhosting: it's not available

 Kuldeep: is it parked
 
outpowerhosting: i guess so
 
Kuldeep: how do we go about that
 
outpowerhosting: you'll have to pay a heavy sum if you need it
 depends on what the owner asks you for
 
Kuldeep: how much
 K
 leave leave
 think of something else
 i've given u the idea
 if we can eliminate help or govt
 or whatever
 
outpowerhosting: you don't want 'me' in it?
 
Kuldeep: yar i don't want to help me only. i want to help others as well
 
outpowerhosting: k

Kuldeep: so its not about me its about US
 
outpowerhosting: would it be appropriate to think in the lines of solution center?
 something like world solution center wsc.com or something?

Kuldeep: hmm
 sounds good

 outpowerhosting: so? then?

Kuldeep: but do u think wsc would make a good impact

 outpowerhosting: nope
 
Kuldeep: got the answer
 
outpowerhosting: but if you advertise it without the domain name.. then it will help..

 Kuldeep: lets make a difference
 
outpowerhosting: like if you advertise it as world solution center insteand of wsc.com.. it will help
 how would you suggest a domain name for that?
 
Kuldeep: that will be a bit long
 www.makeadifference.com

outpowerhosting: already there
 
Kuldeep: helpworld is not there as well

outpowerhosting: k now?
 
Kuldeep: i am asking ? is it?
 
outpowerhosting: nope.. not available

Kuldeep: u create account for hosting
 i'll tell u the domain name later

outpowerhosting: better to do with domain..
 
Kuldeep: why
 
outpowerhosting: name server issue.. coz if i create the account now.. and then register the domain.. the name server change sometimes might affect the account.. and in rare cases, edit or recreate the account.. but it should work most of the time
 
Kuldeep: world's problem solution
 
outpowerhosting: naaa
 
Kuldeep: center
 center theek nahin hai
 something else

outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: some historic word
 saveworld
 
outpowerhosting: naa.. you're not saving anyone.. only helping
 
Kuldeep: worldhelp
 check that
 worldforhelp
 
outpowerhosting: nope.. smarter guys already got it
 
Kuldeep: igottahelp
 ineedhelp
 
outpowerhosting: so.. now it's become all about I ? hahahhaha
 
Kuldeep: weneedhelp
 just giving example
 i am not buying it
 ha ha ha
 
outpowerhosting: k.. just kidding
 we need help already taken
 
Kuldeep: accha
 helpus
 
outpowerhosting: nope
 taken
 
Kuldeep: F1world
 yar going in other direction warna idea accha tha
 
outpowerhosting: F1?
 
Kuldeep: F1=help
 
outpowerhosting: why change?
 hahahahhaha
 do you think everyone's gonna click with that?
 
Kuldeep: letschangeworlf
 
outpowerhosting: it didn't click for an IT admin.. then how come it will click for normal guys?
 
Kuldeep: hmm
 Edit world
 how is this
 
outpowerhosting: now you wannna become wolf? hahahhaha
 
Kuldeep: edit bole to change
 if change is not available
 
outpowerhosting: letschangeworld.com available
 
Kuldeep: the missing
 
outpowerhosting: yeah
 
Kuldeep: but then very lengthy
 
outpowerhosting: add d
 
Kuldeep: nope
 wonb't suit
 am i wasting your time
 
outpowerhosting: naa
 tell me
 
Kuldeep: you are with me na
 
outpowerhosting: yeah

 Kuldeep: synonyms of change
 
outpowerhosting: google :p
 addition , adjustment , advance , break , compression , contraction , conversion , correction , development , difference , distortion , diversification , diversity , enlargement , innovation , metamorphosis , modification , modulation , mutation , novelty , permutation , reconstruction , refinement , remodeling , reversal , revision , revolution , shift , surrogate , switch , tempering , transformation , transition , transmutation , turn , turnover , variance , variation , variety , vicissitude, enlargement
 hahahhahahahha
 
Kuldeep: revolutioners
 check this
 
outpowerhosting: revolutioners.com
 available
 
Kuldeep: agar hai to kar de
 haan kar de
 spelling check kar leoutpowerhosting: are you sure?
 
Kuldeep: are you ?
 
outpowerhosting: seems ok. but not sure if there is a thing in mind that we're going to change when we mean revolution
 coz we revolt against something in existence..
 
Kuldeep: hmmm
 ya so there is something that we want to change and revolt from that
 
outpowerhosting: k..
 
Kuldeep: or evolve
 i had thought of rangdebasanti
 par mila nahin
 for india only
 
outpowerhosting: rangdebasanti?
 what has that got to do with anything?

Kuldeep: are movie nahin dekhi tune
 
outpowerhosting: nope.
 
Kuldeep: kya
 rangdebasanti nahin dekhi
 
outpowerhosting: never got time :p
 
Kuldeep: accha
 phir kya kara
 english dekhi
 koi
 
outpowerhosting: didn't see any recent movies
 
Kuldeep: i saw cloverfield and jumper
 good quality cam rip

outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: http://india.revolutioners.com/
 kaisa lag raha hai
 
outpowerhosting: seems good
 
Kuldeep: ya http://india.letschangetheworld.com/
 
outpowerhosting: which one?
 
Kuldeep: are yar u seem to be in rush
 i am asking u
 
outpowerhosting: no
 letschangetheworld.com and http://india.letschangetheworld.com/ is not available
 
Kuldeep: maine bola hai k agar time nahin hai to main kal kara lunga yar
 not a problem
 
outpowerhosting: no.. I'm right here
 going no where
 
Kuldeep: are u home
 
outpowerhosting: s bolo that na.. leave pe hoon to ghar me hoon

Kuldeep: dekha mujhe pata hi tha k itna accha idea kaun chod dega
 
outpowerhosting: lol
 
Kuldeep: yeh bhi parked hai yar

outpowerhosting: i guess

Kuldeep: haan chal phir 1 hi option bacha revolutioners.com ya yeh theek nahin hai
 
outpowerhosting: are you sure? lock karun?
 
Kuldeep: world laga le uske pehle worldrevolution.com
 
outpowerhosting: lemme check
 
Kuldeep: hai shayad
 
outpowerhosting: nope taken
 
Kuldeep: it says available
 
outpowerhosting: where?
 
Kuldeep: domainsearch.com
 
outpowerhosting: no yaar
 I'll check again.. check your spelling
 
Kuldeep: let me check somewhere else
 
outpowerhosting: nope

Kuldeep: haan
 nahin hai
 govt ko beech main lana is not good waise
 people will think k kucch nahin ho sakta
 ha na
 
outpowerhosting: yeah
 
Kuldeep: accha chal revolutioners.com
 register kar de
 agar kuccch aur idea aayega to aur kara lenge
 theek hai
 
outpowerhosting: okie
 
Kuldeep: now i am going out for sutta and shave
 
outpowerhosting: k.. so <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/">revolutioners.com</a>?
 
Kuldeep: i'll come back in 30 mins or so
 
outpowerhosting: check spelling
 
Kuldeep: haan bhai theek hai
 
outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: tujhe mujhse jyada hi pata hoga
 
outpowerhosting: lol
 
Kuldeep: registrar ko kya information dega
 
Kuldeep: fake ki real
 
outpowerhosting: jo tumne mujhe diya that.. .but three is privacy protection.. your whois info will be hidden
 
Kuldeep: good
 accha how is this
 letseditworld

 outpowerhosting: edit?
 
Kuldeep: haan bole to change
 ;)
 
outpowerhosting: na.. it sounds geeky.. not for average person
 
Kuldeep: chal see ya then
 be online
 
outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: stick with revolutioners

 outpowerhosting: k

Kuldeep: .com
 ok
 
outpowerhosting: yeah.. doing now
 
Kuldeep: be online
 
outpowerhosting: will be
 
Kuldeep: i'll be back in 30 mins
 bye
 
outpowerhosting: k
 bye

 Kuldeep: if u r going offline then mail the details to me
 ok
 outpowerhosting: k
 
Kuldeep: bye
 any contact no u have
 
outpowerhosting: only personal no. as of now.. will get another one within a week. ... will give then
 
Kuldeep: i thought by now you'd give me ur personal no as well.
 anyways
 thanks
 bye
 
<a href="http://outpowerhosting.com/">outpowerhosting</a>: bye</pre>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
