<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>issues &#8211; rLOVEutioners</title>
	<atom:link href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tag/issues/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/</link>
	<description>revoution for evolution</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 13:59:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Issues India needs to sort out in next 10 years to really be a SuperPower</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 12:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=23&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=23</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are many things that Indian Government needs to fix but these are some of them which I feel will make or break our country’s future in the coming years. Inflation: With the most of India’s vast population living close to or below the poverty line, inflation acts as a ‘Poor Man’s Tax’. This effect &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Issues India needs to sort out in next 10 years to really be a SuperPower</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are many things that Indian Government needs to fix but these are some of them which I feel will make or break our country’s future in the coming years.</p>
<p><strong>Inflation</strong>: With the most of India’s vast population living close to or below the poverty line, inflation acts as a ‘Poor Man’s Tax’. This effect is amplified when food prices rise, since food represents more than half of the expenditure of this group.</p>
<p><strong>Terrorism</strong> &#8211; I know it should have been on the top of the list however I chose it to be on the 2nd place because people are any which ways dying due to not being able to feed themselves because of the rise in price of the consumable commodities.We spend a huge amount of money on defense but where is the defense. We have been preparing for WW III for I don’t know how long. And in that process we have forgotten to spend money in the right direction.</p>
<p><strong>Unemployment</strong> – Not a big deal in the rural areas but a huge concern for the people living in the urban areas. It seems to have deteriorated in the past 1 year but we need to go miles from here. We are no where near what a developed country should be. Unemployment rate as of now is around 10%</p>
<p><strong>Infrastructure</strong> – We need around 100 CWG games organized in our country for the infrastructure to improve. After writing the last sentence, I pondered over it for a couple of seconds and this funny thought occurred to me that we would have 100 more corrupt events and millions of rupees will go into our politicians’ pockets again.</p>
<p><strong>Indo-Pak Relation</strong>: To be absolutely frank, we have to take a stand if we really want to solve this problem. It may not be a problem for the neighboring country but it is affecting us as a country, a lot. We have enough army to defeat a country like Pakistan. At the least give the opponent something to think about before they try or think about doing something which brings disgrace to our country. We keep sitting idle and wait for their response all the time after someone takes responsibility to attack India.</p>
<p><strong>Indian Constitution</strong>: I feel the root of all the problems is our constitution. Written over 60 years ago. Things are bound to change. We are still living in the same 60 year old world. We were a developing country then and are still a developing country. There hasn&#8217;t been any change, moreover our politicians and constitution has brought nothing but misery to our country.</p>
<p><strong>Uneducated Politicians</strong>: We are living in a country where an uneducated/illiterate (politically) person can enter the world of politics. We are living in a state of spiritual disbelief of which our politicians are taking undue advantage. We need to get out of this situation, and pretty fast. But the concern is who will bell the cat. These people are strong and powerful because of their unlawful deeds and its hard to reverse the effects for good.</p>
<p><strong>Division of States</strong>: If we can divide the states then it’s imminent that we would have around 30 countries within India in the next 10 years. Dividing states further was the first weakness shown by a weak leader of our country. People will demand unethical things, it does not mean you mess up with the idea of peace and forget what you are supposed to do.</p>
<p><strong>Communal Riots</strong>: We are the world’s second largest standing army in the world. It definitely means something. But a bunch of people take over a state. Terrorize it. I am not convinced with the fact that a million armed forces can’t take down these Naxalites or any other Maoist groups. We declared them as terrorist groups but we can’t fight them. Over 30% of Indian states are affected by these groups in one way or the other.</p>
<p><strong>Education</strong>: 40% of world’s illiterate population is from India. Nothing much to say about this one.</p>
<p>These are my thoughts. There are so many good things to point out. And the web is flooded with information like that but till the time we don’t highlight the bad it won’t turn into good. That’s my theory. We can’t make something right till the time we don’t believe that there is something wrong.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/top-10-indian-issues-of-present-india/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I see a Policeman on motorbike without a Helmet, I stop him and hand him over a ticket</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 13:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=43</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[How cool will that be ? I mean I was just wondering for quite some time now that how nice it would be if we could really take control of our law enforcement. Imagine while roaming on the road you see someone breaking the law and you take out your camera, take a picture while &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">I see a Policeman on motorbike without a Helmet, I stop him and hand him over a ticket</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How cool will that be ? I mean I was just wondering for quite some time now that how nice it would be if we could really take control of our law enforcement. Imagine while roaming on the road you see someone breaking the law and you take out your camera, take a picture while he is breaking the traffic rules. Catch hold of him. Show him the picture and hand over the ticket to him. I mean imagine the force we would have on roads and people will think twice before doing anything wrong.</p>
<p>People may use the power for wrong doing but I think we can start with some intelligent and responsible people like Bus Conductor, Shopkeepers who are sitting on a road watching it all the time. A Pan wallah on the Traffic Signal.</p>
<p>I am thinking of creating another website where I urge people to submit such pictures where people are captured while breaking the law. And our law enforcement team has to just identify the person and fine him/her.</p>
<p>Think about it. Bye !</p>
<p>Let me know your thoughts by posting your comments.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Does Wikipedia really need money?</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-does-wikipedia-need-money/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-does-wikipedia-need-money/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 18:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=70</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I guess I am not the only one who feels the same way. I was just going through the Wikipedia Financial today on their page. What I saw there made me look into this matter in much greater detail. Wikimedia spent almost $3500, 000 in recruiting and wages in the financial year 2009-2010. And it &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-does-wikipedia-need-money/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Does Wikipedia really need money?</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I guess I am not the only one who feels the same way. I was just going through the Wikipedia Financial today on <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323132239/http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/foundation/d/dd/2010-11_Wikimedia_Foundation_Annual_Plan_FINAL_FOR_WEBSITE.pdf">their page</a>. What I saw there made me look into this matter in much greater detail. Wikimedia spent almost $3500, 000 in recruiting and wages in the financial year 2009-2010. And it grew to almost $6000, 000 in the financial year 2010-2011. I was just wondering isn’t that too much for <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323132239/http://strategy.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Foundation_employees.png">50 employees of Wikimedia</a>. I am now confused as in what is actually a non-profit organization. I mean apart from running your websites do you also need money to run the show? Posting a conversation excerpt that I found in a forum.</p>
<p><img src="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323132239im_/http://img220.imageshack.us/img220/6794/wikipediax.jpg" alt="" width="600" /></p>
<blockquote><p>This is why I have lost faith in humanity, because too many people believe what is told to them and would rather believe in the “make me feel safe, secure, and okay” state of mind rather than face reality. It is a reality that non-profit and profit organizations use fraud to gain extra bucks. This is not conspiracy theories as it is even reported in mainstream media. You would have to be either very naive or not informed of what is going on in the world not to realize this.</p>
<p>Look at the last decade during the many world disasters, the mainstream news media always reported on scams/misuse of funds/missing funds for donations drives for:</p>
<ul>
<li>9/11 Victim families</li>
<li>Tsunami relief 2004</li>
<li>Haiti earthquake relief and many others.</li>
</ul>
<p>Just watch/read the news the next time another major disaster happens and donation drives start up, and you will see it shows up. Now, having said all this, I never said that no one should not donate to Wikipedia. I consider Wikipeidia one of the most important acomplishements of human effort for this decade and maybe even farther back because its primary cause is to spread information, something I believe strongly in.</p>
<p>And that is exactly why I mention that donation drives are not 100% innocent just because they have the “non-profit” tag on them. Those that still refuse to believe this reality attempt to counter with “but they report what they use the money for!” And then further counter by saying you have no evidence in return to go against it.</p>
<p>However evidence does exist in the form of history of scams/fraud in past donation drives for various causes. Also, the excuse of saying they report use is very naive as it *assumes* that those reporting are not involved or prone to fraud or are 100% honest. Even in the face of history proving that people can’t be trusted, which is way laws, courts, and oversight organizations exist (which I will also add are also not immune to being corrupt [as proven by history]).</p>
<p>Beyond failing to observe or forgetting history, I believe most people don’t realize this because they have never been in a “controller” position without oversight, in which human bias and nature is unchecked. This is why in science, double-blind experiments are use to remove bias. However, in the controller position without oversight, this is not removed. If you study literature, this topic (i.e. Lord of the Flies) has been covered many times throughout history as well, even up until now and in films.</p>
<p>Again, I just want to say I support Wikipedia because I so strongly believe in the spreading of information, and by that believe I attempt to spread a little, perhaps unpleasant piece of information as well. Which instead of being pushed under the plate should be swallowed whole, even if it tastes bad and unsettles your bowels. Even still you should make it part of you, move on, and seek out more information.</p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-does-wikipedia-need-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>India China comparison – An eye opener</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/india-china-economic-agricultural-industrial-education-comparison-world-bank/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/india-china-economic-agricultural-industrial-education-comparison-world-bank/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 18:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=83</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Below is a really nice comparison of India and China. Where we stand in terms of population, income, industry and many other. China started their family planning policy in 1970, India in 1952 In 2001 our birth rate was nearly 3 times more than China. 27 births per 1000 as against 8.8 for China! India &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/india-china-economic-agricultural-industrial-education-comparison-world-bank/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">India China comparison – An eye opener</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Below is a really nice comparison of India and China. Where we stand in terms of population, income, industry and many other.</p>
<p><strong>China started their family planning policy in 1970, India in 1952</strong></p>
<p>In 2001 our birth rate was nearly 3 times more than China. 27 births per 1000 as against 8.8 for China! India is adding 18 million people per year, against 9 million per year in China. Total addition to population is a function of total births minus total deaths.</p>
<p><strong>India’s per capita earning is US$440 per year against US$990 per year in China</strong></p>
<p>As per the World Bank, the poverty line definition is US$1 per person per day or US$365/person/year, for underdeveloped countries like India, China etc. As per the official data from both governments, China has 3% population below the poverty line, compared to India’s 26 to 29%! Only better governance can help.</p>
<p><strong>China attracts 87 million tourists per year (this is expected to reach 90 million in 2002) against 2.5 million per year to India.</strong></p>
<p>The international Tourism Industry is [7 times the size of I.T. or software] about, US$3700 billion per year. India, in spite of its old history and 21 cultures and languages, seems to have ‘missed the bus’, in Tourism. Tourism is a very big employment generator. It is estimated that every one tourist generates 2 to 4 jobs. Tourism promotes International trade and understanding.<br />
<strong>How will we provide additional 10 million jobs per year?</strong></p>
<p>The Public Sector and State/Central Government, which is already overstaffed, has a total of 18.7 million employees, therefore offers very little scope for new employment. We have to look outside the government for new employment. The unorganized sector and the SME’s (SSI is not SME) offer the maximum scope for employment, like in all other countries of the world, including China. SME’s account for nearly 75% of employment and 80% of trainees!</p>
<p><strong>The Government can only facilitate jobs; they cannot provide jobs for the 300 million partly or fully unemployed in India!</strong></p>
<p>At 10 million jobs per year it will take us 30 years to remove unemployment, at 5 million jobs for year it will take us 60 years! The present Indian ‘mind set’ will require rethinking and reorganization of the existing perceptions about Public Sector enterprises, and the actual role they are supposed to play! Only efficient organizations can deliver results and growth. Only better governance and efficient administration can deliver results!</p>
<p><strong>In Foreign Direct investment, FDI, China + Hong Kong received US$106 billion last year [US$70billion from NRC&#8217;s] vs US$3.6 billion [US$0.2b from NRI&#8217;s] for India! Only better Governance can attract FDI and Tourists. In exports, China is nearly +700% of India</strong></p>
<p>Taking the exports of Hong Kong + Macau into account, China’s exports would be +1000% of India! China’s GDP is 50% in manufacturing or $ 650 billion per year. India’s GDP is 25% in manufacturing or $110 billion per year. China’s manufacturing base is nearly 6 times of India’s.</p>
<p><span id="more-2946"></span><br />
<strong>In agriculture our yields per acre, are well below the international norms.</strong></p>
<p>India could be a giant exporter of food, only if we could put our ‘house in order’ to near world class standards! China with lesser cultivable land, produces double the food grains, at 415 million tons per year compared with India’s 208 million tons per year. God has been very kind to India with a lot of sunshine, rain, rivers, lakes, coastline and good hard working citizens.<br />
The governance of hamlets, villages, cities, districts, Government and Semi-Government agencies, as facilitators, have not done enough to show the results that India is able or capable of achieving. India would definitely rate as the No.1 country in the world, for Potential vs Performance!<br />
Indians score high marks on performance, outside India! This is because the Governance is better outside. In countries where the Governance &amp; Administration is poor, the performance of its citizens is also low!</p>
<p><strong>In Education, 99.1% of Chinese children attend school for 9 years, this ensures a high level of literacy. In India, literacy is 50 to 60%</strong></p>
<p>While IIT’s, IIM’s are important, the country’s real growth will come because of primary and secondary education and vocational and educational training in all districts of the country. India can rise and shine in exports, agriculture, literacy and other areas with better governance.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/india-china-economic-agricultural-industrial-education-comparison-world-bank/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indian Government asking Social Networks and Google to censor political parties and politicians. But why?</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/indian-government-ranks-3rd-in-terms-of-reteriving-data-from-google/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/indian-government-ranks-3rd-in-terms-of-reteriving-data-from-google/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 18:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=75</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Recently read a news about US government asking Google to provide lots and lots of data related which is related to the services Google provides. I am sure they must be utilizing this data for get to the corrupts. And then automatically me being a typical Indian wanted to check our country’s  rank in that &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/indian-government-ranks-3rd-in-terms-of-reteriving-data-from-google/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Indian Government asking Social Networks and Google to censor political parties and politicians. But why?</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently read a news about US government asking Google to provide lots and lots of data related which is related to the services Google provides. I am sure they must be utilizing this data for get to the corrupts. And then automatically me being a typical Indian wanted to check our country’s  rank in that list. To my surprise we rank 3rd in that list after US and Brazil. Wow.. It feels great to be in a such a list. Well that’s one side of the story I was thinking. But after reading the data requests that Google received I started thinking about what would our government departments have actually asked for. Checkout for analysis after the break.</p>
<p><span id="more-2453"></span><br />
<img loading="lazy" class="alignnone" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932im_/http://img201.imageshack.us/img201/1192/indiangovernmentgoogled.png" alt="" width="600" height="321" /><br />
<strong>About Google Transparency</strong> : Its an interactive map of Government Requests that shows the number of government inquiries for information about users and requests for Google to take down or censor content. The interactive Traffic graphs provide information about traffic to Google services around the world. Each graph shows historic traffic patterns for a given country/region and service. By illustrating outages, this tool visualizes disruptions in the free flow of information, whether it’s a government blocking information or a cable being cut.</p>
<p>Below is the graph that shows the requests from Indian Government agencies to Google in the past 1 year.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932im_/http://img52.imageshack.us/img52/6910/searchpatterngoogletran.png" alt="" width="600" height="177" /></p>
<p>I’ll leave you guys with that thought because I need to go to bed now. OK, still let me give you some perspective. Have you ever looked at <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932/http://www.revolutioners.com/where-the-hell-are-indian-web-developers/">our government websites</a>. I have talked about it earlier as well. But I think the more we are so called developing the more our government is showcase that they are technically sound. I mean I am not talking about the politicians. We bloody pay some great amount of money in taxes can’t we hire some sound technical guys to handle these stuffs. Alright I think I am deviating from the topic.</p>
<p>OK, I was suppose to give you some perspective. Alright, I was just looking at my blog and saw an advertisement on my blog via adsense that I have setup. I did not click on the ad but copied the link to the URL. You believe me it was <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932/http://www.delhitrafficpolice.nic.in/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Delhi Traffic Police</a> Delhi Traffic Police is advertising via Google Adwords. Anyways, then in curiosity I went to check out the website. Our government needs to accept the fact that their developers su*k.  So there were some nice presentations regarding common wealth games. I could not believe my eyes by looking at the presentation. I mean such a big country and not even one single fucking person in India who can make a good looking presentation. You don’t believe me check <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104932/http://www.delhitrafficpolice.nic.in/cwg1.ppt" target="_blank" rel="noopener">this out</a>. And yeah I was in an impression since it being a website where the whole world would be browsing to look for updated information but then I saw a link to download flash player which still links to Macromedia site. Thanks to Adobe that they have redirected it to the right place.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/indian-government-ranks-3rd-in-terms-of-reteriving-data-from-google/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How about telemarketers get charged 1000 rs for calling you</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 19:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=95</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Every now and then my mind keeps flooding with some insane ideas. But after some time when I think about it, it all starts making some sense. I was on my way to office 2-3 days ago and I get a call from someone trying to sell me some Life Insurance. This guy has been &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">How about telemarketers get charged 1000 rs for calling you</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every now and then my mind keeps flooding with some insane ideas. But after some time when I think about it, it all starts making some sense. I was on my way to office 2-3 days ago and I get a call from someone trying to sell me some Life Insurance. This guy has been calling me for i don’t know may be for the last 4-5 days continuously. I know like me you are also frustrated with all those telemarketers calling you day and night and selling stuff in which you are not even remotely interested. But I have an idea to deal with this situation. I don’t know the feasibility to implement it. May or may not be possible.</p>
<p><span id="more-2318"></span>How about a service which lets you convert your normal mobile phone number to a premium call rate number. I mean I get to choose how much a person pays for a call whenever someone calls me. For example anyone calling me on my mobile would end up paying 100 Rs per minute. This way I would not be able to stop them calling me but I can ask them to call me up again and again and get them to spend money. I take revenge. And the amazing part is that you get paid a handsome amount of money at the end of the month. Because this is how premium call rate numbers work. The organization that owns these premium call rate numbers gets the share from the total revenue generated.</p>
<p><strong>Now let’s talk about the downsides of this idea</strong>. Suppose I setup this service on my mobile and one of my old friends gets hold of my number and calls me up. He would end up paying 100 bucks for the call. Well I have a solution for that. I ask my operator to warn the users who are calling me about the premium call rate. That way anyone calling me would think twice before calling me.</p>
<p><strong>But what about my friends, family and colleagues?</strong> Would they ever be able to call me on my cell phone?  Hmm.. I thought about that also actually. I got this idea from the recently held Apple Special Event, where Steve announced Ping. In Ping you get to choose who follow you. So basically, you get to choose a white list of numbers who would not be charged premium rates.</p>
<blockquote><p>How about your own premium number to fight spam?</p></blockquote>
<p>I know there are solutions like Block List which I used to use. But that is not universal to all phones. I think only on Nokia phones this functionality is available. And moreover the hassle of adding them in the list and keeping them updated. It’s not just worth it. And don’t forget about the limitation of number of phone numbers that you can add.</p>
<p>I need to think about some idea on Mobile Spam, the text messages because they seem to be bugging more than the phone calls.</p>
<p>Oh, one more thing. Did I tell you that well before even any mobile operator implemented this caller tune thing I had this idea in mind. I thought why not have something different than rather just that old boring Tring Tring. And to my surprise Indian Operators introduced Caller Tune to us.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What if there was nothing immoral</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/lets-for-once-assume-that-there-is-nothing-bad-or-wrong-in-this-world/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/lets-for-once-assume-that-there-is-nothing-bad-or-wrong-in-this-world/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 13:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Well lets just once assume in this world. I mean let the person kill someone if he wants to. Let a person rob someone if he wishes to. Let anyone become a suicide bomber or a terrorist if he/she wants to do it under someone’s influence. What a world would that be. It would be &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/lets-for-once-assume-that-there-is-nothing-bad-or-wrong-in-this-world/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">What if there was nothing immoral</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Well lets just once assume in this world. I mean let the person kill someone if he wants to. Let a person rob someone if he wishes to. Let anyone become a suicide bomber or a terrorist if he/she wants to do it under someone’s influence. What a world would that be. It would be horrific, right. No, It would not be horrible, It would be great because the way I look at it is that if we use the technology to an extent where all these bad activities would not even be remotely possible. I would want to live in a world like that.<br />
<span id="more-1670"></span></p>
<p>I wish technology advances so much that it does not leave any chance of error for humans. For example</p>
<ul>
<li>People could freely shop online and never be afraid of their bank details being leaked and hacked.</li>
<li>I want the examination system to be like that it does not let anyone cheat.</li>
<li>A world where if a crime is committed the culprit can never escape and gets the punishment instantly.</li>
<li>A world where piracy will not be illegal. It will be legal because it would be upto the publishers to protect their creations/products/music/movies etc. And because the technology would be so strong that it does not even leave a chance for anyone to pirate.</li>
<li>Where Microsoft does not have to be afraid over WGA cracks anymore because they know that their activation process is so amazing that no one can make copies.</li>
</ul>
<p>What do you think about it ? Do you wanna live into that kind of world. Where you have all the freedom to do anything in this world and no one would complain about that.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/lets-for-once-assume-that-there-is-nothing-bad-or-wrong-in-this-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to help your Government host a successful event of any kind</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/commonwealth-games-2010-things-you-can-do-to-contribute-for-a-successful-event/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/commonwealth-games-2010-things-you-can-do-to-contribute-for-a-successful-event/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2009 19:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=98</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Alright, I think its the time that I talk about the burning issue of Commonwealth Games supposed to be held in Delhi, India. I think we are trying our best to keep them here but somehow I am getting this feeling that we are not ready. Our government has not even started the construction of &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/commonwealth-games-2010-things-you-can-do-to-contribute-for-a-successful-event/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">How to help your Government host a successful event of any kind</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Alright, I think its the time that I talk about the burning issue of Commonwealth Games supposed to be held in Delhi, India. I think we are trying our best to keep them here but somehow I am getting this feeling that we are not ready. Our government has not even started the construction of some of the stadiums. We I really wish our Indian Government best of luck. May God bless them with some wisdom. Why do these guys not understand that it will be less shameful if we tell the Commonwealth Games community that we are not ready to host the event rather then the athletes coming to India and coming to know that we are not even able to provide the basic facilities to them. Forget about organizing the Commonwealth Games 2010.</p>
<p>Anyways, If I assume it happens and we have all the stadiums ready to organize the games. Though our government has to do a really good job here to crack this nut. What if the people of India are not ready. We are overlooking this part. We have not even considered this factor yet. There will be a huge number of foreigners coming to Delhi and Indian tourism will get a drastic boost during September till December 2010.</p>
<p>I feel there are certain things that we need to take are as Indian citizens. People who are coming from other countries will not be familiar with our countries, so we will have to make sure we help them as much as we can. China was ready for Olympics a year ago from the actual event and we are running late.</p>
<p>Today I am just asking to you remember these 10 things which if done properly would definitely make our country better in terms of hospitality and people coming from other countries will also look at as developing country not under developed.</p>
<p><strong>Give Shelter</strong> : As per Indian Government, Delhi is going to be short of accommodation for at least 6,000 tourists coming to Delhi. I urge every Delhite to make sure if you know someone who is coming to see Commonwealth Games then ask them to stay with you at your house if possible. Otherwise it will really be shameful to not to have space to stay for them.</p>
<p><strong>Have some Generosity</strong> : You might have seen it already when people come from the western side of the world in India they are being overcharged by Indian people. To a certain limit its acceptable. But when people coming at this large scale I don’t think it will be required to do that. So I would urge you all Indians to not to promote such things. If you see some auto rickshaw or taxi driver or any shopkeeper overcharging the foreigners, please go help them.</p>
<p><strong>Keep your city Clean</strong> : Don’t just pee and spit anywhere, I know many of you are reading this would not come under that category, but just think about it. Our government has spent millions in creating places for emergencies like these. I wish we had a rule for penalizing anyone who is found to be spitting on road. And anyone not following it would be charged 500 Rs on the spot. And mainly those Gukta guys, I just can’t explain it. So, guys please mind your tongue for 2 months at least.</p>
<p><strong>Learn to behave</strong> : We by nature are very generous and hospitable, but only for Indians and our brothers. We need to show this hospitality to everyone who is coming to our country. This is the only way we can show our hospitality to the world and people who would come and visit our mother land. Remember<strong> ” Athiti Devo Bhava”</strong> There might be people who are coming to India for the first time and would expect everything to go right.</p>
<p><strong>Help National Security</strong> : We saw terrorist attacks in Mumbai and Delhi this year and last year as well. Mumbai Blasts, Delhi Blasts etc. I am not sure what our government has learnt from it. But I want you to help avoid these kind of mishaps. Help our Security professionals to keep our country safe. I would request you all to report anything you suspect.</p>
<p><strong>Follow traffic rules</strong> : <em>Better late then never</em>, what is this. I don’t understand. Who is <em>late</em>, what is never. I don’t know. All I know is I am getting late and if the traffic signal is not working then I am not going to wait. Please, don’t don’t do this. Don’t show that we don’t have traffic manners. Indians need to understand that traffic rules are not meant to be broken only, then are suppose to be followed as well. Its OK if you wait for 2 minutes and let other pass. If you notice, in hurry you spend 15 minutes standing on the signal because you stuck everybody on the signal. Don’t <a href="http://www.revolutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/">drive rash</a> on roads during the games.</p>
<p><strong>Respect their cultures</strong> : We might see people coming from various countries and cultures. We need to learn to respect their cultures. Their way of living will be different. In western culture display of public affection is not bad but in our culture its not suppose to be a good thing. We need to come out of this conservative ideology and start behaving like a developed country. If we need to be a Developed Country.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/commonwealth-games-2010-things-you-can-do-to-contribute-for-a-successful-event/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Learn to Drive rash on Indian Roads</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2009 19:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What is this all about ? What the crap ? What the hell is wrong with Kuldeep ? Why is he writing on such a pathetic topic? While your mind is flooded with all these kinds of questions, there goes one more. Ever wondered how any people die just because of rash driving. I know &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Learn to Drive rash on Indian Roads</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What is this all about ? What the crap ? What the hell is wrong with Kuldeep ? Why is he writing on such a pathetic topic? While your mind is flooded with all these kinds of questions, there goes one more. Ever wondered how any people die just because of rash driving. I know what you are thinking now. Alright let me tell you.l I did some digging on this. We are number 1 yey ! According to World Road Statistic data 2007 around 1 million people died in road accident. Now what do you think how many of those 1 million people would have died because of their own mistakes. I would say not more than 50%. So how did the rest of the half a million people die in road accidents. The answer is they all died because some jackass was driving rash.</p>
<p>I also drive rash, But I drive with safety and that too when its required and most of all with intelligence. Yeah, I know what you are thinking. But believe me I don’t act like a school kid who has been just handed over the keys of the car or bike. I have been driving car and riding bikes for the last 8-9 years now. And you know what I am from the most crowded part of India. I am from Delhi. I think anyone who has driven safely on Delhi roads can drive anywhere in the world.  Let me get to the point now because I guess I would have to dedicate a whole new blog to just write about Indian Traffic Rules and Regulations. Its really pathetic how Indian people don’t even think about the traffic rules. And the funny part is the same people who jump traffic signals and break traffic rules, if they go in a different country follow every damn traffic rules. Ever thought why is that the case? Well let me tell you. Its because of our government servants.When we go in a different country we know if we break any traffic rules, the penalty will be so Hugh that they would have to rip their asses off to pay the ticket money. On the other hand in India its mere 100 bucks and that too if you don’t have any policemen in distant relation. But don’t worry if you don’t have any policemen in relation you can just bribe these guys. Just slip a 50 Rs note and you are free.</p>
<p>Alright lets get to the point now. Here are some tips to drive rash on Indian Roads. Believe me they are tried and tested and learnt after 8-9 years of experience.</p>
<h3><strong>Always Drive on left side of the road</strong></h3>
<p>Whenever I have to drive fast, I always drive on the left side of the road. Specially at a crossing. I have met with 2-3 accidents on my bike while I was on the right hand side of the road. The problem is when you are driving on the right hand side you can’t see what is coming from the front because your view is blocked by the railing. <em>And we being Indians we don’t stop/slow down on intersections</em>. Trust me most of the accidents on the road happen because of this reason only. You can’t see what is coming from the right hand side but by the time you realize it, its too late.  But at the same time if you are driving on the left side of the road you have a really good time and view to see if someone is coming from front or right hand side of the road. I have tested it and it really works. I have escaped/saved a lot of accidents this way. So the solution is start driving on the left side while crossing an intersection. I think those railings should be removed from the divider at an intersection for at least around 100 meters so that someone coming on the road can look at both sides of the road if someone is coming or not.</p>
<h3><span class="removed_link" title="http://www.revolutioners.com/commonwealth-games-2010-things-you-can-do-to-contribute-for-a-successful-event/"><strong>Always follow Traffic rules</strong></span></h3>
<p>Indians have just re-engineered the whole traffic signal system. <strong>For us Red means if there is place don’t stop and go on. Yellow is, speed up its going to turn red. Green is, it will turn red hurry up, honk honk and honk.</strong> Damn this is funny. OK. Now this is one of the smartest tips if you ask me. Now you would be thinking how can it be a tip for driving rash. Well the thing is you can drive rash without breaking the rules as well. I mean drive fast, but don’t jump red lights, don’t change lane too often, don’t jump in front of someone like an idiot, don’t keep honking. You know I only drive fast and so called rash when its really required. There is no such pleasure then driving/riding slow. So drive fast/rash until and unless there is a need to it.</p>
<h3><strong>Always look through</strong></h3>
<p>How many times it happened that you were driving really nice and suddenly the person in front of you just stood on the break and your car went creening on the road and you managed to stop the car just an inch away from the car in front of you. It has happened right. So the thing is, if you are driving make sure you are not just watching the car in front of you. Look through the car in front of you. If you see that driver driving madly and stopping suddenly because of xyz reason you have a good amount of time.</p>
<p>I usually not look at the car just in front of me. I watch right into the rear and front mirror and look at the car next to the car in front of me. This way, I keep an eye on the car in front and concentrate on the car that is running in front of the car I am driving behind.</p>
<h3><strong>Don’t play it loud</strong></h3>
<p>Well I am sure people who drive rash they have a nice music system in their cars. When you drive rash and the music is loud you can’t hear anyone honking from the back and then you suddenly try to change the lane. This gets dangerous when that vehicle is two wheeler. So stay put, don’t drive out loud.</p>
<h3><strong>Don’t drink and drive</strong></h3>
<p>Here is the thing. You are drunk and you’ve got friends who are also drunk. Get a drunkard’s cab. Yeah they are in business now. Now what, you show off. You show them how well you can drive. In that madness you drive here and there and that’s it. That is the beginning of the end of your life. Don’t drink and drive. I am speaking from my personal experience.</p>
<p><strong>Share it if you would like to save someone’s life.</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to stop killing animals in road accidents</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-can-we-stop-the-killing-of-animals-on-streets/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-can-we-stop-the-killing-of-animals-on-streets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2009 09:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=162</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed it. You take out your vehicle and start your journey to your usualy daily destination. But suddenly you see a dead street dog on the road. The dog was over ran by some vehicle. I don’t know about you guys, but I get very disappointed and feel bad about it. I &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-can-we-stop-the-killing-of-animals-on-streets/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">How to stop killing animals in road accidents</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever noticed it. You take out your vehicle and start your journey to your usualy daily destination. But suddenly you see a dead street dog on the road. The dog was over ran by some vehicle. I don’t know about you guys, but I get very disappointed and feel bad about it.</p>
<p>I decided to write about it today because I saw one dead dog on the road while coming back from office.</p>
<p>I have seen this a lot of times. Some times really nice dogs are found dead. I am a dog lover. I adore them a lot. It does not matter whether its a street dog or a pet dog.</p>
<p>On this, I am asking your suggestion. How can we reduce these kind of incidents. As of now our government has failed to do anything on this. It takes atleast 2-3 days to clean up that dead body from the road. This is how our Muncipality department works.</p>
<p>Now let me talk more about our non profit organizations. I am not in touch with any of them so I don’t know how well they operate. But I feel except 10% or the non-profit organizations in India all are fraud. They are just there to earn money. Its a business for them. Social service is not the cause for them.</p>
<p>What do you guys suggest , how can we stop or reduce these kind incidents. I have just given you an idea about dog but there are many other animals that I see dead and ran over by some vehicle.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-can-we-stop-the-killing-of-animals-on-streets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
