<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>internet &#8211; rLOVEutioners</title>
	<atom:link href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tag/internet/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/</link>
	<description>revoution for evolution</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 13:58:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Meet, US</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/meet-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 08:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=408</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="683" src="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/IMG_0858-1024x683.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-579" srcset="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/IMG_0858-1024x683.jpg 1024w, http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/IMG_0858-300x200.jpg 300w, http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/IMG_0858-768x512.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over 365 Cool, Innovative and Best Profile Picture Ideas – Male Only</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/best-facebook-linkedin-orkut-myspace-profile-pics-photos-images-ideas/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/best-facebook-linkedin-orkut-myspace-profile-pics-photos-images-ideas/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 13:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=47</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While I was hunting for suitable theme for Revolutioners, I stumbled upon a theme website. The theme was not that good but the content on that site made me post this article. It had lot of images of a single person. I thought it would be a good idea to have it as a single &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/best-facebook-linkedin-orkut-myspace-profile-pics-photos-images-ideas/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Over 365 Cool, Innovative and Best Profile Picture Ideas – Male Only</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While I was hunting for suitable theme for Revolutioners, I stumbled upon a theme website. The theme was not that good but the content on that site made me post this article. It had lot of images of a single person. I thought it would be a good idea to have it as a single point to refer in case anyone is looking for ideas for his/her next Facebook or any other Social Media profile picture. I saved the whole site as Image and posting it here on my blog. I really liked the ideas of the pictures shown on the blog. If you need inspiration for clicking your own picture for your social website’s profile then look nowhere else. The image is really long and huge in size. So be careful.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323131000im_/http://img24.imageshack.us/img24/5550/facebookprofilepicturei.jpg" alt="Social Networking Profile Picture Idea" width="600"></p>
<p><a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323131000/http://img24.imageshack.us/img24/5550/facebookprofilepicturei.jpg">Link to full size image</a></p>


<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/best-facebook-linkedin-orkut-myspace-profile-pics-photos-images-ideas/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why India need fat pipes?</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-india-need-fat-pipes/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-india-need-fat-pipes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2011 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=45</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you follow tech news you might have heard of Netflix and it’s recent success after adopting the streaming model. Their website says “For only $7.99 a month, you get unlimited movies &#38; TV episodes instantly over the Internet to your TV or computer. There are no commercials, and you can pause, rewind, fast forward &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-india-need-fat-pipes/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Why India need fat pipes?</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you follow tech news you might have heard of <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323133002/http://netflix.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Netflix</a> and it’s recent success after adopting the streaming model. Their website says “For only <strong>$7.99 a month</strong>, you get unlimited movies &amp; TV episodes instantly over the Internet to your TV or computer. There are no commercials, and you can pause, rewind, fast forward or re-watch as often as you like. It’s really that easy!”</p>
<p>Isn’t this great, for just <strong>Rs.400 a month</strong>, Netflix gives Video on demand on a lot of devices (PC,macs, mobile devices, gaming consoles etc.) with recommendations, resuming playback of movies/T.V shows where you left them off and a lot more. So if you’re watching a movie late in the night and you get too sleepy, you can shut off your movie and resume it the next day on your way to work on your phone.  We end up paying more for Tata sky which doesn’t even provide video on demand or multiple device viewing.</p>
<p>This model has helped Netflix become a major success in the US and Canada with Apple choosing to bundle a Netflix app on their Apple TV as well. This gets us wondering, why isn’t there a service similar to Netflix in India?</p>
<p>Although there have been a few companies which have tried to imitate the earlier Netflix model, i.e DVD rentals none of them have become hugely popular nor have they offered attractive policies like no late fees, no due dates etc. There was a <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323133002/http://gigaom.com/2006/09/22/seventymm-indias-netflix/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">post</a> on gigaOM way back in 2006 pegging seventymm as India’s Netflix, obviously the service hasn’t caught on.<br />
The posts points out a major hurdle for video rental services like these, piracy. With every railway station selling CDs of the latest movies on as soon as their release dates for as cheap as <strong>Rs.50 ($1)</strong>, it becomes a bit difficult for the survival of this model, also with increasing penetration of the not-so-fast broadband in India, you see people downloading<strong> 700mb DVD</strong>rips from piratebay even if it takes them 24 hours.</p>
<p>So Indian players haven’t even succeeded in coming on par with the Netflix of the earlier years, let alone the current streaming based Netflix. The rental service not catching up is because these players haven’t been able to come up with an effective strategy, but the non existent streaming based service is majorly because of the pathetic internet service in India.</p>
<p>The Netflix page specifies minimum connection requirements for it to work fine “Watching instantly works with all different levels of broadband, however, we recommend a minimum speed of <strong>500kpbs (0.5MB)</strong>.” In average Indian homes unfortunately this sort of connectivity is absent. Speeds like these if offered by ISPs cost a lot. So right now if an Indian Netflix would startup it would remain restricted to the offices of Indian people where stuff like this isn’t permitted. Also the mobile market isn’t ready yet for on the move media viewing, the 3G tariffs are expensive, carriers aren’t ready yet to carry huge amounts of data on their network and a huge part of Indians still don’t have smart phones.</p>
<p>This coupled with the fact that many Indians don’t want to pay for something digital. For example: They won’t hesitate much to buy pirated CDs and DVDs but they have a problem buying a <strong>$.99</strong> game from the AppStore. Fortunately this mindset is changing with the increasing penetration of Internet banking, online shopping etc. A lot of channels like NDTV, CNN, IBN, etc and events like the IPL are providing live streams online. So one can just hope for a Netflix like service to come up in India in the next five years. If they have enough partnerships for providing content then DTH services are doomed!</p>
<p>It was reported that Netflix’s competitor Google has also  launched a pay-per-view online service, in order to gain more traffic to their new service.</p>
<p><a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323133002/http://www.watblog.com/2011/04/25/why-isnt-an-online-streaming-solution-not-possible-in-india-yet/">Source</a>: I feel that we desperately need faster broadband connection for sure. It will solve a lot of problems. I feel piracy can somehow be reduced by providing faster broadband in homes and mobile phones. I would definitely want to subscribe for a 24×7 movie available for 400 Rs/per month. And save money on my broadband and electricity bill.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/why-india-need-fat-pipes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top must do after you write a New Blog Post</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/after-what-to-do-after-writing-a-new-blog-post/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/after-what-to-do-after-writing-a-new-blog-post/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 10:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=172</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Do you also feel the same way as I do. I mean do you not feel a bit relaxed after writing that post. I get a sense of accomplishment every time and I am sure you do too. But remember that when you’re done writing a new blog post, you still have some work to &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/after-what-to-do-after-writing-a-new-blog-post/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Top must do after you write a New Blog Post</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you also feel the same way as I do. I mean do you not feel a bit relaxed after writing that post. I get a sense of accomplishment every time and I am sure you do too. But remember that when you’re done writing a new blog post, you still have some work to do. There are many things you should be doing after writing a new post and I will try and explain a few of the most important things you should do after every blog post you write.</p>
<p><strong>#1 Edit Your Post</strong></p>
<p>Well, I do it all the time and still end up with some minor typos. Why I am saying you should always edit your post is because I don’t know about other people but I like to write my posts in one go. I am not that blogger who sits back and writes one post in 1 month. So most of the time I write my posts in 10 to 15 minutes max. Don’t publish your post until it has been completely edited and checked for spelling/grammar errors. Read over it carefully and make sure everything flows and that everything is written correctly. Like I said, It doesn’t have to be perfect but you don’t want it to be full of errors either. You also want to make sure all your spelling and punctuation is correct. One good way to do this is to paste it into MS Word and run a spell check. Like I am doing it right now <img class="wp-smiley" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308094704im_/http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_razz.gif" alt=":P" /></p>
<p><strong>#Share the Post on Social Networks</strong></p>
<p>In the recent past a lot of Social boom has happened so everyone is jumping in the wagon. Therefore the next thing you want to do after you write a blog post is to share your post with as many people as you can. There are a lot of social bookmarking websites on the internet that you can use to do this. Some of the best and most popular are Stumbleupon, Digg, Delicious, Mixx, and Reddit. Make sure you bookmark your post to at least a few of them.</p>
<p><strong>#3 Tweet It</strong></p>
<p>Twitter has really picked up the speed in social networking in the last year or so. Its like the small version of big posts. Sometimes people want to elaborate on their thinking and sometimes they just post a shorter version of that. Any which ways twitter is hot nowadays. So after you write a new blog post you should always “tweet” it. Twitter is really popular right now and it only takes a few seconds to tweet your followers about your post. This can give you extra traffic and maybe even a few people will retweet it or link to your post, which will help even more. So make sure you take a little time to tweet about your post whenever you publish a new one.</p>
<p>Alright, that should be enough to get you started. Just remember that after you finish writing a blog post you aren’t done with the work. If you do the things listed above then you will have a much better shot at building a successful blog.</p>
<p><strong>#4 Comment on other Blogs with post link</strong></p>
<p>This in my views is one of the most effective way ot getting traffic to your blog or site. As soon as you write a post, start going to your favorite blogs and comment with url of the new post that you written. Give the Name accordingly. Some Blog admins don’t mind accepting your name as your blog name if the comment adds something to the conversation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/after-what-to-do-after-writing-a-new-blog-post/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Indian forums to buy/sell Online</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/buy-sell-old-stuff-in-india/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/buy-sell-old-stuff-in-india/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 09:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=157</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Do you have a lot of old computer junk in your house ? Thinking of selling that old car of yours but afraid to go to the dealers ? Don’t have time to find buyers ? Well, then the good news is that you don’t have to run after the buyer anymore. There is a &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/buy-sell-old-stuff-in-india/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Top Indian forums to buy/sell Online</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you have a lot of old computer junk in your house ? Thinking of selling that old car of yours but afraid to go to the dealers ? Don’t have time to find buyers ? Well, then the good news is that you don’t have to run after the buyer anymore. There is a growing community of buying and selling old stuff online day by day in India. I am proving you with the resource where one buy and sell old stuff in India.&nbsp; It all works on trust. People buy and sell stuff purely basis the trust they have gained in the community.&nbsp; These communities are so popular now the the dealers from every corner from India go and register there and provide the products at cheaper rates compared to market. Rest, Go on and register and check them out yourself.</p>
<ol>
<li><a href="http://www.team-bhp.com/forum/classifieds/" rel="nofollow">Team bhp</a> – This is an Automotive Community in India. Very popular. You can buy and sell almost anything here. Cars, Bikes and Gadgets.</li>
<li>Tech Enclave &#8211;&nbsp; Techenclave is my first forum which inspired me to write this post. I started buying and selling stuff in this forum first. Again buy and sell anything here but as the name suggests most of the stuff is related to computers. Group Orders is the most.</li>
<li><a href="http://www.erodov.com/forums/bazaar/" rel="nofollow">Erodov</a> – Erodov is one neat forum with buy and sell section optimized to the fullest. With clear categories defined for buyers and sellers I have started loving Erodov now.</li>
<li><a href="http://www.rimweb.in/forums/forum/50-buy-sell-bazaar/" rel="nofollow">Rim Web</a> – Rimweb may be one of the oldest mobile community. I registered here when I started using Reliance Mobile. I still use it <img class="wp-smiley" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308094606im_/http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_razz.gif" alt=":P"> Well people come here and buy sell their mobile phones primarily. You can also find other stuff here. But primarily, Mobiles.</li>
<li><a href="http://www.hifivision.com/classifieds/" rel="nofollow">HiFi Vision</a> – HiFi Vision is the most renowned Indian forum related to audio and video. Its like the AVS Forum but that is for the bigger world. HiFi Vision is for Indian Audio-Videophiles.</li>
<li><a href="http://www.thinkdigit.com/forum/bazaar/" rel="nofollow">Think Digit</a> – ThinkDigit forum is the official forum from the tech magazine company called Think Digit. Mostly the reader of the magazine come here and buy sell their old computer related stuff.</li>
<li><a href="http://www.xbhp.com/classifieds/" rel="nofollow">xBhp</a> – xBhp is one of the most browsed Biking Community Forum in India. So here, what to expect other than bikes. If you are thinking about selling that old bike. Go there.</li>
<li><a href="http://forums.techarena.in/buy-sell-computer-hardware/" rel="nofollow">Tech Arena</a> &#8211;&nbsp; To be very frank and true, I don’t have any idea about this forum as I never visited this one. I found this forum had a Buy/Sell category and a considerable amount of post in that section so I thought it would be good to share the link with you. No harm in sharing anything. right !</li>
<li>India Broadband Forum &#8211;&nbsp; Oh.. Indian Broadband Forum started with the Broadband scene in India but then gradually picked up many other topics and now is a full fledged tech forum with variety of topics. I am a regular visitor to this forum from the last 4-5 years at least. I registered here when I used to use Sify Broadband. Yeah ! those were the best days of my life. that dc++ hub. I still miss it.. Anyways, again never went to the buy/sell section on this forum, but since the traffic to this forum is huge so I am expecting people do trade here.</li>
<li><a href="http://www.jjmehta.com/forum/index.php?board=8.0" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">JJMehta </a>&#8211; This forums is for Photography enthusiasts so obviously you can sell and purchase photography equipments like Camera, dSLR and Lenses.</li>
</ol>
<p>Mostly you would find people selling their stuff in multiple forums i.e. they are registered on all of the forums.</p>
<p><strong>Important : Please read the rules of the respective forums as they all operate on their own rules and regulations. You don’t wanna get burnt as soon as you start.</strong></p>
<p>I know I have missed a lot of good forums. I will keep updating the list whenever I get to know about anything new. But I listed the ones I knew and am a regular visitor. If you have a longer list do let me know I will definitely add them here.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/buy-sell-old-stuff-in-india/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to use Hiren Boot CD programs with switches</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/notron-ghost-switches-hiren-bootcd-application-switches-command-prompt/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/notron-ghost-switches-hiren-bootcd-application-switches-command-prompt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 10:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=176</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Last night it look me over 3 hours to understand the problem why Norton Ghost was acting weird. I was not able to clone my laptop hard drive with an existing image. The image was correct and consistent however Norton Ghost while restoring kept giving me some inconsistency errors. Image was created with a 160 &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/notron-ghost-switches-hiren-bootcd-application-switches-command-prompt/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">How to use Hiren Boot CD programs with switches</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Last night it look me over 3 hours to understand the problem why Norton Ghost was acting weird. I was not able to clone my laptop hard drive with an existing image. The image was correct and consistent however Norton Ghost while restoring kept giving me some inconsistency errors. Image was created with a 160 GB partition and I was restoring it on 320 GB drive. I tried both ways to restore. Image to Drive and Image to Disk. But every time it gave me inconsistency errors.<br />
<span id="more-2028"></span></p>
<p>Finally after some research I found out the solution for the problem. There are various switches that you can use on command line Ghost. I had to use <strong>-ntc-</strong> switch. This switch basically Disables NTFS contiguous run allocation which makes the image to be restored on any hard drive with any size of drive. But unfortunately when you use Hiren Bootcd you can not run Ghost with any switch.</p>
<p>But suddenly all my problems were solved. Actually what happens is whenever you run any program from the menu it first gets extracted and then gets saved in the RAM drive created by the CD. That’s it. That was the solution.</p>
<p>To run Ghost or any other program from Hiren Bootcd with switches follow the steps below:</p>
<ol>
<li>Boot with Hiren BootCD.</li>
<li>Run a program of your choice. I was using Ghost so I will continue with Ghost with the example.</li>
<li>Once Ghost is up and running <strong>Exi</strong>t it without doing anything.</li>
<li>It will take you back to the Command Prompt.</li>
<li>Now use <strong>Ghost.exe -ntc-</strong></li>
<li>That’s it. Similarily you can use any program with their compatible switches. All you need to do is run it first and then exit it.</li>
</ol>
<p>Pretty Simple huh !!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/notron-ghost-switches-hiren-bootcd-application-switches-command-prompt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ISRO’s Bhuvan will not help the terrorists while Google Earth helped – What a Joke</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/isros-bhuvan-will-not-help-the-terrorists-while-google-earth-helped-what-a-joke/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/isros-bhuvan-will-not-help-the-terrorists-while-google-earth-helped-what-a-joke/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 18:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=89</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ISRO announced today that they will bring Bhuvan the Google Earth competitor in the market. The main feature of ISRO Bhuvan would be that compared to Google Earth, ISRO Bhuvan will be able to zoom till 10 meter anywhere in India. Now tell me last time when terrorists attacked on Parliament and 26/11, our politicians &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/isros-bhuvan-will-not-help-the-terrorists-while-google-earth-helped-what-a-joke/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">ISRO’s Bhuvan will not help the terrorists while Google Earth helped – What a Joke</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ISRO announced today that they will bring Bhuvan the Google Earth competitor in the market. The main feature of <a href="http://www.revolutioners.com/isro-chandrayaan-fails-plans-to-waste-money-again-with-chandrayaan-2/">ISRO</a> Bhuvan would be that compared to Google Earth, ISRO Bhuvan will be able to zoom till 10 meter anywhere in India. Now tell me last time when terrorists attacked on Parliament and 26/11, our politicians said that these guys used Google earth. Will they not have a better tool now. I am not able to understand why <span class="removed_link" title="http://www.revolutioners.com/commonwealth-games-2010-things-you-can-do-to-contribute-for-a-successful-event/">Indian Government</span> is funding such pathetic projects. Another such example of failure is Chandrayaan. I mean I don’t understand why would India send a satellite on moon to find out what ? US have done the research there is nothing that Indian scientists will reveal now. And whatever happened was expected out of it. Chandrayaan was utter failure. All Indian tax payer’s money is going in vain. Nothing is being done for the safety of civilians.</p>
<p>We are still living in the same unprotected world where you don’t know whether you will be alive tomorrow or not. People are so scared to come out of their houses. If there is no terrorist attacks then there are internal terrorists, I mean every day you hear about kidnapping, murders and robberies. Everyday there is a new story about crime. I am sick and tired of listening to these kind of news. I wish I could do something about it. Our law and order needs to be changed. People after being convicted as well roam freely in India. That&#8217;s how our law works. Anyways, I think I deviated from the topic. So what I was saying is that the same way we failed in <a href="http://www.revolutioners.com/isro-chandrayaan-fails-plans-to-waste-money-again-with-chandrayaan-2/">Chandrayaan</a>. ISRO Bhuvan is also going to fail, these guys don’t know what they are up against. Its Google.</p>
<p>Oh my God. We seriously need some developers in Indian Government Department. <a href="http://www.revolutioners.com/where-the-hell-are-indian-web-developers/">Our government websites are damn funny</a>. I can’t even begin to tell you.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/isros-bhuvan-will-not-help-the-terrorists-while-google-earth-helped-what-a-joke/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indian Developers &#8211; Help Indian Government</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/where-the-hell-are-indian-web-developers/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/where-the-hell-are-indian-web-developers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 08:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=155</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What are you thinking now ? Does India not have good Web Developers ? Why Indian Govt websites are such pathetic to look. Is Indian Govt running out of Funds for spending money on our Country’s website. I mean this is the only thing the world looks at now days for a legitimate source of &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/where-the-hell-are-indian-web-developers/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Indian Developers &#8211; Help Indian Government</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What are you thinking now ? Does India not have good Web Developers ? Why Indian Govt websites are such pathetic to look. Is Indian Govt running out of Funds for spending money on our Country’s website. I mean this is the only thing the world looks at now days for a legitimate source of information. I feel Indian Govt websites are created just for the sake of creating them. So what do you think is responsible for this situation. Let me tell you one thing before you come to any conclusion. India has more than 50% of the Software Development Industry business. Its our sick old politicians. Who, in 21st Century don’t even know how a computer is operated. Till the time we have the old generation ruling India, we the younger generation will keep facing the issues.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/where-the-hell-are-indian-web-developers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
