<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>economy &#8211; rLOVEutioners</title>
	<atom:link href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tag/economy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/</link>
	<description>revoution for evolution</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 13:57:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Top Indian forums to buy/sell Online</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/buy-sell-old-stuff-in-india/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/buy-sell-old-stuff-in-india/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 09:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=157</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Do you have a lot of old computer junk in your house ? Thinking of selling that old car of yours but afraid to go to the dealers ? Don’t have time to find buyers ? Well, then the good news is that you don’t have to run after the buyer anymore. There is a &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/buy-sell-old-stuff-in-india/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Top Indian forums to buy/sell Online</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you have a lot of old computer junk in your house ? Thinking of selling that old car of yours but afraid to go to the dealers ? Don’t have time to find buyers ? Well, then the good news is that you don’t have to run after the buyer anymore. There is a growing community of buying and selling old stuff online day by day in India. I am proving you with the resource where one buy and sell old stuff in India.&nbsp; It all works on trust. People buy and sell stuff purely basis the trust they have gained in the community.&nbsp; These communities are so popular now the the dealers from every corner from India go and register there and provide the products at cheaper rates compared to market. Rest, Go on and register and check them out yourself.</p>
<ol>
<li><a href="http://www.team-bhp.com/forum/classifieds/" rel="nofollow">Team bhp</a> – This is an Automotive Community in India. Very popular. You can buy and sell almost anything here. Cars, Bikes and Gadgets.</li>
<li>Tech Enclave &#8211;&nbsp; Techenclave is my first forum which inspired me to write this post. I started buying and selling stuff in this forum first. Again buy and sell anything here but as the name suggests most of the stuff is related to computers. Group Orders is the most.</li>
<li><a href="http://www.erodov.com/forums/bazaar/" rel="nofollow">Erodov</a> – Erodov is one neat forum with buy and sell section optimized to the fullest. With clear categories defined for buyers and sellers I have started loving Erodov now.</li>
<li><a href="http://www.rimweb.in/forums/forum/50-buy-sell-bazaar/" rel="nofollow">Rim Web</a> – Rimweb may be one of the oldest mobile community. I registered here when I started using Reliance Mobile. I still use it <img class="wp-smiley" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308094606im_/http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_razz.gif" alt=":P"> Well people come here and buy sell their mobile phones primarily. You can also find other stuff here. But primarily, Mobiles.</li>
<li><a href="http://www.hifivision.com/classifieds/" rel="nofollow">HiFi Vision</a> – HiFi Vision is the most renowned Indian forum related to audio and video. Its like the AVS Forum but that is for the bigger world. HiFi Vision is for Indian Audio-Videophiles.</li>
<li><a href="http://www.thinkdigit.com/forum/bazaar/" rel="nofollow">Think Digit</a> – ThinkDigit forum is the official forum from the tech magazine company called Think Digit. Mostly the reader of the magazine come here and buy sell their old computer related stuff.</li>
<li><a href="http://www.xbhp.com/classifieds/" rel="nofollow">xBhp</a> – xBhp is one of the most browsed Biking Community Forum in India. So here, what to expect other than bikes. If you are thinking about selling that old bike. Go there.</li>
<li><a href="http://forums.techarena.in/buy-sell-computer-hardware/" rel="nofollow">Tech Arena</a> &#8211;&nbsp; To be very frank and true, I don’t have any idea about this forum as I never visited this one. I found this forum had a Buy/Sell category and a considerable amount of post in that section so I thought it would be good to share the link with you. No harm in sharing anything. right !</li>
<li>India Broadband Forum &#8211;&nbsp; Oh.. Indian Broadband Forum started with the Broadband scene in India but then gradually picked up many other topics and now is a full fledged tech forum with variety of topics. I am a regular visitor to this forum from the last 4-5 years at least. I registered here when I used to use Sify Broadband. Yeah ! those were the best days of my life. that dc++ hub. I still miss it.. Anyways, again never went to the buy/sell section on this forum, but since the traffic to this forum is huge so I am expecting people do trade here.</li>
<li><a href="http://www.jjmehta.com/forum/index.php?board=8.0" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">JJMehta </a>&#8211; This forums is for Photography enthusiasts so obviously you can sell and purchase photography equipments like Camera, dSLR and Lenses.</li>
</ol>
<p>Mostly you would find people selling their stuff in multiple forums i.e. they are registered on all of the forums.</p>
<p><strong>Important : Please read the rules of the respective forums as they all operate on their own rules and regulations. You don’t wanna get burnt as soon as you start.</strong></p>
<p>I know I have missed a lot of good forums. I will keep updating the list whenever I get to know about anything new. But I listed the ones I knew and am a regular visitor. If you have a longer list do let me know I will definitely add them here.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/buy-sell-old-stuff-in-india/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ISRO Chandrayaan fails – Plans to waste money again with Chandrayaan 2</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/isro-chandrayaan-fails-plans-to-waste-money-again-with-chandrayaan-2/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/isro-chandrayaan-fails-plans-to-waste-money-again-with-chandrayaan-2/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2009 18:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=85</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I saw it coming. I knew ISRO Chandrayaan was going to be a failure. I had doubts and ISRO has not left me with any doubts now. Our government has already wasted m0ney on ISRO Bhuvan and now this. ISRO chairman Madhavan Nair has confirmed: “We will have to face the reality but we will have &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/isro-chandrayaan-fails-plans-to-waste-money-again-with-chandrayaan-2/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">ISRO Chandrayaan fails – Plans to waste money again with Chandrayaan 2</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I saw it coming. I knew <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308094546/http://www.revolutioners.com/google-earth-helped-terrorists-but-isro-bhuvan-will-not-what-a-joke/">ISRO Chandrayaan</a> was going to be a failure. I had doubts and ISRO has not left me with any doubts now. Our government has already wasted m0ney on <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308094546/http://www.revolutioners.com/google-earth-helped-terrorists-but-isro-bhuvan-will-not-what-a-joke/">ISRO Bhuvan </a>and now this.</p>
<blockquote><p>ISRO chairman Madhavan Nair has confirmed: “We will have to face the reality but we will have a better opportunity tomorrow.”<br />
<span id="more-1364"></span></p></blockquote>
<p>These guys aren’t over yet. They still wants to waste our money. I am not in favor of these kinds of missions. As stated earlier I want our government to invest in Indian Infrastructure. Build new Railway tracks, build new airports, build better roads; I mean there are millions of things that our government could do. Our government just simply wasted 81 million $ which could have been utilized in a better manner.  It does not matter whether we spent lesser money compared to what others have. All that matters is that we did waste money. And what is bothering me now is that our government is not ready to learn any lesson from this.</p>
<p>“The mission is definitely over. We have lost contact with the spacecraft,” Mayilsamy Annadurai, Project Director of the Chandrayaan-1, told PTI. He said the mission had almost completed its scientific objectives. <strong>“It has done its job technically … 100 per cent. Scientifically also, it has done almost 90-95 per cent of its job,”</strong> said Mr. Annadurai.</p>
<p>What job are we talking about here. What did ISRO Chandrayaan achieve. I am not sure. Can someone throw some light on the achievements of our ISRO Chandrayaan mission apart from some pictures being taken from it.</p>
<p>The mission was built to be failed. Its been proven now.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/isro-chandrayaan-fails-plans-to-waste-money-again-with-chandrayaan-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
