<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>psychology &#8211; rLOVEutioners</title>
	<atom:link href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tag/psychology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/</link>
	<description>revoution for evolution</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 14:49:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>मैॅ तो बस बोलता हूॅ</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/main-to-bas-bolta-hoon/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/main-to-bas-bolta-hoon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 05:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/?p=526</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[लिखने का शौक तो नहीॅपर शब्दोॅ मेॅ रस घोलता हूॅजाने अनजाने ही सहीपर कडवा सच बोलता हूॅजीवन के अनसुलझे रहस्योॅ कोपरत दर परत खोलता हूॅ इसलिए &#8230;मैॅ तो बस बोलता हूॅ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>लिखने का शौक तो नहीॅ<br>पर शब्दोॅ मेॅ रस घोलता हूॅ<br>जाने अनजाने ही सही<br>पर कडवा सच बोलता हूॅ<br>जीवन के अनसुलझे रहस्योॅ को<br>परत दर परत खोलता हूॅ<br><br>इसलिए &#8230;<br>मैॅ तो बस बोलता हूॅ<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/main-to-bas-bolta-hoon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bhagat Singh</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/bhagat-singh/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 07:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=427</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[“Leave sentimentalism aside. Be prepared to face the facts. Revolution is a very difficult task. It is beyond the power of any man to make a revolution. Neither can it be brought about on any appointed date. It is brought about by special environments, social and economic. The function of an organized party is to &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/bhagat-singh/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Bhagat Singh</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre id="tw-target-text" class="tw-data-text tw-ta tw-text-small" dir="ltr" data-placeholder="Translation" data-fulltext=""><span lang="hi">
“Leave sentimentalism aside. Be prepared to face the facts. Revolution is a very difficult task. It is beyond the power of any man to make a revolution. Neither can it be brought about on any appointed date. It is brought about by special environments, social and economic. The function of an organized party is to utilize such an opportunity offered by these circumstances. [To] prepare the masses and organize the forces for the revolution is a very difficult task. And that requires a very great sacrifice on the part of the revolutionary workers.”

<strong>Bhagat Singh</strong> in a letter “To the young political workers”, 2 February 1931

</span></pre>
<pre id="tw-target-text" class="tw-data-text tw-ta tw-text-small" dir="ltr" data-placeholder="Translation" data-fulltext=""><span lang="hi">
भावुक होना छोड़ दें।
और सच का सामना करने के लिए तैयार हो जाऍ।
क्रांति करना एक असाधारण कार्य है।
और क्रांति का उद्घोष करना किसी एक व्यक्ति विशेष की शक्ति से परे है।
और न ही इसे किसी एक सुनिश्चित समय पर लाया जा सकता है।
क्रांति विशेषतः, अनुकूल सामाजिक और आर्थिक परिस्थितियों द्वारा लाई जाती है।
एक सुव्यवस्थित संगठन का कर्तव्य इन परिस्थितियों द्वारा उत्पन्न किए जाने वाले अवसरोॅ का सदुपयोग करना है।
[जनता को] क्रांति के लिये तैयार करना और क्रांतिकारी ताकतोॅ को सॅगठित करना एक बहुत ही मुश्किल काम है।
और इसके लिए क्रांतिकारीयोॅ को एक महान त्याग करने की आवश्यकता है।

<strong>भगत सिॅह</strong> का २ फरवरी १९३१ को "युवा राजनैतिक कार्यकर्ताओॅ " के लिये लिखा पत्र 

</span></pre>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meet, US</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/meet-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 08:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=408</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="683" src="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/IMG_0858-1024x683.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-579" srcset="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/IMG_0858-1024x683.jpg 1024w, http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/IMG_0858-300x200.jpg 300w, http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/IMG_0858-768x512.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Diwali &#8211; Plan Baksheesh</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/plan-baksheesh/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/plan-baksheesh/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 09:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=166</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Around Diwali, the usual constant stream of “visitors” will show up. The crew of building watchmen (half a dozen of whom you’ve never seen before), the janitor, the postman, the maid, and probably some random strangers chancing their luck – they will all knock on your door looking for Diwali “Baksheesh.” Baksheesh is a term &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/plan-baksheesh/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">This Diwali &#8211; Plan Baksheesh</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Around Diwali, the usual constant stream of “visitors” will show up. The crew of building watchmen (half a dozen of whom you’ve never seen before), the janitor, the postman, the maid, and probably some random strangers chancing their luck – they will all knock on your door looking for Diwali “Baksheesh.” <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Baksheesh">Baksheesh</a> is a term that loosely refers to either a tip or, interestingly, a bribe.</p>
<p>For people, the popularity of tipping has always been something of a mystery. Take restaurant tipping as a typical example. Since the tip is usually given at the end of the meal, what good purpose does it serve? Since the service has already been provided, it can’t by definition affect the quality of the service you received? It would make sense maybe for a repeat customer on the basis that a kind tip would lead to the probability of better service next time.</p>
<p>But <a href="http://www.ft.com/intl/cms/s/0/be390fbe-a893-11d9-87a9-00000e2511c8.html#axzz1bhFznael">researchers</a> have something else to say. As per the researchers, tipping is equally likely to yield same service whether a customer plans to return or not. The consensus seems to be that tipping is best understood as a social norm, a form of charitable giving tied to the provision of a service.</p>
<p><span id="more-3341"></span>But back to the folks knocking on your door.  Should you be giving them? Why do they expect a tip at Diwali, when you tend to tip them anyway throughout the year, such as when the watchman helps bring up a heavy parcel, or maid comes thrice a day on your request?</p>
<p>During Diwali, Its believed and wise to make necessary pay-outs to avoid sudden disruption of services. So try the formula desribed below and let me know what difference did it make:</p>
<ol>
<li> Begin with a firm budget. Make sure you have in mind about how much to spend on Baksheesh during the festive season well in advance.</li>
<li>Prepare a list of service-providers in descending order of importance. Like Milkman, Sweeper, Maid, Newspaper Wallah, Watchman etc.</li>
<li>Divide the service providers into 2 different lists. First, those who need to be motivated and second, those who need recognition.</li>
<li>Now divide each list further into 3 parts, depending the importance of work they do for you and your family. The persons in the <strong>first list</strong> are the most important service providers like the maid, watchman and liftman. If anyone of them is disappointed, it results in immediate fall-out action. The maid will come late, much after your wife or mom has completed half the housework. The watchman will permit hawkers to knock at our door in the afternoons and spoil your siesta. And the liftman will declare that the lift is under repair and ensure that you climb six floors. They, therefore, should be given top most priority.</li>
<li>In the <strong>second list</strong> houses service providers that are not so important but are required alm0st everyday like, the milkman, the washerwoman and the sweeper. Since the milkman and washerwoman are paid on a daily basis, they recognise that we may have some cash-flow problems. They seem satisfied with smaller amounts. The sweeper, however, needs to be handled with care. He has the power to skip a few days’ garbage collection and cause serious nasal disorder.</li>
<li>The<strong> third list</strong> consists of the people that are not so important like, telephone, post and telegraph community. This list does not evoke too much concern. The importance of the telephone lineman has taken a huge dip. A faulty line does not bother people any more in these days of the mobile phone except you are the broadband subscriber. The post and telegraph group too does not attract too much money. The e-mail has made letter-writing redundant. Therefore you may want to keep service providers alike in this list.</li>
</ol>
<p>A little off topic, there’s a certain irony in being expected to offer a Diwali Baksheesh to someone like the postman who is a government employee and is supposed to do his job without expecting or receiving a tip. Perhaps the double meaning of Baksheesh is fitting here since people have become used to paying bribes for services that they’re entitled to.</p>
<p>I have always remained a keen observer of these Diwali pay-outs over the last so many years and am fascinated by the methods employed by the beneficiaries to gain more handsome pay-outs. Each one carries a list of neighbourhood donors. We know our neighbours well enough to realise that the figures are grossly exaggerated. This is an old technique called <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peer_pressure">Peer Pressure</a>.</p>
<p>I am also intrigued by the fact that the beneficiaries never come in a bunch. They stagger their time of arrival through careful networking, without doubt. All said, the Diwali baksheesh — both the handing and receiving of it — is an interesting exercise in human management.</p>
<p>Thanks for reading. Happy Diwali to you and your familiy in advance.</p>
<p>If you like the post then take 2 minutes and share it with your friends and family. Also do let me know via comments if it helped you or not?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/plan-baksheesh/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smoking Ban Act, India – Must Read</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/smoking-and-tobacco-facts-and-figures-india-smoking-ban-india/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/smoking-and-tobacco-facts-and-figures-india-smoking-ban-india/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 18:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=80</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Let’s see the scene of tobacco and smoking in India first. OK, some facts and figures about Smoking and Tobacco in India. In India, tobacco use causes nearly 40 percent of all health problems and 50 percent of all cancers, according to Health Minister, Anbumani Ramadoss. In India The tobacco contributes to 56.4% and 44.9% &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/smoking-and-tobacco-facts-and-figures-india-smoking-ban-india/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Smoking Ban Act, India – Must Read</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Let’s see the scene of tobacco and smoking in India first. OK, some facts and figures about Smoking and Tobacco in India.</p>
<ul>
<li>In India, tobacco use causes nearly 40 percent of all health problems and 50 percent of all cancers, according to Health Minister, Anbumani Ramadoss.</li>
<li>In India The tobacco contributes to 56.4% and 44.9% of cancers in men and women, respectively.</li>
<li><strong>India ranks 2nd in smoking cigarette in top 10 countries.</strong></li>
<li>Nearly 17 percent of students in India, aged 15 and under, use some form of tobacco, mainly cigarettes, according to a survey conducted by the World Health Organization.</li>
<li>India has the largest number of oral cancer cases in the world which is due to tobacco.</li>
<li>In India, an estimated 120 million people smoke. But the problem is that smoking in India is on rising side unlike Western countries.</li>
<li>Cigarettes compromise just 19 percent of tobacco consumption in India however Bidis account for 53 percent, according to the Bidi Smoking and Public Health report by the Union Ministry of Health and Family.</li>
<li><strong>Around 1 billion Bidis are sold in India every year.</strong> Bidis contain more tar, nicotine and other toxic substances but less tobacco than traditional cigarettes.</li>
<li>Tobacco smoking accounts for 82% of Chronic obstructive lung disease in India.</li>
</ul>
<p>It’s been around 1 year now that Indian Government imposed ban on smoking in public places including government and private offices. You might not know but this act was in existence for 2 years before our government thought of implementing it seriously. Seriously, imagine. We create acts, put them in files, make a pile out of it, put them in a room somewhere and then don’t look at them for 3-4 years. Then suddenly you wake up and try to enforce everything. And I’ll tell you some facts about this so called smoking ban in public places today. Well, I think I don’t really have to tell you anything as most of you already know it to some extent.</p>
<p>Alright let’s first discuss what the ban exactly is. As per the government, no one is allowed to smoke in public places including public transportation and public offices etc. As per the rules, smoking is banned in shopping malls, cinema halls, public/private work place, hotels, banquet halls, discotheques, canteen, coffee house, pubs, bars, airport lounge, railway stations. Public places cover all government, private and public sector offices as well. I work with an MNC and believe me there people adhere to the regulation. People go out of the offices for smoke. Earlier employees could smoke in the office premises but ever since the smoking ban everyone is prohibited to smoke inside the office premises. Also, any employer found to be letting its employees smoke inside the office premises are supposed to be penalized. Moreover I think people working with big MNCs in India are mature enough to understand what it means for our country. We tell clients coming from abroad that there are restrictions on smoking inside the premises, so we don’t want them to see us smoking in there.</p>
<p><span id="more-2359"></span>Alright, that’s the rule now lets see how is our government who imposed the ban is doing about it. You remember me <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308104834/http://www.revolutioners.com/visit-to-mtnl-sanchaar-haat-a-must-read/">visiting MTNL office</a>, I saw employees smoking inside the building. Well, that was not it. I shave seen many more government offices with people smoking inside the offices. But today was the height of everything, I went to a government office today (would not want to quote) and saw employee smoking in the building that too on his seat as well. And the head of the office was also smoking in the office.</p>
<p>I just want to understand why has it always been like this? <strong>Why do we citizens only have to follow all the rules?</strong> Why the people who create the rules, don’t have to adhere to them.</p>
<p>And believe me its not the only thing which is wrong these days Things like these keep happening in our country. It has been in existence in one or another form with each and every government department of India. <strong>For example, Delhi Police does not need any helmet while driving on the road but they want each and every rider in Delhi to wear helmet and don’t miss a chance of not giving ticket to the rider if he/she is not wearing the helmet.</strong>Similarly they want everyone to wear seat-belts while driving even if the traffic is not even moving. <em>Every government department you go in, you’d find yourself on the verge of having an argument all the time</em>. People don’t really seem to take their jobs seriously.</p>
<p>I am not able to understand the mentality of our government employees as in why do these people behave like this. I mean its good that you are sitting there in a government office but aren’t you suppose to work. Yeah, let me not just start that. I’d need an entire book on that just one post won’t be enough I guess.</p>
<p>Don’t know when would we be free, free as in FREE…! The ultimate question is should we try and ban these things from selling or should we ban smoking of cigarettes. ?</p>
<p>Some interesting reading about tobacco and smoking.</p>
<ul>
<li>Avoiding tobacco adds 20 years to the life of a teenager.</li>
<li><strong>In India, 900,000 people die due to tobacco related diseases per year.</strong></li>
<li>Tobacco smoking accounts for 82% of Chronic obstructive lung disease in India.</li>
<li><strong>Tobacco indirectly causes lung tuberculosis.</strong> Prevalence of TB is about 3 times as great among the ever-smokers as among the never-smokers. The heavier the smoking, either cigarettes or bidis, the greater the prevalence of TB among smokers. Mortality from TB is 3 to 4 times as great in ever-smokers as in never-smokers.</li>
<li><strong>About half of the teenagers who use tobacco will eventually be killed by it (about a quarter in middle age and a quarter in old age).</strong></li>
<li>It is estimated that India as compared to any other country will have the fastest rise in tobacco related deaths each year.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/smoking-and-tobacco-facts-and-figures-india-smoking-ban-india/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What if there was nothing immoral</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/lets-for-once-assume-that-there-is-nothing-bad-or-wrong-in-this-world/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/lets-for-once-assume-that-there-is-nothing-bad-or-wrong-in-this-world/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 13:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Well lets just once assume in this world. I mean let the person kill someone if he wants to. Let a person rob someone if he wishes to. Let anyone become a suicide bomber or a terrorist if he/she wants to do it under someone’s influence. What a world would that be. It would be &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/lets-for-once-assume-that-there-is-nothing-bad-or-wrong-in-this-world/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">What if there was nothing immoral</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Well lets just once assume in this world. I mean let the person kill someone if he wants to. Let a person rob someone if he wishes to. Let anyone become a suicide bomber or a terrorist if he/she wants to do it under someone’s influence. What a world would that be. It would be horrific, right. No, It would not be horrible, It would be great because the way I look at it is that if we use the technology to an extent where all these bad activities would not even be remotely possible. I would want to live in a world like that.<br />
<span id="more-1670"></span></p>
<p>I wish technology advances so much that it does not leave any chance of error for humans. For example</p>
<ul>
<li>People could freely shop online and never be afraid of their bank details being leaked and hacked.</li>
<li>I want the examination system to be like that it does not let anyone cheat.</li>
<li>A world where if a crime is committed the culprit can never escape and gets the punishment instantly.</li>
<li>A world where piracy will not be illegal. It will be legal because it would be upto the publishers to protect their creations/products/music/movies etc. And because the technology would be so strong that it does not even leave a chance for anyone to pirate.</li>
<li>Where Microsoft does not have to be afraid over WGA cracks anymore because they know that their activation process is so amazing that no one can make copies.</li>
</ul>
<p>What do you think about it ? Do you wanna live into that kind of world. Where you have all the freedom to do anything in this world and no one would complain about that.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/lets-for-once-assume-that-there-is-nothing-bad-or-wrong-in-this-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Learn to Drive rash on Indian Roads</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2009 19:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What is this all about ? What the crap ? What the hell is wrong with Kuldeep ? Why is he writing on such a pathetic topic? While your mind is flooded with all these kinds of questions, there goes one more. Ever wondered how any people die just because of rash driving. I know &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Learn to Drive rash on Indian Roads</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What is this all about ? What the crap ? What the hell is wrong with Kuldeep ? Why is he writing on such a pathetic topic? While your mind is flooded with all these kinds of questions, there goes one more. Ever wondered how any people die just because of rash driving. I know what you are thinking now. Alright let me tell you.l I did some digging on this. We are number 1 yey ! According to World Road Statistic data 2007 around 1 million people died in road accident. Now what do you think how many of those 1 million people would have died because of their own mistakes. I would say not more than 50%. So how did the rest of the half a million people die in road accidents. The answer is they all died because some jackass was driving rash.</p>
<p>I also drive rash, But I drive with safety and that too when its required and most of all with intelligence. Yeah, I know what you are thinking. But believe me I don’t act like a school kid who has been just handed over the keys of the car or bike. I have been driving car and riding bikes for the last 8-9 years now. And you know what I am from the most crowded part of India. I am from Delhi. I think anyone who has driven safely on Delhi roads can drive anywhere in the world.  Let me get to the point now because I guess I would have to dedicate a whole new blog to just write about Indian Traffic Rules and Regulations. Its really pathetic how Indian people don’t even think about the traffic rules. And the funny part is the same people who jump traffic signals and break traffic rules, if they go in a different country follow every damn traffic rules. Ever thought why is that the case? Well let me tell you. Its because of our government servants.When we go in a different country we know if we break any traffic rules, the penalty will be so Hugh that they would have to rip their asses off to pay the ticket money. On the other hand in India its mere 100 bucks and that too if you don’t have any policemen in distant relation. But don’t worry if you don’t have any policemen in relation you can just bribe these guys. Just slip a 50 Rs note and you are free.</p>
<p>Alright lets get to the point now. Here are some tips to drive rash on Indian Roads. Believe me they are tried and tested and learnt after 8-9 years of experience.</p>
<h3><strong>Always Drive on left side of the road</strong></h3>
<p>Whenever I have to drive fast, I always drive on the left side of the road. Specially at a crossing. I have met with 2-3 accidents on my bike while I was on the right hand side of the road. The problem is when you are driving on the right hand side you can’t see what is coming from the front because your view is blocked by the railing. <em>And we being Indians we don’t stop/slow down on intersections</em>. Trust me most of the accidents on the road happen because of this reason only. You can’t see what is coming from the right hand side but by the time you realize it, its too late.  But at the same time if you are driving on the left side of the road you have a really good time and view to see if someone is coming from front or right hand side of the road. I have tested it and it really works. I have escaped/saved a lot of accidents this way. So the solution is start driving on the left side while crossing an intersection. I think those railings should be removed from the divider at an intersection for at least around 100 meters so that someone coming on the road can look at both sides of the road if someone is coming or not.</p>
<h3><span class="removed_link" title="http://www.revolutioners.com/commonwealth-games-2010-things-you-can-do-to-contribute-for-a-successful-event/"><strong>Always follow Traffic rules</strong></span></h3>
<p>Indians have just re-engineered the whole traffic signal system. <strong>For us Red means if there is place don’t stop and go on. Yellow is, speed up its going to turn red. Green is, it will turn red hurry up, honk honk and honk.</strong> Damn this is funny. OK. Now this is one of the smartest tips if you ask me. Now you would be thinking how can it be a tip for driving rash. Well the thing is you can drive rash without breaking the rules as well. I mean drive fast, but don’t jump red lights, don’t change lane too often, don’t jump in front of someone like an idiot, don’t keep honking. You know I only drive fast and so called rash when its really required. There is no such pleasure then driving/riding slow. So drive fast/rash until and unless there is a need to it.</p>
<h3><strong>Always look through</strong></h3>
<p>How many times it happened that you were driving really nice and suddenly the person in front of you just stood on the break and your car went creening on the road and you managed to stop the car just an inch away from the car in front of you. It has happened right. So the thing is, if you are driving make sure you are not just watching the car in front of you. Look through the car in front of you. If you see that driver driving madly and stopping suddenly because of xyz reason you have a good amount of time.</p>
<p>I usually not look at the car just in front of me. I watch right into the rear and front mirror and look at the car next to the car in front of me. This way, I keep an eye on the car in front and concentrate on the car that is running in front of the car I am driving behind.</p>
<h3><strong>Don’t play it loud</strong></h3>
<p>Well I am sure people who drive rash they have a nice music system in their cars. When you drive rash and the music is loud you can’t hear anyone honking from the back and then you suddenly try to change the lane. This gets dangerous when that vehicle is two wheeler. So stay put, don’t drive out loud.</p>
<h3><strong>Don’t drink and drive</strong></h3>
<p>Here is the thing. You are drunk and you’ve got friends who are also drunk. Get a drunkard’s cab. Yeah they are in business now. Now what, you show off. You show them how well you can drive. In that madness you drive here and there and that’s it. That is the beginning of the end of your life. Don’t drink and drive. I am speaking from my personal experience.</p>
<p><strong>Share it if you would like to save someone’s life.</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to stop killing animals in road accidents</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-can-we-stop-the-killing-of-animals-on-streets/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-can-we-stop-the-killing-of-animals-on-streets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2009 09:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=162</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed it. You take out your vehicle and start your journey to your usualy daily destination. But suddenly you see a dead street dog on the road. The dog was over ran by some vehicle. I don’t know about you guys, but I get very disappointed and feel bad about it. I &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-can-we-stop-the-killing-of-animals-on-streets/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">How to stop killing animals in road accidents</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever noticed it. You take out your vehicle and start your journey to your usualy daily destination. But suddenly you see a dead street dog on the road. The dog was over ran by some vehicle. I don’t know about you guys, but I get very disappointed and feel bad about it.</p>
<p>I decided to write about it today because I saw one dead dog on the road while coming back from office.</p>
<p>I have seen this a lot of times. Some times really nice dogs are found dead. I am a dog lover. I adore them a lot. It does not matter whether its a street dog or a pet dog.</p>
<p>On this, I am asking your suggestion. How can we reduce these kind of incidents. As of now our government has failed to do anything on this. It takes atleast 2-3 days to clean up that dead body from the road. This is how our Muncipality department works.</p>
<p>Now let me talk more about our non profit organizations. I am not in touch with any of them so I don’t know how well they operate. But I feel except 10% or the non-profit organizations in India all are fraud. They are just there to earn money. Its a business for them. Social service is not the cause for them.</p>
<p>What do you guys suggest , how can we stop or reduce these kind incidents. I have just given you an idea about dog but there are many other animals that I see dead and ran over by some vehicle.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-can-we-stop-the-killing-of-animals-on-streets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
