<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>tricks &#8211; rLOVEutioners</title>
	<atom:link href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tag/tricks/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/</link>
	<description>revoution for evolution</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 13:53:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>This Diwali &#8211; Plan Baksheesh</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/plan-baksheesh/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/plan-baksheesh/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 09:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=166</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Around Diwali, the usual constant stream of “visitors” will show up. The crew of building watchmen (half a dozen of whom you’ve never seen before), the janitor, the postman, the maid, and probably some random strangers chancing their luck – they will all knock on your door looking for Diwali “Baksheesh.” Baksheesh is a term &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/plan-baksheesh/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">This Diwali &#8211; Plan Baksheesh</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Around Diwali, the usual constant stream of “visitors” will show up. The crew of building watchmen (half a dozen of whom you’ve never seen before), the janitor, the postman, the maid, and probably some random strangers chancing their luck – they will all knock on your door looking for Diwali “Baksheesh.” <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Baksheesh">Baksheesh</a> is a term that loosely refers to either a tip or, interestingly, a bribe.</p>
<p>For people, the popularity of tipping has always been something of a mystery. Take restaurant tipping as a typical example. Since the tip is usually given at the end of the meal, what good purpose does it serve? Since the service has already been provided, it can’t by definition affect the quality of the service you received? It would make sense maybe for a repeat customer on the basis that a kind tip would lead to the probability of better service next time.</p>
<p>But <a href="http://www.ft.com/intl/cms/s/0/be390fbe-a893-11d9-87a9-00000e2511c8.html#axzz1bhFznael">researchers</a> have something else to say. As per the researchers, tipping is equally likely to yield same service whether a customer plans to return or not. The consensus seems to be that tipping is best understood as a social norm, a form of charitable giving tied to the provision of a service.</p>
<p><span id="more-3341"></span>But back to the folks knocking on your door.  Should you be giving them? Why do they expect a tip at Diwali, when you tend to tip them anyway throughout the year, such as when the watchman helps bring up a heavy parcel, or maid comes thrice a day on your request?</p>
<p>During Diwali, Its believed and wise to make necessary pay-outs to avoid sudden disruption of services. So try the formula desribed below and let me know what difference did it make:</p>
<ol>
<li> Begin with a firm budget. Make sure you have in mind about how much to spend on Baksheesh during the festive season well in advance.</li>
<li>Prepare a list of service-providers in descending order of importance. Like Milkman, Sweeper, Maid, Newspaper Wallah, Watchman etc.</li>
<li>Divide the service providers into 2 different lists. First, those who need to be motivated and second, those who need recognition.</li>
<li>Now divide each list further into 3 parts, depending the importance of work they do for you and your family. The persons in the <strong>first list</strong> are the most important service providers like the maid, watchman and liftman. If anyone of them is disappointed, it results in immediate fall-out action. The maid will come late, much after your wife or mom has completed half the housework. The watchman will permit hawkers to knock at our door in the afternoons and spoil your siesta. And the liftman will declare that the lift is under repair and ensure that you climb six floors. They, therefore, should be given top most priority.</li>
<li>In the <strong>second list</strong> houses service providers that are not so important but are required alm0st everyday like, the milkman, the washerwoman and the sweeper. Since the milkman and washerwoman are paid on a daily basis, they recognise that we may have some cash-flow problems. They seem satisfied with smaller amounts. The sweeper, however, needs to be handled with care. He has the power to skip a few days’ garbage collection and cause serious nasal disorder.</li>
<li>The<strong> third list</strong> consists of the people that are not so important like, telephone, post and telegraph community. This list does not evoke too much concern. The importance of the telephone lineman has taken a huge dip. A faulty line does not bother people any more in these days of the mobile phone except you are the broadband subscriber. The post and telegraph group too does not attract too much money. The e-mail has made letter-writing redundant. Therefore you may want to keep service providers alike in this list.</li>
</ol>
<p>A little off topic, there’s a certain irony in being expected to offer a Diwali Baksheesh to someone like the postman who is a government employee and is supposed to do his job without expecting or receiving a tip. Perhaps the double meaning of Baksheesh is fitting here since people have become used to paying bribes for services that they’re entitled to.</p>
<p>I have always remained a keen observer of these Diwali pay-outs over the last so many years and am fascinated by the methods employed by the beneficiaries to gain more handsome pay-outs. Each one carries a list of neighbourhood donors. We know our neighbours well enough to realise that the figures are grossly exaggerated. This is an old technique called <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peer_pressure">Peer Pressure</a>.</p>
<p>I am also intrigued by the fact that the beneficiaries never come in a bunch. They stagger their time of arrival through careful networking, without doubt. All said, the Diwali baksheesh — both the handing and receiving of it — is an interesting exercise in human management.</p>
<p>Thanks for reading. Happy Diwali to you and your familiy in advance.</p>
<p>If you like the post then take 2 minutes and share it with your friends and family. Also do let me know via comments if it helped you or not?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/plan-baksheesh/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over 365 Cool, Innovative and Best Profile Picture Ideas – Male Only</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/best-facebook-linkedin-orkut-myspace-profile-pics-photos-images-ideas/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/best-facebook-linkedin-orkut-myspace-profile-pics-photos-images-ideas/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 13:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=47</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While I was hunting for suitable theme for Revolutioners, I stumbled upon a theme website. The theme was not that good but the content on that site made me post this article. It had lot of images of a single person. I thought it would be a good idea to have it as a single &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/best-facebook-linkedin-orkut-myspace-profile-pics-photos-images-ideas/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Over 365 Cool, Innovative and Best Profile Picture Ideas – Male Only</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While I was hunting for suitable theme for Revolutioners, I stumbled upon a theme website. The theme was not that good but the content on that site made me post this article. It had lot of images of a single person. I thought it would be a good idea to have it as a single point to refer in case anyone is looking for ideas for his/her next Facebook or any other Social Media profile picture. I saved the whole site as Image and posting it here on my blog. I really liked the ideas of the pictures shown on the blog. If you need inspiration for clicking your own picture for your social website’s profile then look nowhere else. The image is really long and huge in size. So be careful.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323131000im_/http://img24.imageshack.us/img24/5550/facebookprofilepicturei.jpg" alt="Social Networking Profile Picture Idea" width="600"></p>
<p><a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20120323131000/http://img24.imageshack.us/img24/5550/facebookprofilepicturei.jpg">Link to full size image</a></p>


<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/best-facebook-linkedin-orkut-myspace-profile-pics-photos-images-ideas/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I see a Policeman on motorbike without a Helmet, I stop him and hand him over a ticket</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 13:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=43</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[How cool will that be ? I mean I was just wondering for quite some time now that how nice it would be if we could really take control of our law enforcement. Imagine while roaming on the road you see someone breaking the law and you take out your camera, take a picture while &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">I see a Policeman on motorbike without a Helmet, I stop him and hand him over a ticket</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How cool will that be ? I mean I was just wondering for quite some time now that how nice it would be if we could really take control of our law enforcement. Imagine while roaming on the road you see someone breaking the law and you take out your camera, take a picture while he is breaking the traffic rules. Catch hold of him. Show him the picture and hand over the ticket to him. I mean imagine the force we would have on roads and people will think twice before doing anything wrong.</p>
<p>People may use the power for wrong doing but I think we can start with some intelligent and responsible people like Bus Conductor, Shopkeepers who are sitting on a road watching it all the time. A Pan wallah on the Traffic Signal.</p>
<p>I am thinking of creating another website where I urge people to submit such pictures where people are captured while breaking the law. And our law enforcement team has to just identify the person and fine him/her.</p>
<p>Think about it. Bye !</p>
<p>Let me know your thoughts by posting your comments.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/i-see-a-policeman-on-motorbike-without-a-helmet-i-stop-him-and-hand-him-over-a-ticket/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How about telemarketers get charged 1000 rs for calling you</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 19:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=95</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Every now and then my mind keeps flooding with some insane ideas. But after some time when I think about it, it all starts making some sense. I was on my way to office 2-3 days ago and I get a call from someone trying to sell me some Life Insurance. This guy has been &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">How about telemarketers get charged 1000 rs for calling you</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every now and then my mind keeps flooding with some insane ideas. But after some time when I think about it, it all starts making some sense. I was on my way to office 2-3 days ago and I get a call from someone trying to sell me some Life Insurance. This guy has been calling me for i don’t know may be for the last 4-5 days continuously. I know like me you are also frustrated with all those telemarketers calling you day and night and selling stuff in which you are not even remotely interested. But I have an idea to deal with this situation. I don’t know the feasibility to implement it. May or may not be possible.</p>
<p><span id="more-2318"></span>How about a service which lets you convert your normal mobile phone number to a premium call rate number. I mean I get to choose how much a person pays for a call whenever someone calls me. For example anyone calling me on my mobile would end up paying 100 Rs per minute. This way I would not be able to stop them calling me but I can ask them to call me up again and again and get them to spend money. I take revenge. And the amazing part is that you get paid a handsome amount of money at the end of the month. Because this is how premium call rate numbers work. The organization that owns these premium call rate numbers gets the share from the total revenue generated.</p>
<p><strong>Now let’s talk about the downsides of this idea</strong>. Suppose I setup this service on my mobile and one of my old friends gets hold of my number and calls me up. He would end up paying 100 bucks for the call. Well I have a solution for that. I ask my operator to warn the users who are calling me about the premium call rate. That way anyone calling me would think twice before calling me.</p>
<p><strong>But what about my friends, family and colleagues?</strong> Would they ever be able to call me on my cell phone?  Hmm.. I thought about that also actually. I got this idea from the recently held Apple Special Event, where Steve announced Ping. In Ping you get to choose who follow you. So basically, you get to choose a white list of numbers who would not be charged premium rates.</p>
<blockquote><p>How about your own premium number to fight spam?</p></blockquote>
<p>I know there are solutions like Block List which I used to use. But that is not universal to all phones. I think only on Nokia phones this functionality is available. And moreover the hassle of adding them in the list and keeping them updated. It’s not just worth it. And don’t forget about the limitation of number of phone numbers that you can add.</p>
<p>I need to think about some idea on Mobile Spam, the text messages because they seem to be bugging more than the phone calls.</p>
<p>Oh, one more thing. Did I tell you that well before even any mobile operator implemented this caller tune thing I had this idea in mind. I thought why not have something different than rather just that old boring Tring Tring. And to my surprise Indian Operators introduced Caller Tune to us.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/how-about-your-own-personal-premium-call-rate-number-to-stop-mobile-spam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top must do after you write a New Blog Post</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/after-what-to-do-after-writing-a-new-blog-post/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/after-what-to-do-after-writing-a-new-blog-post/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 10:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=172</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Do you also feel the same way as I do. I mean do you not feel a bit relaxed after writing that post. I get a sense of accomplishment every time and I am sure you do too. But remember that when you’re done writing a new blog post, you still have some work to &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/after-what-to-do-after-writing-a-new-blog-post/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Top must do after you write a New Blog Post</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you also feel the same way as I do. I mean do you not feel a bit relaxed after writing that post. I get a sense of accomplishment every time and I am sure you do too. But remember that when you’re done writing a new blog post, you still have some work to do. There are many things you should be doing after writing a new post and I will try and explain a few of the most important things you should do after every blog post you write.</p>
<p><strong>#1 Edit Your Post</strong></p>
<p>Well, I do it all the time and still end up with some minor typos. Why I am saying you should always edit your post is because I don’t know about other people but I like to write my posts in one go. I am not that blogger who sits back and writes one post in 1 month. So most of the time I write my posts in 10 to 15 minutes max. Don’t publish your post until it has been completely edited and checked for spelling/grammar errors. Read over it carefully and make sure everything flows and that everything is written correctly. Like I said, It doesn’t have to be perfect but you don’t want it to be full of errors either. You also want to make sure all your spelling and punctuation is correct. One good way to do this is to paste it into MS Word and run a spell check. Like I am doing it right now <img class="wp-smiley" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20130308094704im_/http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_razz.gif" alt=":P" /></p>
<p><strong>#Share the Post on Social Networks</strong></p>
<p>In the recent past a lot of Social boom has happened so everyone is jumping in the wagon. Therefore the next thing you want to do after you write a blog post is to share your post with as many people as you can. There are a lot of social bookmarking websites on the internet that you can use to do this. Some of the best and most popular are Stumbleupon, Digg, Delicious, Mixx, and Reddit. Make sure you bookmark your post to at least a few of them.</p>
<p><strong>#3 Tweet It</strong></p>
<p>Twitter has really picked up the speed in social networking in the last year or so. Its like the small version of big posts. Sometimes people want to elaborate on their thinking and sometimes they just post a shorter version of that. Any which ways twitter is hot nowadays. So after you write a new blog post you should always “tweet” it. Twitter is really popular right now and it only takes a few seconds to tweet your followers about your post. This can give you extra traffic and maybe even a few people will retweet it or link to your post, which will help even more. So make sure you take a little time to tweet about your post whenever you publish a new one.</p>
<p>Alright, that should be enough to get you started. Just remember that after you finish writing a blog post you aren’t done with the work. If you do the things listed above then you will have a much better shot at building a successful blog.</p>
<p><strong>#4 Comment on other Blogs with post link</strong></p>
<p>This in my views is one of the most effective way ot getting traffic to your blog or site. As soon as you write a post, start going to your favorite blogs and comment with url of the new post that you written. Give the Name accordingly. Some Blog admins don’t mind accepting your name as your blog name if the comment adds something to the conversation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/after-what-to-do-after-writing-a-new-blog-post/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to use Hiren Boot CD programs with switches</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/notron-ghost-switches-hiren-bootcd-application-switches-command-prompt/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/notron-ghost-switches-hiren-bootcd-application-switches-command-prompt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 10:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=176</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Last night it look me over 3 hours to understand the problem why Norton Ghost was acting weird. I was not able to clone my laptop hard drive with an existing image. The image was correct and consistent however Norton Ghost while restoring kept giving me some inconsistency errors. Image was created with a 160 &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/notron-ghost-switches-hiren-bootcd-application-switches-command-prompt/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">How to use Hiren Boot CD programs with switches</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Last night it look me over 3 hours to understand the problem why Norton Ghost was acting weird. I was not able to clone my laptop hard drive with an existing image. The image was correct and consistent however Norton Ghost while restoring kept giving me some inconsistency errors. Image was created with a 160 GB partition and I was restoring it on 320 GB drive. I tried both ways to restore. Image to Drive and Image to Disk. But every time it gave me inconsistency errors.<br />
<span id="more-2028"></span></p>
<p>Finally after some research I found out the solution for the problem. There are various switches that you can use on command line Ghost. I had to use <strong>-ntc-</strong> switch. This switch basically Disables NTFS contiguous run allocation which makes the image to be restored on any hard drive with any size of drive. But unfortunately when you use Hiren Bootcd you can not run Ghost with any switch.</p>
<p>But suddenly all my problems were solved. Actually what happens is whenever you run any program from the menu it first gets extracted and then gets saved in the RAM drive created by the CD. That’s it. That was the solution.</p>
<p>To run Ghost or any other program from Hiren Bootcd with switches follow the steps below:</p>
<ol>
<li>Boot with Hiren BootCD.</li>
<li>Run a program of your choice. I was using Ghost so I will continue with Ghost with the example.</li>
<li>Once Ghost is up and running <strong>Exi</strong>t it without doing anything.</li>
<li>It will take you back to the Command Prompt.</li>
<li>Now use <strong>Ghost.exe -ntc-</strong></li>
<li>That’s it. Similarily you can use any program with their compatible switches. All you need to do is run it first and then exit it.</li>
</ol>
<p>Pretty Simple huh !!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/notron-ghost-switches-hiren-bootcd-application-switches-command-prompt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Learn to Drive rash on Indian Roads</title>
		<link>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/</link>
					<comments>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ku1deep]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2009 19:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.revolutioners.com/?p=100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What is this all about ? What the crap ? What the hell is wrong with Kuldeep ? Why is he writing on such a pathetic topic? While your mind is flooded with all these kinds of questions, there goes one more. Ever wondered how any people die just because of rash driving. I know &#8230; <a href="http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Learn to Drive rash on Indian Roads</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What is this all about ? What the crap ? What the hell is wrong with Kuldeep ? Why is he writing on such a pathetic topic? While your mind is flooded with all these kinds of questions, there goes one more. Ever wondered how any people die just because of rash driving. I know what you are thinking now. Alright let me tell you.l I did some digging on this. We are number 1 yey ! According to World Road Statistic data 2007 around 1 million people died in road accident. Now what do you think how many of those 1 million people would have died because of their own mistakes. I would say not more than 50%. So how did the rest of the half a million people die in road accidents. The answer is they all died because some jackass was driving rash.</p>
<p>I also drive rash, But I drive with safety and that too when its required and most of all with intelligence. Yeah, I know what you are thinking. But believe me I don’t act like a school kid who has been just handed over the keys of the car or bike. I have been driving car and riding bikes for the last 8-9 years now. And you know what I am from the most crowded part of India. I am from Delhi. I think anyone who has driven safely on Delhi roads can drive anywhere in the world.  Let me get to the point now because I guess I would have to dedicate a whole new blog to just write about Indian Traffic Rules and Regulations. Its really pathetic how Indian people don’t even think about the traffic rules. And the funny part is the same people who jump traffic signals and break traffic rules, if they go in a different country follow every damn traffic rules. Ever thought why is that the case? Well let me tell you. Its because of our government servants.When we go in a different country we know if we break any traffic rules, the penalty will be so Hugh that they would have to rip their asses off to pay the ticket money. On the other hand in India its mere 100 bucks and that too if you don’t have any policemen in distant relation. But don’t worry if you don’t have any policemen in relation you can just bribe these guys. Just slip a 50 Rs note and you are free.</p>
<p>Alright lets get to the point now. Here are some tips to drive rash on Indian Roads. Believe me they are tried and tested and learnt after 8-9 years of experience.</p>
<h3><strong>Always Drive on left side of the road</strong></h3>
<p>Whenever I have to drive fast, I always drive on the left side of the road. Specially at a crossing. I have met with 2-3 accidents on my bike while I was on the right hand side of the road. The problem is when you are driving on the right hand side you can’t see what is coming from the front because your view is blocked by the railing. <em>And we being Indians we don’t stop/slow down on intersections</em>. Trust me most of the accidents on the road happen because of this reason only. You can’t see what is coming from the right hand side but by the time you realize it, its too late.  But at the same time if you are driving on the left side of the road you have a really good time and view to see if someone is coming from front or right hand side of the road. I have tested it and it really works. I have escaped/saved a lot of accidents this way. So the solution is start driving on the left side while crossing an intersection. I think those railings should be removed from the divider at an intersection for at least around 100 meters so that someone coming on the road can look at both sides of the road if someone is coming or not.</p>
<h3><span class="removed_link" title="http://www.revolutioners.com/commonwealth-games-2010-things-you-can-do-to-contribute-for-a-successful-event/"><strong>Always follow Traffic rules</strong></span></h3>
<p>Indians have just re-engineered the whole traffic signal system. <strong>For us Red means if there is place don’t stop and go on. Yellow is, speed up its going to turn red. Green is, it will turn red hurry up, honk honk and honk.</strong> Damn this is funny. OK. Now this is one of the smartest tips if you ask me. Now you would be thinking how can it be a tip for driving rash. Well the thing is you can drive rash without breaking the rules as well. I mean drive fast, but don’t jump red lights, don’t change lane too often, don’t jump in front of someone like an idiot, don’t keep honking. You know I only drive fast and so called rash when its really required. There is no such pleasure then driving/riding slow. So drive fast/rash until and unless there is a need to it.</p>
<h3><strong>Always look through</strong></h3>
<p>How many times it happened that you were driving really nice and suddenly the person in front of you just stood on the break and your car went creening on the road and you managed to stop the car just an inch away from the car in front of you. It has happened right. So the thing is, if you are driving make sure you are not just watching the car in front of you. Look through the car in front of you. If you see that driver driving madly and stopping suddenly because of xyz reason you have a good amount of time.</p>
<p>I usually not look at the car just in front of me. I watch right into the rear and front mirror and look at the car next to the car in front of me. This way, I keep an eye on the car in front and concentrate on the car that is running in front of the car I am driving behind.</p>
<h3><strong>Don’t play it loud</strong></h3>
<p>Well I am sure people who drive rash they have a nice music system in their cars. When you drive rash and the music is loud you can’t hear anyone honking from the back and then you suddenly try to change the lane. This gets dangerous when that vehicle is two wheeler. So stay put, don’t drive out loud.</p>
<h3><strong>Don’t drink and drive</strong></h3>
<p>Here is the thing. You are drunk and you’ve got friends who are also drunk. Get a drunkard’s cab. Yeah they are in business now. Now what, you show off. You show them how well you can drive. In that madness you drive here and there and that’s it. That is the beginning of the end of your life. Don’t drink and drive. I am speaking from my personal experience.</p>
<p><strong>Share it if you would like to save someone’s life.</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://idls.github.io/rLOVEutioners.com/tips-for-rash-driving-on-indian-roads/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
